<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-08-01T23:11:45.993Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 1 Million Domains at Risk of 'Sitting Ducks' Domain Hijacking Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/over-1-million-domains-at-risk-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/over-1-million-domains-at-risk-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a million domains are susceptible to takeover by malicious actors by means of what has been called a Sitting Ducks attack.
The powerful attack vector, which exploits weaknesses in the domain name system (DNS), is being exploited by over a dozen Russian-nexus cybercriminal actors to stealthily hijack domains, a joint analysis published by Infoblox and Eclypsium has revealed.
"In a Sitting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Distributing Malicious Python Packages via Popular Developer Q&A Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-distributing-malicious-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-distributing-malicious-python.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In yet another sign that threat actors are always looking out for new ways to trick users into downloading malware, it has come to light that the question-and-answer (Q&A) platform known as Stack Exchange has been abused to direct unsuspecting developers to bogus Python packages capable of draining their cryptocurrency wallets.
"Upon installation, this code would execute automatically,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Banking Trojan BingoMod Steals Money, Wipes Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-banking-trojan-bingomod.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-banking-trojan-bingomod.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new Android remote access trojan (RAT) called BingoMod that not only performs fraudulent money transfers from the compromised devices but also wipes them in an attempt to erase traces of the malware.
Italian cybersecurity firm Cleafy, which discovered the RAT towards the end of May 2024, said the malware is under active development. It attributed the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obfuscation: There Are Two Sides To Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/obfuscation-there-are-two-sides-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/obfuscation-there-are-two-sides-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to detect and prevent attackers from using these various techniques
Obfuscation is an important technique for protecting software that also carries risks, especially when used by malware authors. In this article, we examine obfuscation, its effects, and responses to it.
What Is Obfuscation?
Obfuscation is the technique of intentionally making information difficult to read, especially in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Adds App-Bound Encryption to Protect Cookies from Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-chrome-adds-app-bound-encryption.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-chrome-adds-app-bound-encryption.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's adding a new layer of protection to its Chrome browser through what's called app-bound encryption to prevent information-stealing malware from grabbing cookies on Windows systems.
"On Windows, Chrome uses the Data Protection API (DPAPI) which protects the data at rest from other users on the system or cold boot attacks," Will Harris from the Chrome security team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0641/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0641/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic Elasticsearch (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0640/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0640/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic Elasticsearch. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0639/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0639/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Ads Lead to Fake Websites Stealing Credit Card Information]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/facebook-ads-lead-to-fake-websites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/facebook-ads-lead-to-fake-websites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook users are the target of a scam e-commerce network that uses hundreds of fake websites to steal personal and financial data using brand impersonation and malvertising tricks.
Recorded Future's Payment Fraud Intelligence team, which detected the campaign on April 17, 2024, has given it the name ERIAKOS owing to the use of the same content delivery network (CDN) oss.eriakos[.]com.
"These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigiCert to Revoke 83,000+ SSL Certificates Due to Domain Validation Oversight]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/digicert-to-revoke-83000-ssl.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/digicert-to-revoke-83000-ssl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certificate authority (CA) DigiCert has warned that it will be revoking a subset of SSL/TLS certificates within 24 hours due to an oversight with how it verified if a digital certificate is issued to the rightful owner of a domain.
The company said it will be taking the step of revoking certificates that do not have proper Domain Control Validation (DCV).
"Before issuing a certificate to a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea-Linked Malware Targets Developers on Windows, Linux, and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korea-linked-malware-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korea-linked-malware-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind an ongoing malware campaign targeting software developers have demonstrated new malware and tactics, expanding their focus to include Windows, Linux, and macOS systems.
The activity cluster, dubbed DEV#POPPER and linked to North Korea, has been found to have singled out victims across South Korea, North America, Europe, and the Middle East.
"This form of attack is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Target Japanese Firms with LODEINFO and NOOPDOOR Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-japanese-firms.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-japanese-firms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese organizations are the target of a Chinese nation-state threat actor that leverages malware families like LODEINFO and NOOPDOOR to harvest sensitive information from compromised hosts while stealthily remaining under the radar in some cases for a time period ranging from two to three years.
Israeli cybersecurity company Cybereason is tracking the campaign under the name Cuckoo Spear,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get the Most From Your Security Team’s Email Alert Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-get-most-from-your-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-get-most-from-your-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ll TL;DR the FUDdy introduction: we all know that phishing attacks are on the rise in scale and complexity, that AI is enabling more sophisticated attacks that evade traditional defenses, and the never-ending cybersecurity talent gap means we’re all struggling to keep security teams fully staffed. 
Given that reality, security teams need to be able to monitor and respond to threats]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Deploy 100K+ Malware Android Apps to Steal OTP Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-deploy-100k-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-deploy-100k-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malicious campaign has been observed making use of malicious Android apps to steal users' SMS messages since at least February 2022 as part of a large-scale campaign.
The malicious apps, spanning over 107,000 unique samples, are designed to intercept one-time passwords (OTPs) used for online account verification to commit identity fraud.
"Of those 107,000 malware samples, over 99,000 of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Espionage Group XDSpy Targets Companies in Russia and Moldova]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-espionage-group-xdspy-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-espionage-group-xdspy-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies in Russia and Moldova have been the target of a phishing campaign orchestrated by a little-known cyber espionage group known as XDSpy.
The findings come from cybersecurity firm F.A.C.C.T., which said the infection chains lead to the deployment of a malware called DSDownloader. The activity was observed this month, it added.
XDSpy is a threat actor of indeterminate origin that was first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic Kibana (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0638/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0638/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic Kibana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager  (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0637/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0637/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0636/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0636/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Settles for $1.4 Billion with Texas Over Illegal Biometric Data Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-settles-for-14-billion-with-texas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-settles-for-14-billion-with-texas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T04:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, the parent company of Facebook, Instagram, and WhatsApp, agreed to a record $1.4 billion settlement with the U.S. state of Texas over allegations that it illegally collected biometric data of millions of users without their permission, marking one of the largest penalties levied by regulators against the tech giant.
"This historic settlement demonstrates our commitment to standing up to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mandrake Spyware Found in Google Play Store Apps After Two Years]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-mandrake-spyware-found-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-mandrake-spyware-found-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new iteration of a sophisticated Android spyware called Mandrake has been discovered in five applications that were available for download from the Google Play Store and remained undetected for two years.
The applications attracted a total of more than 32,000 installations before being pulled from the app storefront, Kaspersky said in a Monday write-up. A majority of the downloads originated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans StormShield Management Center (30 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0635/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0635/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans StormShield Management Center. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power and Peril of RMM Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/the-power-and-peril-of-rmm-tools.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/the-power-and-peril-of-rmm-tools.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more people work remotely, IT departments must manage devices distributed over different cities and countries relying on VPNs and remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools for system administration. 
However, like any new technology, RMM tools can also be used maliciously. Threat actors can establish connections to a victim's device and run commands, exfiltrate data, and stay]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Target Polish Businesses with Agent Tesla and Formbook Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-target-polish-businesses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-target-polish-businesses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detailed widespread phishing campaigns targeting small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in Poland during May 2024 that led to the deployment of several malware families like Agent Tesla, Formbook, and Remcos RAT.
Some of the other regions targeted by the campaigns include Italy and Romania, according to cybersecurity firm ESET.
"Attackers used previously]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Threat Intelligence: Illuminating the Deep, Dark Cybercriminal Underground]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-threat-intelligence-illuminating.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-threat-intelligence-illuminating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
The deep and dark web, otherwise known as the cybercriminal underground, is where malicious actors gather to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (30 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0634/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0634/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T08:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance. Apple indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-23296 est...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SideWinder Cyber Attacks Target Maritime Facilities in Multiple Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-sidewinder-cyber-attacks-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-sidewinder-cyber-attacks-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nation-state threat actor known as SideWinder has been attributed to a new cyber espionage campaign targeting ports and maritime facilities in the Indian Ocean and Mediterranean Sea.
The BlackBerry Research and Intelligence Team, which discovered the activity, said targets of the spear-phishing campaign include countries like Pakistan, Egypt, Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, Myanmar, Nepal, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneDrive Phishing Scam Tricks Users into Running Malicious PowerShell Script]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/onedrive-phishing-scam-tricks-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/onedrive-phishing-scam-tricks-users.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about a new phishing campaign that targets Microsoft OneDrive users with the aim of executing a malicious PowerShell script.
"This campaign heavily relies on social engineering tactics to deceive users into executing a PowerShell script, thereby compromising their systems," Trellix security researcher Rafael Pena said in a Monday analysis.
The cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware ESXi Flaw Exploited by Ransomware Groups for Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vmware-esxi-flaw-exploited-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vmware-esxi-flaw-exploited-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T04:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched security flaw impacting VMware ESXi hypervisors has been actively exploited by "several" ransomware groups to gain elevated permissions and deploy file-encrypting malware.
The attacks involve the exploitation of CVE-2024-37085 (CVSS score: 6.8), an Active Directory integration authentication bypass that allows an attacker to obtain administrative access to the host.
"A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Acronis Cyber Infrastructure Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-acronis-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-acronis-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity company Acronis is warning that a now-patched critical security flaw impacting its Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) product has been exploited in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-45249 (CVSS score: 9.8), concerns a case of remote code execution that stems from the use of default passwords.
The flaw impacts the following versions of Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) -

&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proofpoint Email Routing Flaw Exploited to Send Millions of Spoofed Phishing Emails]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/proofpoint-email-routing-flaw-exploited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/proofpoint-email-routing-flaw-exploited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor has been linked to a massive scam campaign that exploited an email routing misconfiguration in email security vendor Proofpoint's defenses to send millions of messages spoofing various legitimate companies.
"These emails echoed from official Proofpoint email relays with authenticated SPF and DKIM signatures, thus bypassing major security protections — all to deceive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Searchable Encryption Changes the Data Security Game]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-searchable-encryption-changes-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-searchable-encryption-changes-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searchable Encryption has long been a mystery. An oxymoron. An unattainable dream of cybersecurity professionals everywhere.
Organizations know they must encrypt their most valuable, sensitive data to prevent data theft and breaches. They also understand that organizational data exists to be used. To be searched, viewed, and modified to keep businesses running. Unfortunately, our Network and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-034 (29 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-034/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-034/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T08:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stargazer Goblin' Creates 3,000 Fake GitHub Accounts for Malware Spread]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/stargazer-goblin-creates-3000-fake.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/stargazer-goblin-creates-3000-fake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor known as Stargazer Goblin has set up a network of inauthentic GitHub accounts to fuel a Distribution-as-a-Service (DaaS) that propagates a variety of information-stealing malware and netting them $100,000 in illicit profits over the past year.
The network, which comprises over 3,000 accounts on the cloud-based code hosting platform, spans thousands of repositories that are used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gh0st RAT Trojan Targets Chinese Windows Users via Fake Chrome Site]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gh0st-rat-trojan-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gh0st-rat-trojan-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T04:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remote access trojan known as Gh0st RAT has been observed being delivered by an "evasive dropper" called Gh0stGambit as part of a drive-by download scheme targeting Chinese-speaking Windows users.
These infections stem from a fake website ("chrome-web[.]com") serving malicious installer packages masquerading as Google's Chrome browser, indicating that users searching for the software on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Launch Operation to Remove PlugX Malware from Infected Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/french-authorities-launch-operation-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/french-authorities-launch-operation-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French judicial authorities, in collaboration with Europol, have launched a so-called "disinfection operation" to rid compromised hosts of a known malware called PlugX.
The Paris Prosecutor's Office, Parquet de Paris, said the initiative was launched on July 18 and that it's expected to continue for "several months."
It further said around a hundred victims located in France, Malta, Portugal,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious PyPI Package Targets macOS to Steal Google Cloud Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-pypi-package-targets-macos-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-pypi-package-targets-macos-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a malicious package on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that targets Apple macOS systems with the goal of stealing users' Google Cloud credentials from a narrow pool of victims.
The package, named "lr-utils-lib," attracted a total of 59 downloads before it was taken down. It was uploaded to the registry in early June 2024.
"The malware uses a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This AI-Powered Cybercrime Service Bundles Phishing Kits with Malicious Android Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/spanish-hackers-bundle-phishing-kits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/spanish-hackers-bundle-phishing-kits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Spanish-speaking cybercrime group named GXC Team has been observed bundling phishing kits with malicious Android applications, taking malware-as-a-service (MaaS) offerings to the next level.
Singaporean cybersecurity company Group-IB, which has been tracking the e-crime actor since January 2023, described the crimeware solution as a "sophisticated AI-powered phishing-as-a-service platform"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0633/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0633/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T12:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0632/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0632/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0631/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0631/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM QRadar (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0630/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0630/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans IBM QRadar. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0629/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0629/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive AI: The Sine Qua Non of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/offensive-ai-sine-qua-non-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/offensive-ai-sine-qua-non-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Peace is the virtue of civilization. War is its crime. Yet it is often in the furnace of war that the sharpest tools of peace are forged." - Victor Hugo.
In 1971, an unsettling message started appearing on several computers that comprised ARPANET, the precursor to what we now know as the Internet. The message, which read "I'm the Creeper: catch me if you can." was the output of a program named]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0628/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0628/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T10:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0627/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0627/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T10:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DoJ Indicts North Korean Hacker for Ransomware Attacks on Hospitals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-doj-indicts-north-korean-hacker-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-doj-indicts-north-korean-hacker-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Thursday unsealed an indictment against a North Korean military intelligence operative for allegedly carrying out ransomware attacks against healthcare facilities in the country and funneling the payments to orchestrate additional intrusions into defense, technology, and government entities across the world.
"Rim Jong Hyok and his co-conspirators deployed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ongoing Cyberattack Targets Exposed Selenium Grid Services for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ongoing-cyberattack-targets-exposed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ongoing-cyberattack-targets-exposed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T06:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are sounding the alarm over an ongoing campaign that's leveraging internet-exposed Selenium Grid services for illicit cryptocurrency mining.
Cloud security Wiz is tracking the activity under the name SeleniumGreed. The campaign, which is targeting older versions of Selenium (3.141.59 and prior), is believed to be underway since at least April 2023.
"Unbeknownst to most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike Warns of New Phishing Scam Targeting German Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-warns-of-new-phishing-scam.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-warns-of-new-phishing-scam.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T05:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike is alerting about an unfamiliar threat actor attempting to capitalize on the Falcon Sensor update fiasco to distribute dubious installers targeting German customers as part of a highly targeted campaign.
The cybersecurity company said it identified what it described as an unattributed spear-phishing attempt on July 24, 2024, distributing an inauthentic CrowdStrike Crash Reporter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Telerik Report Server Poses Remote Code Execution Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-telerik-report-server.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-telerik-report-server.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T04:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software is urging users to update their Telerik Report Server instances following the discovery of a critical security flaw that could result in remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-6327 (CVSS score: 9.9), impacts Report Server version 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.514) and earlier.
"In Progress Telerik Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.709), a remote code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Shift from Cyber Espionage to Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korean-hackers-shift-from-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korean-hackers-shift-from-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A North Korea-linked threat actor known for its cyber espionage operations has gradually expanded into financially-motivated attacks that involve the deployment of ransomware, setting it apart from other nation-state hacking groups linked to the country.
Google-owned Mandiant is tracking the activity cluster under a new moniker APT45, which overlaps with names such as Andariel, Nickel Hyatt,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Types of Applications Security Testing You Must Know About]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/6-types-of-applications-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/6-types-of-applications-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While the specifics for security testing vary for applications, web applications, and APIs, a holistic and proactive applications security strategy is essential for all three types. There are six core types of testing that every security professional should know about to secure their applications, regardless of what phase they are in in development or deployment. 
In this article, we will]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Removes 63,000 Instagram Accounts Linked to Nigerian Sextortion Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-removes-63000-instagram-accounts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-removes-63000-instagram-accounts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Platforms on Wednesday said it took steps to remove around 63,000 Instagram accounts in Nigeria that were found to target people with financial sextortion scams.
"These included a smaller coordinated network of around 2,500 accounts that we were able to link to a group of around 20 individuals," the company said. "They targeted primarily adult men in the U.S. and used fake accounts to mask]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Securing the Modern Workspace: What Enterprises MUST Know about Enterprise Browser Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/webinar-securing-modern-workspace-what.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/webinar-securing-modern-workspace-what.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The browser is the nerve center of the modern workspace. Ironically, however, the browser is also one of the least protected threat surfaces of the modern enterprise. Traditional security tools provide little protection against browser-based threats, leaving organizations exposed. Modern cybersecurity requires a new approach based on the protection of the browser itself, which offers both]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (25 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0626/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0626/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (25 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0625/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0625/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:52:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Cloud Skipper (25 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0624/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0624/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:49:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Cloud Skipper. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Reveal ConfusedFunction Vulnerability in Google Cloud Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-expose-confusedfunction.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-expose-confusedfunction.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a privilege escalation vulnerability impacting Google Cloud Platform's Cloud Functions service that an attacker could exploit to access other services and sensitive data in an unauthorized manner.
Tenable has given the vulnerability the name ConfusedFunction.
"An attacker could escalate their privileges to the Default Cloud Build Service Account and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Docker Engine Flaw Allows Attackers to Bypass Authorization Plugins]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-docker-engine-flaw-allows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-docker-engine-flaw-allows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Docker is warning of a critical flaw impacting certain versions of Docker Engine that could allow an attacker to sidestep authorization plugins (AuthZ) under specific circumstances.
Tracked as CVE-2024-41110, the bypass and privilege escalation vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 10.0, indicating maximum severity.
"An attacker could exploit a bypass using an API request with Content-Length set]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Exploitable Vulnerabilities in Popular BIND 9 DNS Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-warns-of-exploitable.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-warns-of-exploitable.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Internet Systems Consortium (ISC) has released patches to address multiple security vulnerabilities in the Berkeley Internet Name Domain (BIND) 9 Domain Name System (DNS) software suite that could be exploited to trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.
"A cyber threat actor could exploit one of these vulnerabilities to cause a denial-of-service condition," the U.S. Cybersecurity and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Chrome Feature Scans Password-Protected Files for Malicious Content]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-chrome-feature-scans-password.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-chrome-feature-scans-password.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-25T05:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google said it's adding new security warnings when downloading potentially suspicious and malicious files via its Chrome web browser.
"We have replaced our previous warning messages with more detailed ones that convey more nuance about the nature of the danger and can help users make more informed decisions," Jasika Bawa, Lily Chen, and Daniel Rubery from the Chrome Security team said.
To that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram App Flaw Exploited to Spread Malware Hidden in Videos]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/telegram-app-flaw-exploited-to-spread.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/telegram-app-flaw-exploited-to-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A zero-day security flaw in Telegram's mobile app for Android called EvilVideo made it possible for attackers to malicious files disguised as harmless-looking videos.
The exploit appeared for sale for an unknown price in an underground forum on June 6, 2024, ESET said. Following responsible disclosure on June 26, the issue was addressed by Telegram in version 10.14.5 released on July 11.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a Trust Center Solves Your Security Questionnaire Problem]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-trust-center-solves-your-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-trust-center-solves-your-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security questionnaires aren’t just an inconvenience — they’re a recurring problem for security and sales teams.
They bleed time from organizations, filling the schedules of professionals with monotonous, automatable work. But what if there were a way to reduce or even altogether eliminate security questionnaires? The root problem isn’t a lack of great questionnaire products — it’s the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Reduce SaaS Spend and Risk Without Impacting Productivity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-reduce-saas-spend-and-risk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-reduce-saas-spend-and-risk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There is one simple driver behind the modern explosion in SaaS adoption: productivity. We have reached an era where purpose-built tools exist for almost every aspect of modern business and it’s incredibly easy (and tempting) for your workforce to adopt these tools without going through the formal IT approval and procurement process.
But this trend has also increased the attack surface—and with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patchwork Hackers Target Bhutan with Advanced Brute Ratel C4 Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/patchwork-hackers-target-bhutan-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/patchwork-hackers-target-bhutan-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Patchwork has been linked to a cyber attack targeting entities with ties to Bhutan to deliver the Brute Ratel C4 framework and an updated version of a backdoor called PGoShell.
The development marks the first time the adversary has been observed using the red teaming software, the Knownsec 404 Team said in an analysis published last week.
The activity cluster, also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités Microsoft GroupMe (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0623/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0623/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:53:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0622/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0622/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:52:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Nagios XI (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0621/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0621/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:52:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Nagios XI. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0620/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0620/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:52:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0619/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0619/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:52:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans ISC BIND (24 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0618/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0618/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:51:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans ISC BIND. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike Explains Friday Incident Crashing Millions of Windows Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-explains-friday-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-explains-friday-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T08:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike on Wednesday blamed an issue in its validation system for causing millions of Windows devices to crash as part of a widespread outage late last week.
"On Friday, July 19, 2024 at 04:09 UTC, as part of regular operations, CrowdStrike released a content configuration update for the Windows sensor to gather telemetry on possible novel threat techniques," the company]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Defender Flaw Exploited to Deliver ACR, Lumma, and Meduza Stealers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsoft-defender-flaw-exploited-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsoft-defender-flaw-exploited-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security flaw in the Microsoft Defender SmartScreen has been exploited as part of a new campaign designed to deliver information stealers such as ACR Stealer, Lumma, and Meduza.
Fortinet FortiGuard Labs said it detected the stealer campaign targeting Spain, Thailand, and the U.S. using booby-trapped files that exploit CVE-2024-21412 (CVSS score: 8.1).
The high-severity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds Twilio Authy and IE Flaws to Exploited Vulnerabilities List]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-adds-twilio-authy-and-ie-flaws-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-adds-twilio-authy-and-ie-flaws-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-24T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added two security flaws to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerabilities are listed below -

CVE-2012-4792 (CVSS score: 9.3) - Microsoft Internet Explorer Use-After-Free Vulnerability
CVE-2024-39891 (CVSS score: 5.3) - Twilio Authy Information Disclosure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Target Taiwan and US NGO with MgBot Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwan-and-us.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-taiwan-and-us.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations in Taiwan and a U.S. non-governmental organization (NGO) based in China have been targeted by a Beijing-affiliated state-sponsored hacking group called Daggerfly using an upgraded set of malware tools.
The campaign is a sign that the group "also engages in internal espionage," Symantec's Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a new report published today. "In the attack on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ICS Malware 'FrostyGoop' Targeting Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ics-malware-frostygoop-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ics-malware-frostygoop-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered what they say is the ninth Industrial Control Systems (ICS)-focused malware that has been used in a disruptive cyber attack targeting an energy company in the Ukrainian city of Lviv earlier this January.
Industrial cybersecurity firm Dragos has dubbed the malware FrostyGoop, describing it as the first malware strain to directly use Modbus TCP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Securely Onboard New Employees Without Sharing Temporary Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-securely-onboard-new-employees.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-securely-onboard-new-employees.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The initial onboarding stage is a crucial step for both employees and employers. However, this process often involves the practice of sharing temporary first-day passwords, which can expose organizations to security risks.
Traditionally, IT departments have been cornered into either sharing passwords in plain text via email or SMS, or arranging in-person meetings to verbally communicate these]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magento Sites Targeted with Sneaky Credit Card Skimmer via Swap Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/magento-sites-targeted-with-sneaky.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/magento-sites-targeted-with-sneaky.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed using swap files in compromised websites to conceal a persistent credit card skimmer and harvest payment information.
The sneaky technique, observed by Sucuri on a Magento e-commerce site's checkout page, allowed the malware to survive multiple cleanup attempts, the company said.
The skimmer is designed to capture all the data into the credit card form on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Given Deadline to Address E.U. Concerns Over 'Pay or Consent' Model]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-given-deadline-to-address-eu.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-given-deadline-to-address-eu.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has been given time till September 1, 2024, to respond to concerns raised by the European Commission over its "pay or consent" advertising model or risk-facing enforcement measures, including sanctions.
The European Commission said the Consumer Protection Cooperation (CPC) Network has notified the social media giant of the model adopted on Facebook and Instagram of potentially violating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian Institutions Targeted Using HATVIBE and CHERRYSPY Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ukrainian-institutions-targeted-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ukrainian-institutions-targeted-using.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T09:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has alerted of a spear-phishing campaign targeting a scientific research institution in the country with malware known as HATVIBE and CHERRYSPY.
The agency attributed the attack to a threat actor it tracks under the name UAC-0063, which was previously observed targeting various government entities to gather sensitive information using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (23 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0617/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0617/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T07:35:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Abandons Plan to Phase Out Third-Party Cookies in Chrome]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/google-abandons-plan-to-phase-out-third.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/google-abandons-plan-to-phase-out-third.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-23T04:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Monday abandoned plans to phase out third-party tracking cookies in its Chrome web browser more than four years after it introduced the option as part of a larger set of a controversial proposal called the Privacy Sandbox.
"Instead of deprecating third-party cookies, we would introduce a new experience in Chrome that lets people make an informed choice that applies across their web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover Chinese Cybercrime Network Behind Gambling and Human Trafficking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-uncover-chinese-cybercrime.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-uncover-chinese-cybercrime.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The relationship between various TDSs and DNS associated with Vigorish Viper and the final landing experience for the user
A Chinese organized crime syndicate with links to money laundering and human trafficking across Southeast Asia has been using an advanced "technology suite" that runs the whole cybercrime supply chain spectrum to spearhead its operations.
Infoblox is tracking the proprietor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PINEAPPLE and FLUXROOT Hacker Groups Abuse Google Cloud for Credential Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/pineapple-and-fluxroot-hacker-groups.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/pineapple-and-fluxroot-hacker-groups.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T12:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Latin America (LATAM)-based financially motivated actor codenamed FLUXROOT has been observed leveraging Google Cloud serverless projects to orchestrate credential phishing activity, highlighting the abuse of the cloud computing model for malicious purposes.
"Serverless architectures are attractive to developers and enterprises for their flexibility, cost effectiveness, and ease of use," Google]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Set up an Automated SMS Analysis Service with AI in Tines]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-set-up-automated-sms-analysis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-set-up-automated-sms-analysis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The opportunities to use AI in workflow automation are many and varied, but one of the simplest ways to use AI to save time and enhance your organization’s security posture is by building an automated SMS analysis service. 
Workflow automation platform Tines provides a good example of how to do it. The vendor recently released their first native AI features, and security teams have already]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MSPs & MSSPs: How to Increase Engagement with Your Cybersecurity Clients Through vCISO Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/msps-mssps-how-to-increase-engagement.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/msps-mssps-how-to-increase-engagement.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As a vCISO, you are responsible for your client's cybersecurity strategy and risk governance. This incorporates multiple disciplines, from research to execution to reporting. Recently, we published a comprehensive playbook for vCISOs, “Your First 100 Days as a vCISO – 5 Steps to Success”, which covers all the phases entailed in launching a successful vCISO engagement, along with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Atlassian (22 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0616/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0616/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:24:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Atlassian. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits NetApp (22 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0615/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0615/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T07:23:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits NetApp. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SocGholish Malware Exploits BOINC Project for Covert Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/socgholish-malware-exploits-boinc.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/socgholish-malware-exploits-boinc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The JavaScript downloader malware known as SocGholish (aka FakeUpdates) is being used to deliver a remote access trojan called AsyncRAT as well as a legitimate open-source project called BOINC.
BOINC, short for Berkeley Open Infrastructure Network Computing Client, is an open-source "volunteer computing" platform maintained by the University of California with an aim to carry out "large-scale]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Variant of Play Ransomware Targeting VMWare ESXi Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-linux-variant-of-play-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-linux-variant-of-play-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-22T03:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new Linux variant of a ransomware strain known as Play (aka Balloonfly and PlayCrypt) that's designed to target VMWare ESXi environments.
"This development suggests that the group could be broadening its attacks across the Linux platform, leading to an expanded victim pool and more successful ransom negotiations," Trend Micro researchers said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploit CrowdStrike Update Mishap to Distribute Remcos RAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-exploit-crowdstrike.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-exploit-crowdstrike.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-20T16:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity firm CrowdStrike, which is facing the heat for causing worldwide IT disruptions by pushing out a flawed update to Windows devices, is now warning that threat actors are exploiting the situation to distribute Remcos RAT to its customers in Latin America under the guise of a providing a hotfix.
The attack chains involve distributing a ZIP archive file named "crowdstrike-hotfix.zip,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17-Year-Old Linked to Scattered Spider Cybercrime Syndicate Arrested in U.K.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/17-year-old-linked-to-scattered-spider.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/17-year-old-linked-to-scattered-spider.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-20T04:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement officials in the U.K. have arrested a 17-year-old boy from Walsall who is suspected to be a member of the notorious Scattered Spider cybercrime syndicate.
The arrest was made "in connection with a global cyber online crime group which has been targeting large organizations with ransomware and gaining access to computer networks," West Midlands police said. "The arrest is part of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Faulty CrowdStrike Update Crashes Windows Systems, Impacting Businesses Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/faulty-crowdstrike-update-crashes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/faulty-crowdstrike-update-crashes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Businesses across the world have been hit by widespread disruptions to their Windows workstations stemming from a faulty update pushed out by cybersecurity company CrowdStrike.
"CrowdStrike is actively working with customers impacted by a defect found in a single content update for Windows hosts," the company's CEO George Kurtz said in a statement. "Mac and Linux hosts are not impacted. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Russian Nationals Plead Guilty in LockBit Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/two-russian-nationals-plead-guilty-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/two-russian-nationals-plead-guilty-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Russian nationals have pleaded guilty in a U.S. court for their participation as affiliates in the LockBit ransomware scheme and helping facilitate ransomware attacks across the world.
The defendants include Ruslan Magomedovich Astamirov, 21, of Chechen Republic, and Mikhail Vasiliev, 34, a dual Canadian and Russian national of Bradford, Ontario.
Astamirov was arrested in Arizona by U.S. law]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-033 (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-033/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-033/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T12:07:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans IBM MaaS360 (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0614/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0614/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:55:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits IBM. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0613/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0613/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:50:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0612/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0612/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0611/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0611/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0610/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0610/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Safeguard Personal and Corporate Identities with Identity Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/safeguard-personal-and-corporate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/safeguard-personal-and-corporate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
In the current cyber threat landscape, the protection of personal and corporate identities has become vital.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Panne informatique affectant les systèmes Microsoft Windows disposant de l'EDR Crowdstrike Falcon (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-032/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-032/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T09:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 19 juillet 2024, le CERT-FR a été informé d’incidents affectant des systèmes sur lesquels l’agent de l’EDR Crowdstrike Falcon est installé et utilisant le système d’exploitation Microsoft Windows. Le présent bulletin d’actualité reprend les différents éléments dont le CERT-FR a connaissance....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Houthi Group Targets Yemen Aid Organizations with Android Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/pro-houthi-group-targets-yemen-aid.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/pro-houthi-group-targets-yemen-aid.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected pro-Houthi threat group targeted at least three humanitarian organizations in Yemen with Android spyware designed to harvest sensitive information.
These attacks, attributed to an activity cluster codenamed OilAlpha, entail a new set of malicious mobile apps that come with their own supporting infrastructure, Recorded Future's Insikt Group said.
Targets of the ongoing campaign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Summary of "AI Leaders Spill Their Secrets" Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/summary-of-ai-leaders-spill-their.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/summary-of-ai-leaders-spill-their.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Event Overview
The "AI Leaders Spill Their Secrets" webinar, hosted by Sigma Computing, featured prominent AI experts sharing their experiences and strategies for success in the AI industry. The panel included Michael Ward from Sardine, Damon Bryan from Hyperfinity, and Stephen Hillian from Astronomer, moderated by Zalak Trivedi, Sigma Computing's Product Manager.
Key Speakers and Their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT41 Infiltrates Networks in Italy, Spain, Taiwan, Turkey, and the U.K.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/apt41-infiltrates-networks-in-italy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/apt41-infiltrates-networks-in-italy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several organizations operating within global shipping and logistics, media and entertainment, technology, and automotive sectors in Italy, Spain, Taiwan, Thailand, Turkey, and the U.K. have become the target of a "sustained campaign" by the prolific China-based APT41 hacking group.
"APT41 successfully infiltrated and maintained prolonged, unauthorized access to numerous victims' networks since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0609/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0609/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SolarWinds. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Patches 11 Critical Flaws in Access Rights Manager Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/solarwinds-patches-11-critical-flaws-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/solarwinds-patches-11-critical-flaws-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has addressed a set of critical security flaws impacting its Access Rights Manager (ARM) software that could be exploited to access sensitive information or execute arbitrary code.
Of the 11 vulnerabilities, seven are rated Critical in severity and carry a CVSS score of 9.6 out of 10.0. The remaining four weaknesses have been rated High in severity, with each of them having a CVSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans VMware Tanzu (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0608/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0608/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T07:07:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Tanzu. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (19 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0607/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0607/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T06:49:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WazirX Cryptocurrency Exchange Loses $230 Million in Major Security Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/wazirx-cryptocurrency-exchange-loses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/wazirx-cryptocurrency-exchange-loses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-19T04:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian cryptocurrency exchange WazirX has confirmed that it was the target of a security breach that led to the theft of $230 million in cryptocurrency assets.
"A cyber attack occurred in one of our [multi-signature] wallets involving a loss of funds exceeding $230 million," the company said in a statement. "This wallet was operated utilizing the services of Liminal's digital asset custody and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: HotPage Adware Disguised as Ad Blocker Installs Malicious Kernel Driver]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/alert-hotpage-adware-disguised-as-ad.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/alert-hotpage-adware-disguised-as-ad.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on an adware module that purports to block ads and malicious websites, while stealthily offloading a kernel driver component that grants attackers the ability to run arbitrary code with elevated permissions on Windows hosts.
The malware, dubbed HotPage, gets its name from the eponymous installer ("HotPage.exe"), according to new findings from ESET.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AppSec Webinar: How to Turn Developers into Security Champions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/appsec-webinar-how-to-turn-developers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/appsec-webinar-how-to-turn-developers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's face it: AppSec and developers often feel like they're on opposing teams. You're battling endless vulnerabilities while they just want to ship code. Sound familiar?
It's a common challenge, but there is a solution.
Ever wish they proactively cared about security? The answer lies in a proven, but often overlooked, strategy: Security Champion Programs — a way to turn developers from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Threats Pose Increasing Risk to the Travel Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/automated-threats-pose-increasing-risk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/automated-threats-pose-increasing-risk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the travel industry rebounds post-pandemic, it is increasingly targeted by automated threats, with the sector experiencing nearly 21% of all bot attack requests last year. That’s according to research from Imperva, a Thales company. In their 2024 Bad Bot Report, Imperva finds that bad bots accounted for 44.5% of the industry’s web traffic in 2023—a significant jump from 37.4% in 2022.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SAP AI Core Vulnerabilities Expose Customer Data to Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/sap-ai-core-vulnerabilities-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/sap-ai-core-vulnerabilities-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered security shortcomings in SAP AI Core cloud-based platform for creating and deploying predictive artificial intelligence (AI) workflows that could be exploited to get hold of access tokens and customer data.
The five vulnerabilities have been collectively dubbed SAPwned by cloud security firm Wiz.
"The vulnerabilities we found could have allowed attackers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TAG-100: New Threat Actor Uses Open-Source Tools for Widespread Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/tag-100-new-threat-actor-uses-open.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/tag-100-new-threat-actor-uses-open.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unknown threat actors have been observed leveraging open-source tools as part of a suspected cyber espionage campaign targeting global government and private sector organizations.
Recorded Future's Insikt Group is tracking the activity under the temporary moniker TAG-100, noting that the adversary likely compromised organizations in at least ten countries across Africa, Asia, North America,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0606/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0606/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Sonicwall (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0605/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0605/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:32:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Sonicwall. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0604/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0604/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:30:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Apache HTTP Server (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0603/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0603/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:27:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Apache HTTP Server. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0602/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0602/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T07:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (18 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0601/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0601/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Halts AI Use in Brazil Following Data Protection Authority's Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-halts-ai-use-in-brazil-following.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-halts-ai-use-in-brazil-following.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has suspended the use of generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) in Brazil after the country's data protection authority issued a preliminary ban objecting to its new privacy policy.
The development was first reported by news agency Reuters.
The company said it has decided to suspend the tools while it is in talks with Brazil's National Data Protection Authority (ANPD) to address the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Warns of Critical Flaw Affecting On-Prem Smart Software Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-flaw-affecting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisco-warns-of-critical-flaw-affecting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-18T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released patches to address a maximum-severity security flaw impacting Smart Software Manager On-Prem (Cisco SSM On-Prem) that could enable a remote, unauthenticated attacker to change the password of any users, including those belonging to administrative users.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-20419, carries a CVSS score of 10.0.
"This vulnerability is due to improper]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Update BeaverTail Malware to Target MacOS Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korean-hackers-update-beavertail.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korean-hackers-update-beavertail.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T16:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an updated variant of a known stealer malware that attackers affiliated with the Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK) have delivered as part of prior cyber espionage campaigns targeting job seekers.
The artifact in question is an Apple macOS disk image (DMG) file named "MiroTalk.dmg" that mimics the legitimate video call service of the same name,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Sonicwall NetExtender (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0600/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0600/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:10:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Sonicwall NetExtender. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating Insider Risks: Are your Employees Enabling External Threats?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/navigating-insider-risks-are-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/navigating-insider-risks-are-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T11:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attacks on your network are often meticulously planned operations launched by sophisticated threats. Sometimes your technical fortifications provide a formidable challenge, and the attack requires assistance from the inside to succeed. For example, in 2022, the FBI issued a warning1 that SIM swap attacks are growing: gain control of the phone and earn a gateway to email, bank accounts, stocks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIN7 Group Advertises Security-Bypassing Tool on Dark Web Forums]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/fin7-group-advertises-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/fin7-group-advertises-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financially motivated threat actor known as FIN7 has been observed using multiple pseudonyms across several underground forums to likely advertise a tool known to be used by ransomware groups like Black Basta.
"AvNeutralizer (aka AuKill), a highly specialized tool developed by FIN7 to tamper with security solutions, has been marketed in the criminal underground and used by multiple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Weblogic (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0599/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0599/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T10:04:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle WebLogic. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Virtualization (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0598/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0598/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:56:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Virtualization. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Systems (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0597/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0597/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:51:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Systems. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle PeopleSoft (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0596/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0596/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:46:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle PeopleSoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle MySQL (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0595/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0595/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle MYSQL. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Java SE (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0594/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0594/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T09:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Java SE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Database Server (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0593/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0593/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:57:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Database Server. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-linked APT17 Targets Italian Companies with 9002 RAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/china-linked-apt17-targets-italian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/china-linked-apt17-targets-italian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A China-linked threat actor called APT17 has been observed targeting Italian companies and government entities using a variant of a known malware referred to as 9002 RAT.
The two targeted attacks took place on June 24 and July 2, 2024, Italian cybersecurity company TG Soft said in an analysis published last week.
"The first campaign on June 24, 2024 used an Office document, while the second]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0592/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0592/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:42:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0591/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0591/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:34:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0590/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0590/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:27:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Xen (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0589/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0589/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T08:13:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mozilla Thunderbird (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0588/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0588/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mozilla Thunderbird. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (17 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0587/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0587/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T07:47:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scattered Spider Adopts RansomHub and Qilin Ransomware for Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/scattered-spider-adopts-ransomhub-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/scattered-spider-adopts-ransomhub-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous cybercrime group known as Scattered Spider has incorporated ransomware strains such as RansomHub and Qilin into its arsenal, Microsoft has revealed.
Scattered Spider is the designation given to a threat actor that's known for its sophisticated social engineering schemes to breach targets and establish persistence for follow-on exploitation and data theft. It also has a history of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Apache HugeGraph Vulnerability Under Attack - Patch ASAP]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-apache-hugegraph-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-apache-hugegraph-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-17T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively exploiting a recently disclosed critical security flaw impacting Apache HugeGraph-Server that could lead to remote code execution attacks.
Tracked as CVE-2024-27348 (CVSS score: 9.8), the vulnerability impacts all versions of the software before 1.3.0. It has been described as a remote command execution flaw in the Gremlin graph traversal language API.
"Users are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Konfety' Ad Fraud Uses 250+ Google Play Decoy Apps to Hide Malicious Twins]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/konfety-ad-fraud-uses-250-google-play.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/konfety-ad-fraud-uses-250-google-play.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a "massive ad fraud operation" that leverages hundreds of apps on the Google Play Store to perform a host of nefarious activities.
The campaign has been codenamed Konfety – the Russian word for Candy – owing to its abuse of a mobile advertising software development kit (SDK) associated with a Russia-based ad network called CaramelAds.
"Konfety represents a new form of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Threat Prevention & Detection in SaaS Environments - 101]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/threat-prevention-detection-in-saas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/threat-prevention-detection-in-saas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity-based threats on SaaS applications are a growing concern among security professionals, although few have the capabilities to detect and respond to them. 
According to the US Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), 90% of all cyberattacks begin with phishing, an identity-based threat. Throw in attacks that use stolen credentials, over-provisioned accounts, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Found Using Image Files to Hide Backdoor Code]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-npm-packages-found-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-npm-packages-found-using.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T10:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified two malicious packages on the npm package registry that concealed backdoor code to execute malicious commands sent from a remote server.
The packages in question – img-aws-s3-object-multipart-copy and legacyaws-s3-object-multipart-copy – have been downloaded 190 and 48 times each. As of writing, they have been taken down by the npm security team.
"They]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Stormshield (16 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0586/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0586/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T09:22:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Stormshield. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Deploy New BugSleep Backdoor in Middle East Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/iranian-hackers-deploy-new-bugsleep.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/iranian-hackers-deploy-new-bugsleep.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian nation-state actor known as MuddyWater has been observed using a never-before-seen backdoor as part of a recent attack campaign, shifting away from its well-known tactic of deploying legitimate remote monitoring and management (RMM) software for maintaining persistent access.
That's according to independent findings from cybersecurity firms Check Point and Sekoia, which have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Void Banshee APT Exploits Microsoft MHTML Flaw to Spread Atlantida Stealer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/void-banshee-apt-exploits-microsoft.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/void-banshee-apt-exploits-microsoft.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An advanced persistent threat (APT) group called Void Banshee has been observed exploiting a recently disclosed security flaw in the Microsoft MHTML browser engine as a zero-day to deliver an information stealer called Atlantida.
Cybersecurity firm Trend Micro, which observed the activity in mid-May 2024, the vulnerability – tracked as CVE-2024-38112 – was used as part of a multi-stage attack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (16 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0585/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0585/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T06:44:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky Exits U.S. Market Following Commerce Department Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/kaspersky-exits-us-market-following.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/kaspersky-exits-us-market-following.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T04:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian security vendor Kaspersky has said it's exiting the U.S. market nearly a month after the Commerce Department announced a ban on the sale of its software in the country citing a national security risk.
News of the closure was first reported by journalist Kim Zetter.
The company is expected to wind down its U.S. operations on July 20, 2024, the same day the ban comes into effect. It's also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Actively Exploited RCE Flaw in GeoServer GeoTools Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-rce.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-rce.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-16T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday added a critical security flaw impacting OSGeo GeoServer GeoTools to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
GeoServer is an open-source software server written in Java that allows users to share and edit geospatial data. It is the reference implementation of the Open]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Token Leak Exposes Python's Core Repositories to Potential Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/github-token-leak-exposes-pythons-core.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/github-token-leak-exposes-pythons-core.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers said they discovered an accidentally leaked GitHub token that could have granted elevated access to the GitHub repositories of the Python language, Python Package Index (PyPI), and the Python Software Foundation (PSF) repositories.
JFrog, which found the GitHub Personal Access Token, said the secret was leaked in a public Docker container hosted on Docker Hub.
"This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (15 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0584/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0584/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T12:18:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-031 (15 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-031/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-031/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T11:58:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Kaspersky (15 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0583/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0583/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T11:50:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Kaspersky. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10,000 Victims a Day: Infostealer Garden of Low-Hanging Fruit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/10000-victims-day-infostealer-garden-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/10000-victims-day-infostealer-garden-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T10:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine you could gain access to any Fortune 100 company for $10 or less, or even for free. Terrifying thought, isn’t it? Or exciting, depending on which side of the cybersecurity barricade you are on. Well, that’s basically the state of things today. Welcome to the infostealer garden of low-hanging fruit.
Over the last few years, the problem has grown bigger and bigger, and only now are we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CRYSTALRAY Hackers Infect Over 1,500 Victims Using Network Mapping Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crystalray-hackers-infect-over-1500.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crystalray-hackers-infect-over-1500.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor that was previously observed using an open-source network mapping tool has greatly expanded their operations to infect over 1,500 victims.
Sysdig, which is tracking the cluster under the name CRYSTALRAY, said the activities have witnessed a 10x surge, adding it includes "mass scanning, exploiting multiple vulnerabilities, and placing backdoors using multiple [open-source software]]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Axis (15 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0582/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0582/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T08:11:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Axis. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits ESET (15 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0581/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0581/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits ESET. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Banks to Phase Out OTPs for Online Logins Within 3 Months]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/singapore-banks-to-phase-out-otps-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/singapore-banks-to-phase-out-otps-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T07:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Retail banking institutions in Singapore have three months to phase out the use of one-time passwords (OTPs) for authentication purposes when signing into online accounts to mitigate the risk of phishing attacks.
The decision was announced by the Monetary Authority of Singapore (MAS) and The Association of Banks in Singapore (ABS) on July 9, 2024.
"Customers who have activated their digital]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HardBit Ransomware 4.0 Uses Passphrase Protection to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-hardbit-ransomware-40-uses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-hardbit-ransomware-40-uses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-15T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a new version of a ransomware strain called HardBit that comes packaged with new obfuscation techniques to deter analysis efforts.
"Unlike previous versions, HardBit Ransomware group enhanced the version 4.0 with passphrase protection," Cybereason researchers Kotaro Ogino and Koshi Oyama said in an analysis.
"The passphrase needs to be provided during]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AT&T Confirms Data Breach Affecting Nearly All Wireless Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/at-confirms-data-breach-affecting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/at-confirms-data-breach-affecting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-13T05:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[American telecom service provider AT&T has confirmed that threat actors managed to access data belonging to "nearly all" of its wireless customers as well as customers of mobile virtual network operators (MVNOs) using AT&T's wireless network.
"Threat actors unlawfully accessed an AT&T workspace on a third-party cloud platform and, between April 14 and April 25, 2024, exfiltrated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkGate Malware Exploits Samba File Shares in Short-Lived Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/darkgate-malware-exploits-samba-file.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/darkgate-malware-exploits-samba-file.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a short-lived DarkGate malware campaign that leveraged Samba file shares to initiate the infections.
Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 said the activity spanned the months of March and April 2024, with the infection chains using servers running public-facing Samba file shares hosting Visual Basic Script (VBS) and JavaScript files. Targets included North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0580/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0580/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0580</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0580"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T13:27:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0579/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0579/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0579</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0579"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:45:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0578/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0578/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0578</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0578"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:26:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Australian Defence Force Private and Husband Charged with Espionage for Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/australian-defence-force-private-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/australian-defence-force-private-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T12:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two Russian-born Australian citizens have been arrested and charged in the country for spying on behalf of Russia as part of a "complex" law enforcement operation codenamed BURGAZADA.
This includes a 40-year-old woman, an Australian Defence Force (ADF) Army Private, and her husband, a 62-year-old self-employed laborer. Media reports have identified them as Kira Korolev and Igor Korolev,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0577/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0577/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T11:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0577</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0577"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T11:45:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Exim Mail Server Vulnerability Exposes Millions to Malicious Attachments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-exim-mail-server-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-exim-mail-server-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security issue has been disclosed in the Exim mail transfer agent that could enable threat actors to deliver malicious attachments to target users' inboxes.

The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-39929, has a CVSS score of 9.1 out of 10.0. It has been addressed in version 4.98.

"Exim through 4.97.1 misparses a multiline RFC 2231 header filename, and thus remote attackers can bypass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ever Wonder How Hackers Really Steal Passwords? Discover Their Tactics in This Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ever-wonder-how-hackers-really-steal.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ever-wonder-how-hackers-really-steal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital age, passwords serve as the keys to our most sensitive information, from social media accounts to banking and business systems. This immense power brings with it significant responsibility—and vulnerability.
Most people don't realize their credentials have been compromised until the damage is done.
Imagine waking up to drained bank accounts, stolen identities, or a company's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Exim (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0576/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0576/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T09:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Exim. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Exim (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0576</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0576"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T09:50:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Exim. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Seizes Domains Used by AI-Powered Russian Bot Farm for Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-seizes-domains-used-by-ai-powered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-seizes-domains-used-by-ai-powered.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T08:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) said it seized two internet domains and searched nearly 1,000 social media accounts that Russian threat actors allegedly used to covertly spread pro-Kremlin disinformation in the country and abroad on a large scale.
"The social media bot farm used elements of AI to create fictitious social media profiles — often purporting to belong to individuals in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Juniper Networks (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0575/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0575/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T08:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Juniper Networks (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0575</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0575"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T08:11:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Citrix uberAgent (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0574/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0574/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T07:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Citrix uberAgent. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Citrix uberAgent (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0574</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0574"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T07:32:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Citrix uberAgent. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0573/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0573/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T07:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (12 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0573</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0573"/>
        <updated>2024-07-12T07:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks Patches Critical Flaw in Expedition Migration Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/palo-alto-networks-patches-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/palo-alto-networks-patches-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T15:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks has released security updates to address five security flaws impacting its products, including a critical bug that could lead to an authentication bypass.
Cataloged as CVE-2024-5910 (CVSS score: 9.3), the vulnerability has been described as a case of missing authentication in its Expedition migration tool that could lead to an admin account takeover.
"Missing authentication]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[60 New Malicious Packages Uncovered in NuGet Supply Chain Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/60-new-malicious-packages-uncovered-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/60-new-malicious-packages-uncovered-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed publishing a new wave of malicious packages to the NuGet package manager as part of an ongoing campaign that began in August 2023, while also adding a new layer of stealth to evade detection.
The fresh packages, about 60 in number and spanning 290 versions, demonstrate a refined approach from the previous set that came to light in October 2023, software supply]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0572/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0572/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0572</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0572"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T14:26:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codes malveillants utilisés à des fins destructrices (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-002/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-002/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les marqueurs techniques suivants sont associés à des codes destructeurs connus à ce jour (voir la publication /cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007/ ) Ils peuvent être utilisés à des fins de recherche de compromission dans des journaux historiques ou de détection :]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codes malveillants utilisés à des fins destructrices (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-002</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-002"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T13:25:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les marqueurs techniques suivants sont associés à des codes destructeurs connus à ce jour (voir la publication ["Codes malveillants utilisés à des fins destructrices"](/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007/ ) ) Ils peuvent être utilisés à des fins de recherche de compromission dans des journaux historiques ou...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codes malveillants utilisés à des fins destructrices (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T12:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les attaques à but de déstabilisation constituent des menaces informatiques qui visent de manière récurrente les grands évènements sportifs. Si elles prennent souvent la forme d’attaques par déni de service distribué (DDoS) ou de défigurations de sites Web, elles peuvent aussi passer par des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Codes malveillants utilisés à des fins destructrices (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-007"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T12:49:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Les attaques à but de déstabilisation constituent des menaces informatiques qui visent de manière récurrente les grands évènements sportifs. Si elles prennent souvent la forme d’attaques par déni de service distribué (DDoS) ou de défigurations de sites Web, elles peuvent aussi passer par des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese APT41 Upgrades Malware Arsenal with DodgeBox and MoonWalk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-apt41-upgrades-malware-arsenal.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-apt41-upgrades-malware-arsenal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T12:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) group codenamed APT41 is suspected to be using an "advanced and upgraded version" of a known malware called StealthVector to deliver a previously undocumented backdoor dubbed MoonWalk.
The new variant of StealthVector – which is also referred to as DUSTPAN – has been codenamed DodgeBox by Zscaler ThreatLabz, which discovered the loader strain in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlined Security Solutions: PAM for Small to Medium-sized Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/streamlined-security-solutions-pam-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/streamlined-security-solutions-pam-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Today, all organizations are exposed to the threat of cyber breaches, irrespective of their scale. Historically, larger companies were frequent targets due to their substantial resources, sensitive data, and regulatory responsibilities, whereas smaller entities often underestimated their attractiveness to hackers. However, this assumption is precarious, as cybercriminals frequently exploit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Poco RAT Targets Spanish-Speaking Victims in Phishing Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-poco-rat-targets-spanish-speaking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-poco-rat-targets-spanish-speaking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Spanish language victims are the target of an email phishing campaign that delivers a new remote access trojan (RAT) called Poco RAT since at least February 2024.
The attacks primarily single out mining, manufacturing, hospitality, and utilities sectors, according to cybersecurity company Cofense.
"The majority of the custom code in the malware appears to be focused on anti-analysis,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits VMware (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0571/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0571/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T09:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits VMware. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits VMware (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0571</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0571"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T09:09:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits VMware. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compromission de la bibliothèque polyfill[.]io (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-030/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-030/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Résumé Le 25 juin 2024, l’éditeur Sansec indique que des redirections malveillantes sont déployées par la bibliothèque polyfill.js. Cette dernière est employée par plusieurs centaines de milliers de sites à travers le monde et permet à des sites web de supporter des navigateurs obsolètes comme...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Compromission de la bibliothèque polyfill[.]io (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-030</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-030"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:55:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Résumé Le 25 juin 2024, l’éditeur Sansec indique que des redirections malveillantes sont déployées par la bibliothèque polyfill.js. Cette dernière est employée par plusieurs centaines de milliers de sites à travers le monde et permet à des sites web de supporter des navigateurs obsolètes comme...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Moxa (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0570/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0570/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:49:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Moxa. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Moxa (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0570</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0570"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:49:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Moxa. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0569/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0569/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0569</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0569"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:37:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Wireshark (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0568/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0568/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Wireshark. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Wireshark (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0568</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0568"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Wireshark. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0567/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0567/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0567</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0567"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T08:03:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GLPI (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0566/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0566/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GLPI. lles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GLPI (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0566</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0566"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:49:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GLPI. lles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Mitel (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0565/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0565/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Mitel. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Mitel (11 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0565</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0565"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T07:33:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Mitel. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PHP Vulnerability Exploited to Spread Malware and Launch DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/php-vulnerability-exploited-to-spread.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/php-vulnerability-exploited-to-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T05:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple threat actors have been observed exploiting a recently disclosed security flaw in PHP to deliver remote access trojans, cryptocurrency miners, and distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) botnets.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-4577 (CVSS score: 9.8), which allows an attacker to remotely execute malicious commands on Windows systems using Chinese and Japanese language locales. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab Patches Critical Flaw Allowing Unauthorized Pipeline Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gitlab-patches-critical-flaw-allowing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gitlab-patches-critical-flaw-allowing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-11T03:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab has shipped another round of updates to close out security flaws in its software development platform, including a critical bug that allows an attacker to run pipeline jobs as an arbitrary user.
Tracked as CVE-2024-6385, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.6 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting versions 15.8 prior to 16.11.6, 17.0 prior to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ransomware Group Exploiting Veeam Backup Software Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ransomware-group-exploiting-veeam.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ransomware-group-exploiting-veeam.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security flaw in Veeam Backup & Replication software is being exploited by a nascent ransomware operation known as EstateRansomware.
Singapore-headquartered Group-IB, which discovered the threat actor in early April 2024, said the modus operandi involved the exploitation of CVE-2023-27532 (CVSS score: 7.5) to carry out the malicious activities.
Initial access to the target]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Smash-and-Grab Extortion]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/smash-and-grab-extortion.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/smash-and-grab-extortion.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Problem
The “2024 Attack Intelligence Report” from the staff at Rapid7 [1] is a well-researched, well-written report that is worthy of careful study. Some key takeaways are: 

53% of the over 30 new vulnerabilities that were widely exploited in 2023 and at the start of 2024 were zero-days.
More mass compromise events arose from zero-day vulnerabilities than from n-day vulnerabilities.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's July Update Patches 143 Flaws, Including Two Actively Exploited]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsofts-july-update-patches-143.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsofts-july-update-patches-143.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released patches to address a total of 143 security flaws as part of its monthly security updates, two of which have come under active exploitation in the wild.
Five out of the 143 flaws are rated Critical, 136 are rated Important, and four are rated Moderate in severity. The fixes are in addition to 33 vulnerabilities that have been addressed in the Chromium-based Edge browser]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[True Protection or False Promise? The Ultimate ITDR Shortlisting Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/true-protection-or-false-promise.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/true-protection-or-false-promise.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s the age of identity security. The explosion of driven ransomware attacks has made CISOs and security teams realize that identity protection lags 20 years behind their endpoints and networks. This realization is mainly due to the transformation of lateral movement from fine art, found in APT and top cybercrime groups only, to a commodity skill used in almost every ransomware attack. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Adds Passkeys to Advanced Protection Program for High-Risk Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/google-adds-passkeys-to-advanced.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/google-adds-passkeys-to-advanced.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T10:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Wednesday announced that it's making available passkeys for high-risk users to enroll in its Advanced Protection Program (APP).
"Users traditionally needed a physical security key for APP — now they can choose a passkey to secure their account," Shuvo Chatterjee, product lead of APP, said.
Passkeys are considered a more secure and phishing-resistant alternative to passwords. Based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0564/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0564/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0564</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0564"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0563/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0563/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0563</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0563"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T09:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Joomla! (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0562/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0562/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Joomla!. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Joomla! (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0562</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0562"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:53:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Joomla!. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0561/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0561/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0561</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0561"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:45:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0560/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0560/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0560</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0560"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0559/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0559/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0559</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0559"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0558/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0558/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0558</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0558"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0557/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0557/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que les...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0557</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0557"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que les...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0556/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0556/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0556</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0556"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:40:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0555/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0555/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (10 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0555</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0555"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Analysts Expose HuiOne Guarantee's $11 Billion Cybercrime Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crypto-analysts-expose-huione.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crypto-analysts-expose-huione.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency analysts have shed light on an online marketplace called HuiOne Guarantee that's widely used by cybercriminals in Southeast Asia, particularly those linked to pig butchering scams.
"Merchants on the platform offer technology, data, and money laundering services, and have engaged in transactions totaling at least $11 billion," Elliptic said in a report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ViperSoftX Malware Disguises as eBooks on Torrents to Spread Stealthy Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vipersoftx-malware-disguises-as-ebooks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vipersoftx-malware-disguises-as-ebooks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T05:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The sophisticated malware known as ViperSoftX has been observed being distributed as eBooks over torrents.
"A notable aspect of the current variant of ViperSoftX is that it uses the Common Language Runtime (CLR) to dynamically load and run PowerShell commands, thereby creating a PowerShell environment within AutoIt for operations," Trellix security researchers Mathanraj Thangaraju and Sijo Jacob]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New OpenSSH Vulnerability Discovered: Potential Remote Code Execution Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-openssh-vulnerability-discovered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-openssh-vulnerability-discovered.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-10T03:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Select versions of the OpenSSH secure networking suite are susceptible to a new vulnerability that can trigger remote code execution (RCE).
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-6409 (CVSS score: 7.0), is distinct from CVE-2024-6387 (aka RegreSSHion) and relates to a case of code execution in the privsep child process due to a race condition in signal handling. It only impacts versions 8.7p1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0554/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0554/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0554</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0554"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:38:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0552/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0552/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0552</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0552"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T13:13:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité OpenSSH dans des systèmes d'exploitation (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0551/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0551/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSH. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité OpenSSH dans des systèmes d'exploitation (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0551</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0551"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:58:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSH. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans le protocole RADIUS (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0550/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0550/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans le protocole RADIUS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans le protocole RADIUS (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0550</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0550"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans le protocole RADIUS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RADIUS Protocol Vulnerability Exposes Networks to MitM Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/radius-protocol-vulnerability-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/radius-protocol-vulnerability-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a security vulnerability in the RADIUS network authentication protocol called BlastRADIUS that could be exploited by an attacker to stage Mallory-in-the-middle (MitM) attacks and bypass integrity checks under certain circumstances.
"The RADIUS protocol allows certain Access-Request messages to have no integrity or authentication checks," InkBridge]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Schneider Electric (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0549/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0549/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Schneider Electric. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Schneider Electric (09 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0549</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0549"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T12:27:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Schneider Electric. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting Jenkins Script Console for Cryptocurrency Mining Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/hackers-exploiting-jenkins-script.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/hackers-exploiting-jenkins-script.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have found that it's possible for attackers to weaponize improperly configured Jenkins Script Console instances to further criminal activities such as cryptocurrency mining.
"Misconfigurations such as improperly set up authentication mechanisms expose the '/script' endpoint to attackers," Trend Micro's Shubham Singh and Sunil Bharti said in a technical write-up]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HUMINT: Diving Deep into the Dark Web]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/humint-diving-deep-into-dark-web.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/humint-diving-deep-into-dark-web.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Clear Web vs. Deep Web vs. Dark Web
Threat intelligence professionals divide the internet into three main components:

Clear Web - Web assets that can be viewed through public search engines, including media, blogs, and other pages and sites.
Deep Web - Websites and forums that are unindexed by search engines. For example, webmail, online banking, corporate intranets, walled gardens, etc. Some]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GuardZoo Malware Targets Over 450 Middle Eastern Military Personnel]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/guardzoo-malware-targets-over-450.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/guardzoo-malware-targets-over-450.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Military personnel from Middle East countries are the target of an ongoing surveillanceware operation that delivers an Android data-gathering tool called GuardZoo.
The campaign, believed to have commenced as early as October 2019, has been attributed to a Houthi-aligned threat actor based on the application lures, command-and-control (C2) server logs, targeting footprint, and the attack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Agencies Warn of China-linked APT40's Rapid Exploit Adaptation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybersecurity-agencies-warn-of-china.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybersecurity-agencies-warn-of-china.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity agencies from Australia, Canada, Germany, Japan, New Zealand, South Korea, the U.K., and the U.S. have released a joint advisory about a China-linked cyber espionage group called APT40, warning about its ability to co-opt exploits for newly disclosed security flaws within hours or days of public release.
"APT 40 has previously targeted organizations in various countries, including]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Trojanized jQuery Packages Found on npm, GitHub, and jsDelivr Code Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/trojanized-jquery-packages-found-on-npm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/trojanized-jquery-packages-found-on-npm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-09T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unknown threat actors have been found propagating trojanized versions of jQuery on npm, GitHub, and jsDelivr in what appears to be an instance of a "complex and persistent" supply chain attack.
"This attack stands out due to the high variability across packages," Phylum said in an analysis published last week.
"The attacker has cleverly hidden the malware in the seldom-used 'end' function of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New APT Group "CloudSorcerer" Targets Russian Government Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-apt-group-cloudsorcerer-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-apt-group-cloudsorcerer-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented advanced persistent threat (APT) group dubbed CloudSorcerer has been observed targeting Russian government entities by leveraging cloud services for command-and-control (C2) and data exfiltration.
Cybersecurity firm Kaspersky, which discovered the activity in May 2024, the tradecraft adopted by the threat actor bears similarities with that of CloudWizard, but pointed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dark Web Malware Logs Expose 3,300 Users Linked to Child Abuse Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/dark-web-malware-logs-expose-3300-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/dark-web-malware-logs-expose-3300-users.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of information-stealing malware logs published on the dark web has led to the discovery of thousands of consumers of child sexual abuse material (CSAM), indicating how such information could be used to combat serious crimes.
"Approximately 3,300 unique users were found with accounts on known CSAM sources," Recorded Future said in a proof-of-concept (PoC) report published last week. "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Ransomware-as-a-Service 'Eldorado' Targets Windows and Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ransomware-as-service-eldorado.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-ransomware-as-service-eldorado.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An emerging ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation called Eldorado comes with locker variants to encrypt files on Windows and Linux systems.
Eldorado first appeared on March 16, 2024, when an advertisement for the affiliate program was posted on the ransomware forum RAMP, Singapore-headquartered Group-IB said.
The cybersecurity firm, which infiltrated the ransomware group, noted that its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Key Questions CISOs Must Ask Themselves About Their Cybersecurity Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/5-key-questions-cisos-must-ask.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/5-key-questions-cisos-must-ask.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Events like the recent massive CDK ransomware attack – which shuttered car dealerships across the U.S. in late June 2024 – barely raise public eyebrows anymore. 
Yet businesses, and the people that lead them, are justifiably jittery. Every CISO knows that cybersecurity is an increasingly hot topic for executives and board members alike. And when the inevitable CISO/Board briefing rolls]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Warn of Mekotio Banking Trojan Targeting Latin American Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-warn-of-mekotio-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/experts-warn-of-mekotio-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Financial institutions in Latin America are being threatened by a banking trojan called Mekotio (aka Melcoz).
That's according to findings from Trend Micro, which said it recently observed a surge in cyber attacks distributing the Windows malware.
Mekotio, known to be actively put to use since 2015, is known to target Latin American countries like Brazil, Chile, Mexico, Spain, Peru, and Portugal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-029 (08 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-029</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-029"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T09:42:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (08 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0548</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0548"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T06:58:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Unpatched Flaws Disclosed in Popular Gogs Open-Source Git Service]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-vulnerabilities-disclosed-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-vulnerabilities-disclosed-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four unpatched security flaws, including three critical ones, have been disclosed in the Gogs open-source, self-hosted Git service that could enable an authenticated attacker to breach susceptible instances, steal or wipe source code, and even plant backdoors.
The vulnerabilities, according to SonarSource researchers Thomas Chauchefoin and Paul Gerste, are listed below -

CVE-2024-39930 (CVSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Removes VPN Apps from Russian App Store Amid Government Pressure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/apple-removes-vpn-apps-from-russian-app.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/apple-removes-vpn-apps-from-russian-app.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-08T06:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple removed a number of virtual private network (VPN) apps in Russia from its App Store on July 4, 2024, following a request by Russia's state communications watchdog Roskomnadzor, Russian news media reported.
This includes the mobile apps of 25 VPN service providers, including ProtonVPN, Red Shield VPN, NordVPN and Le VPN, according to MediaZona. It's worth noting that NordVPN previously shut]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (05 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0547</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0547"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T13:06:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar Alert: Learn How ITDR Solutions Stop Sophisticated Identity Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/webinar-alert-learn-how-itdr-solutions.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/webinar-alert-learn-how-itdr-solutions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity theft isn't just about stolen credit cards anymore. Today, cybercriminals are using advanced tactics to infiltrate organizations and cause major damage with compromised credentials.
The stakes are high: ransomware attacks, lateral movement, and devastating data breaches.
Don't be caught off guard. Join us for a groundbreaking webinar that will change the way you approach cybersecurity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OVHcloud Hit with Record 840 Million PPS DDoS Attack Using MikroTik Routers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ovhcloud-hit-with-record-840-million.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ovhcloud-hit-with-record-840-million.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French cloud computing firm OVHcloud said it mitigated a record-breaking distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack in April 2024 that reached a packet rate of 840 million packets per second (Mpps).
This is just above the previous record of 809 million Mpps reported by Akamai as targeting a large European bank in June 2020.
The 840 Mpps DDoS attack is said to have been a combination of a TCP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (05 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0546</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0546"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T11:23:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blueprint for Success: Implementing a CTEM Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/blueprint-for-success-implementing-ctem.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/blueprint-for-success-implementing-ctem.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The attack surface isn’t what it once was and it’s becoming a nightmare to protect. A constantly expanding and evolving attack surface means risk to the business has skyrocketed and current security measures are struggling to keep it protected. If you’ve clicked on this article, there’s a good chance you’re looking for solutions to manage this risk.
In 2022, a new framework was coined by Gartner]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans VMware Cloud Director Availability (05 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0545</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0545"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T09:38:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Cloud Director Availability. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Apache HTTP Server (05 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0544</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0544"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T09:09:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Apache HTTP Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GootLoader Malware Still Active, Deploys New Versions for Enhanced Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gootloader-malware-delivers-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gootloader-malware-delivers-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T08:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The malware known as GootLoader continues to be in active use by threat actors looking to deliver additional payloads to compromised hosts.
"Updates to the GootLoader payload have resulted in several versions of GootLoader, with GootLoader 3 currently in active use," cybersecurity firm Cybereason said in an analysis published last week.
"While some of the particulars of GootLoader payloads have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Polyfill[.]io Attack Impacts Over 380,000 Hosts, Including Major Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/polyfillio-attack-impacts-over-380000.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/polyfillio-attack-impacts-over-380000.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T04:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The supply chain attack targeting widely-used Polyfill[.]io JavaScript library is wider in scope than previously thought, with new findings from Censys showing that over 380,000 hosts are embedding a polyfill script linking to the malicious domain as of July 2, 2024.
This includes references to "https://cdn.polyfill[.]io" or "https://cdn.polyfill[.]com" in their HTTP responses, the attack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Golang-Based Zergeca Botnet Capable of Powerful DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-golang-based-zergeca-botnet-capable.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-golang-based-zergeca-botnet-capable.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-05T03:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new botnet called Zergeca that's capable of conducting distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks.
Written in Golang, the botnet is so named for its reference to a string named "ootheca" present in the command-and-control (C2) servers ("ootheca[.]pw" and "ootheca[.]top").
"Functionally, Zergeca is not just a typical DDoS botnet; besides supporting six]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Apache Tomcat (04 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0543</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0543"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Apache Tomcat. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB (04 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0542</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0542"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:31:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Splunk (04 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0541</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0541"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:24:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Splunk. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Python (04 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0540</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0540"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Python. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Uncovers Critical Flaws in Rockwell Automation PanelView Plus]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsoft-uncovers-critical-flaws-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/microsoft-uncovers-critical-flaws-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has revealed two security flaws in Rockwell Automation PanelView Plus that could be weaponized by remote, unauthenticated attackers to execute arbitrary code and trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition.
"The [remote code execution] vulnerability in PanelView Plus involves two custom classes that can be abused to upload and load a malicious DLL into the device," security researcher]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil Halts Meta's AI Data Processing Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/brazil-halts-metas-ai-data-processing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/brazil-halts-metas-ai-data-processing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazil's data protection authority, Autoridade Nacional de Proteção de Dados (ANPD), has temporarily banned Meta from processing users' personal data to train the company's artificial intelligence (AI) algorithms.
The ANPD said it found "evidence of processing of personal data based on inadequate legal hypothesis, lack of transparency, limitation of the rights of data subjects, and risks to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Police Operation Shuts Down 600 Cybercrime Servers Linked to Cobalt Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/global-police-operation-shuts-down-600.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/global-police-operation-shuts-down-600.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T03:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coordinated law enforcement operation codenamed MORPHEUS has felled close to 600 servers that were used by cybercriminal groups and were part of an attack infrastructure associated with the Cobalt Strike. 
The crackdown targeted older, unlicensed versions of the Cobalt Strike red teaming framework between June 24 and 28, according to Europol.
Of the 690 IP addresses that were flagged to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Twilio's Authy App Breach Exposes Millions of Phone Numbers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/twilios-authy-app-breach-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/twilios-authy-app-breach-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-04T03:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud communications provider Twilio has revealed that unidentified threat actors took advantage of an unauthenticated endpoint in Authy to identify data associated with Authy accounts, including users' cell phone numbers.
The company said it took steps to secure the endpoint to no longer accept unauthenticated requests.
The development comes days after an online persona named ShinyHunters]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité OpenSSH dans des systèmes d'exploitation (03 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0539</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0539"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T12:56:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans le composant OpenSSH utilisé par différents systèmes d'exploitation. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Identity Exposure (03 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0538</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0538"/>
        <updated>2024-07-03T11:12:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Identity Exposure. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>