<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2023-12-31T17:26:39.451Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Scam-as-a-Service Aiding Cybercriminals in Crypto Wallet-Draining Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/beware-scam-as-service-aiding.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/beware-scam-as-service-aiding.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-30T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about an increase in phishing attacks that are capable of draining cryptocurrency wallets.
"These threats are unique in their approach, targeting a wide range of blockchain networks, from Ethereum and Binance Smart Chain to Polygon, Avalanche, and almost 20 other networks by using a crypto wallet-draining technique," Check Point researchers Oded Vanunu,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Albanian Parliament and One Albania Telecom Hit by Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/albanian-parliament-and-one-albania.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/albanian-parliament-and-one-albania.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T13:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Assembly of the Republic of Albania and telecom company One Albania have been targeted by cyber attacks, the country’s National Authority for Electronic Certification and Cyber Security (AKCESK) revealed this week.
“These infrastructures, under the legislation in force, are not currently classified as critical or important information infrastructure,” AKCESK said.
One Albania, which has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERT-UA Uncovers New Malware Wave Distributing OCEANMAP, MASEPIE, STEELHOOK]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cert-ua-uncovers-new-malware-wave.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cert-ua-uncovers-new-malware-wave.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of a new phishing campaign orchestrated by the Russia-linked APT28 group to deploy previously undocumented malware such as OCEANMAP, MASEPIE, and STEELHOOK to harvest sensitive information.
The activity, which was detected by the agency between December 15 and 25, 2023, targets government entities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1062 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (29 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1062/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1062/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T09:59:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Juniper Secure Analytics. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1061 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Apache OpenOffice (29 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1061/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1061/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T09:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Apache OpenOffice. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky Hackers Deploying AppleSeed, Meterpreter, and TinyNuke in Latest Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/kimsuky-hackers-deploying-appleseed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/kimsuky-hackers-deploying-appleseed.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T09:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-state actors affiliated to North Korea have been observed using spear-phishing attacks to deliver an assortment of backdoors and tools such as AppleSeed, Meterpreter, and TinyNuke to seize control of compromised machines.
South Korea-based cybersecurity company AhnLab attributed the activity to an advanced persistent threat group known as Kimsuky.
“A notable point about attacks that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Disables MSIX App Installer Protocol Widely Used in Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-disables-msix-app-installer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-disables-msix-app-installer.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-29T05:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Thursday said it’s once again disabling the ms-appinstaller protocol handler by default following its abuse by multiple threat actors to distribute malware.
“The observed threat actor activity abuses the current implementation of the ms-appinstaller protocol handler as an access vector for malware that may lead to ransomware distribution,” the Microsoft Threat Intelligence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud Resolves Privilege Escalation Flaw Impacting Kubernetes Service]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/google-cloud-resolves-privilege.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/google-cloud-resolves-privilege.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T13:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google Cloud has addressed a medium-severity security flaw in its platform that could be abused by an attacker who already has access to a Kubernetes cluster to escalate their privileges.
"An attacker who has compromised the Fluent Bit logging container could combine that access with high privileges required by Anthos Service Mesh (on clusters that have enabled it) to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Most Sophisticated iPhone Hack Ever Exploited Apple's Hidden Hardware Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/most-sophisticated-iphone-hack-ever.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/most-sophisticated-iphone-hack-ever.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Operation Triangulation spyware attacks targeting Apple iOS devices leveraged never-before-seen exploits that made it possible to even bypass pivotal hardware-based security protections erected by the company.
Russian cybersecurity firm Kaspersky, which discovered the campaign at the beginning of 2023 after becoming one of the targets, described it as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1060 : Vulnérabilité dans NetApp Active IQ Unified Manager (28 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1060/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1060/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T09:56:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans NetApp Active IQ Unified Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Rugmi Malware Loader Surges with Hundreds of Daily Detections]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-rugmi-malware-loader-surges-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-rugmi-malware-loader-surges-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-28T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware loader is being used by threat actors to deliver a wide range of information stealers such as Lumma Stealer (aka LummaC2), Vidar, RecordBreaker (aka Raccoon Stealer V2), and Rescoms.
Cybersecurity firm ESET is tracking the trojan under the name Win/TrojanDownloader.Rugmi.
"This malware is a loader with three types of components: a downloader that downloads an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Zero-Day in Apache OfBiz ERP System Exposes Businesses to Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/critical-zero-day-in-apache-ofbiz-erp.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/critical-zero-day-in-apache-ofbiz-erp.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new zero-day security flaw has been discovered in the Apache OfBiz, an open-source Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) system that could be exploited to bypass authentication protections.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-51467, resides in the login functionality and is the result of an incomplete patch for another critical vulnerability (CVE-2023-49070, CVSS score: 9.8) that was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploited New Zero-Day in Barracuda's ESG Appliances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/chinese-hackers-exploited-new-zero-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/chinese-hackers-exploited-new-zero-day.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Barracuda has revealed that Chinese threat actors exploited a new zero-day in its Email Security Gateway (ESG) appliances to deploy backdoor on a "limited number" of devices.
Tracked as CVE-2023-7102, the issue relates to a case of arbitrary code execution that resides within a third-party and open-source library Spreadsheet::ParseExcel that's used by the Amavis scanner within the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Sneaky Xamalicious Android Malware Hits Over 327,000 Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-sneaky-xamalicious-android-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-sneaky-xamalicious-android-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Android backdoor has been discovered with potent capabilities to carry out a range of malicious actions on infected devices.
Dubbed Xamalicious by the McAfee Mobile Research Team, the malware is so named for the fact that it's developed using an open-source mobile app framework called Xamarin and abuses the operating system's accessibility permissions to fulfill its objectives.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: Poorly Secured Linux SSH Servers Under Attack for Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/warning-poorly-secured-linux-ssh.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/warning-poorly-secured-linux-ssh.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-27T05:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Poorly secured Linux SSH servers are being targeted by bad actors to install port scanners and dictionary attack tools with the goal of targeting other vulnerable servers and co-opting them into a network to carry out cryptocurrency mining and distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks.
"Threat actors can also choose to install only scanners and sell the breached IP and account credentials on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-ACT-055 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2023-ACT-055 (26 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-055/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-055/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T16:26:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1059 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moxa ioLogik E1200 (26 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1059/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1059/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T09:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moxa ioLogik E1200. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1058 : Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (26 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1058/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1058/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T08:57:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Stormshield Network Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Carbanak Banking Malware Resurfaces with New Ransomware Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/carbanak-banking-malware-resurfaces.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/carbanak-banking-malware-resurfaces.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-26T07:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The banking malware known as Carbanak has been observed being used in ransomware attacks with updated tactics.
"The malware has adapted to incorporate attack vendors and techniques to diversify its effectiveness," cybersecurity firm NCC Group said in an analysis of ransomware attacks that took place in November 2023.
"Carbanak returned last month through new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud Atlas' Spear-Phishing Attacks Target Russian Agro and Research Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cloud-atlas-spear-phishing-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cloud-atlas-spear-phishing-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-25T07:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor referred to as Cloud Atlas has been linked to a set of spear-phishing attacks on Russian enterprises.
Targets included a Russian agro-industrial enterprise and a state-owned research company, according to a report from F.A.C.C.T., a standalone cybersecurity company formed after Group-IB's formal exit from Russia earlier this year.
Cloud Atlas, active since at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[British LAPSUS$ Teen Members Sentenced for High-Profile Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/british-lapsus-teen-members-sentenced.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/british-lapsus-teen-members-sentenced.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-24T05:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two British teens part of the LAPSUS$ cyber crime and extortion gang have been sentenced for their roles in orchestrating a string of high-profile attacks against a number of companies.
Arion Kurtaj, an 18-year-old from Oxford, has been sentenced to an indefinite hospital order due to his intent to get back to cybercrime "as soon as possible," BBC reported. Kurtaj, who is autistic, was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogue WordPress Plugin Exposes E-Commerce Sites to Credit Card Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/rogue-wordpress-plugin-exposes-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/rogue-wordpress-plugin-exposes-e.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have discovered a rogue WordPress plugin that's capable of creating bogus administrator users and injecting malicious JavaScript code to steal credit card information.
The skimming activity is part of a Magecart campaign targeting e-commerce websites, according to Sucuri.
"As with many other malicious or fake WordPress plugins it contains some deceptive information at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1057 : Vulnérabilité dans Postfix (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1057/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1057/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:56:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans . Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1056 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1056/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1056/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:48:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Operation RusticWeb: Rust-Based Malware Targets Indian Government Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/operation-rusticweb-rust-based-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/operation-rusticweb-rust-based-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian government entities and the defense sector have been targeted by a phishing campaign that's engineered to drop Rust-based malware for intelligence gathering.
The activity, first detected in October 2023, has been codenamed Operation RusticWeb by enterprise security firm SEQRITE.
"New Rust-based payloads and encrypted PowerShell commands have been utilized to exfiltrate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1055 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1055/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1055/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T12:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Decoy Microsoft Word Documents Used to Deliver Nim-Based Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/decoy-microsoft-word-documents-used-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/decoy-microsoft-word-documents-used-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T12:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing campaign is leveraging decoy Microsoft Word documents as bait to deliver a backdoor written in the Nim programming language.
"Malware written in uncommon programming languages puts the security community at a disadvantage as researchers and reverse engineers' unfamiliarity can hamper their investigation," Netskope researchers Ghanashyam Satpathy and Jan Michael Alcantara]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1054 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1054/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1054/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T12:42:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1053 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits ESET (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1053/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1053/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:17:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits ESET. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1052 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (22 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1052/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1052/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T10:12:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Access Rights Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[UAC-0099 Using WinRAR Exploit to Target Ukrainian Firms with LONEPAGE Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/uac-0099-using-winrar-exploit-to-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/uac-0099-using-winrar-exploit-to-target.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T07:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as UAC-0099 has been linked to continued attacks aimed at Ukraine, some of which leverage a high-severity flaw in the WinRAR software to deliver a malware strain called LONEPAGE.
"The threat actor targets Ukrainian employees working for companies outside of Ukraine," cybersecurity firm Deep Instinct said in a Thursday analysis.
UAC-0099 was first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of New 'FalseFont' Backdoor Targeting the Defense Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-new-falsefont.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-new-falsefont.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-22T05:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations in the Defense Industrial Base (DIB) sector are in the crosshairs of an Iranian threat actor as part of a campaign designed to deliver a never-before-seen backdoor called FalseFont.
The findings come from Microsoft, which is tracking the activity under its weather-themed moniker Peach Sandstorm (formerly Holmium), which is also known as APT33, Elfin, and Refined Kitten.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Detail Multi-Million Dollar Licensing Model of Predator Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/multi-million-dollar-predator-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/multi-million-dollar-predator-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new analysis of the sophisticated commercial spyware called Predator has revealed that its ability to persist between reboots is offered as an "add-on feature" and that it depends on the licensing options opted by a customer.
"In 2021, Predator spyware couldn't survive a reboot on the infected Android system (it had it on iOS)," Cisco Talos researchers Mike Gentile, Asheer Malhotra, and Vitor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chameleon Android Banking Trojan Variant Bypasses Biometric Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-chameleon-android-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-chameleon-android-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an updated version of an Android banking malware called Chameleon that has expanded its targeting to include users in the U.K. and Italy.
"Representing a restructured and enhanced iteration of its predecessor, this evolved Chameleon variant excels in executing Device Takeover (DTO) using the accessibility service, all while expanding its targeted region,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New JavaScript Malware Targeted 50,000+ Users at Dozens of Banks Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-javascript-malware-targeted-50000.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-javascript-malware-targeted-50000.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new piece of JavaScript malware has been observed attempting to steal users' online banking account credentials as part of a campaign that has targeted more than 40 financial institutions across the world.
The activity cluster, which employs JavaScript web injections, is estimated to have led to at least 50,000 infected user sessions spanning North America, South America, Europe, and Japan.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cost of a Data Breach Report 2023: Insights, Mitigators and Best Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cost-of-data-breach-report-2023.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cost-of-data-breach-report-2023.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[John Hanley of IBM Security shares 4 key findings from the highly acclaimed annual Cost of a Data Breach Report 2023
What is the IBM Cost of a Data Breach Report?
The IBM Cost of a Data Breach Report is an annual report that provides organizations with quantifiable information about the financial impacts of breaches. With this data, they can make data driven decisions about how they implement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Authorities Dismantle Dark Web Hub 'Kingdom Market' in Global Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/german-authorities-dismantle-dark-web.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/german-authorities-dismantle-dark-web.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German law enforcement has announced the disruption of a dark web platform called Kingdom Market that specialized in the sales of narcotics and malware to "tens of thousands of users."
The exercise, which involved collaboration from authorities from the U.S., Switzerland, Moldova, and Ukraine, began on December 16, 2023, the Federal Criminal Police Office (BKA) said.
Kingdom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1051 : Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (21 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1051/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1051/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T09:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.
 Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2023-7024 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1050 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (21 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1050/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1050/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T09:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1049 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ivanti Avalanche (21 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1049/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1049/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T08:52:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ivanti Avalanche. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting Old MS Excel Vulnerability to Spread Agent Tesla Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-exploiting-old-ms-excel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-exploiting-old-ms-excel.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T07:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are weaponizing an old Microsoft Office vulnerability as part of phishing campaigns to distribute a strain of malware called Agent Tesla.
The infection chains leverage decoy Excel documents attached in invoice-themed messages to trick potential targets into opening them and activate the exploitation of CVE-2017-11882 (CVSS score: 7.8), a memory corruption vulnerability in Office's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urgent: New Chrome Zero-Day Vulnerability Exploited in the Wild - Update ASAP]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/urgent-new-chrome-zero-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/urgent-new-chrome-zero-day.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-21T03:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has rolled out security updates for the Chrome web browser to address a high-severity zero-day flaw that it said has been exploited in the wild.
The vulnerability, assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2023-7024, has been described as a heap-based buffer overflow bug in the WebRTC framework that could be exploited to result in program crashes or arbitrary code execution.
Clément]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Remote Encryption Attacks Surge: How One Vulnerable Device Can Spell Disaster]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/remote-encryption-attacks-surge-how-one.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/remote-encryption-attacks-surge-how-one.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware groups are increasingly switching to remote encryption in their attacks, marking a new escalation in tactics adopted by financially motivated actors to ensure the success of their campaigns.
"Companies can have thousands of computers connected to their network, and with remote ransomware, all it takes is one underprotected device to compromise the entire network," Mark Loman, vice]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Product Explained: Memcyco's Real-Time Defense Against Website Spoofing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/product-explained-memcycos-real-time.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/product-explained-memcycos-real-time.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-On Review: Memcyco’s Threat Intelligence Solution
Website impersonation, also known as brandjacking or website spoofing, has emerged as a significant threat to online businesses. Malicious actors clone legitimate websites to trick customers, leading to financial scams and data theft causing reputation damage and financial losses for both organizations and customers.
The Growing Threat of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Chinese-Speaking Hackers Pose as UAE Authority in Latest Smishing Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/alert-chinese-hackers-pose-as-uae.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/alert-chinese-hackers-pose-as-uae.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese-speaking threat actors behind Smishing Triad have been observed masquerading as the United Arab Emirates Federal Authority for Identity and Citizenship to send malicious SMS messages with the ultimate goal of gathering sensitive information from residents and foreigners in the country.
"These criminals send malicious links to their victims' mobile devices through SMS or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3,500 Arrested in Global Operation HAECHI-IV Targeting Financial Criminals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/3500-arrested-in-global-operation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/3500-arrested-in-global-operation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T08:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A six-month-long international police operation codenamed HAECHI-IV has resulted in the arrests of nearly 3,500 individuals and seizures worth $300 million across 34 countries.
The exercise, which took place from July through December 2023, took aim at various types of financial crimes such as voice phishing, romance scams, online sextortion, investment fraud, money laundering]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Go-Based JaskaGO Malware Targeting Windows and macOS Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-go-based-jaskago-malware-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-go-based-jaskago-malware-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T08:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Go-based information stealer malware called JaskaGO has emerged as the latest cross-platform threat to infiltrate both Windows and Apple macOS systems.
AT&T Alien Labs, which made the discovery, said the malware is "equipped with an extensive array of commands from its command-and-control (C&C) server."
Artifacts designed for macOS were first observed in July]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1048 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (20 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1048/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1048/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:38:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1047 : Vulnérabilité dans macOS Sonoma (20 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1047/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1047/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-20T07:31:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans macOS Sonoma. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Takes Down BlackCat Ransomware, Releases Free Decryption Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/fbi-takes-down-blackcat-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/fbi-takes-down-blackcat-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Justice Department (DoJ) has officially announced the disruption of the BlackCat ransomware operation and released a decryption tool that victims can use to regain access to files locked by the malware.
Court documents show that the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) enlisted the help of a confidential human source (CHS) to act as an affiliate for the BlackCat and gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes of Matveev's Ransomware Empire: Tactics and Team]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/behind-scenes-of-matveevs-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/behind-scenes-of-matveevs-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on the inner workings of the ransomware operation led by Mikhail Pavlovich Matveev, a Russian national who was indicted by the U.S. government earlier this year for his alleged role in launching thousands of attacks across the world.
Matveev, who resides in Saint Petersburg and is known by the aliases Wazawaka, m1x, Boriselcin, Uhodiransomwar,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Abusing GitHub to Evade Detection and Control Compromised Hosts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-abusing-github-to-evade.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-abusing-github-to-evade.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are increasingly making use of GitHub for malicious purposes through novel methods, including abusing secret Gists and issuing malicious commands via git commit messages.
"Malware authors occasionally place their samples in services like Dropbox, Google Drive, OneDrive, and Discord to host second stage malware and sidestep detection tools," ReversingLabs researcher Karlo Zanki]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are We Ready to Give Up on Security Awareness Training?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/are-we-ready-to-give-up-on-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/are-we-ready-to-give-up-on-security.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T11:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Some of you have already started budgeting for 2024 and allocating funds to security areas within your organization. It is safe to say that employee security awareness training is one of the expenditure items, too. However, its effectiveness is an open question with people still engaging in insecure behaviors at the workplace. Besides, social engineering remains one of the most prevalent attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Using MuddyC2Go in Telecom Espionage Attacks Across Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/iranian-hackers-using-muddyc2go-in-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/iranian-hackers-using-muddyc2go-in-new.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T11:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian nation-state actor known as MuddyWater has leveraged a newly discovered command-and-control (C2) framework called MuddyC2Go in its attacks on the telecommunications sector in Egypt, Sudan, and Tanzania.
The Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, is tracking the activity under the name Seedworm, which is also tracked under the monikers Boggy Serpens, Cobalt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malvertising Campaign Distributing PikaBot Disguised as Popular Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-malvertising-campaign-distributing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-malvertising-campaign-distributing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The malware loader known as PikaBot is being distributed as part of a malvertising campaign targeting users searching for legitimate software like AnyDesk.
"PikaBot was previously only distributed via malspam campaigns similarly to QakBot and emerged as one of the preferred payloads for a threat actor known as TA577," Malwarebytes' Jérôme Segura said.
The malware family,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1046 : Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network VPN Client (19 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1046/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1046/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Stormshield Network VPN Client. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1045 : Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (19 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1045/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1045/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:01:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1044 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans OpenSSH (19 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1044/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1044/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T08:00:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans OpenSSH. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8220 Gang Exploiting Oracle WebLogic Server Vulnerability to Spread Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/8220-gang-exploiting-oracle-weblogic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/8220-gang-exploiting-oracle-weblogic.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors associated with the 8220 Gang have been observed exploiting a high-severity flaw in Oracle WebLogic Server to propagate their malware.
The security shortcoming is CVE-2020-14883 (CVSS score: 7.2), a remote code execution bug that could be exploited by authenticated attackers to take over susceptible servers.
"This vulnerability allows remote authenticated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Double-Extortion Play Ransomware Strikes 300 Organizations Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/double-extortion-play-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/double-extortion-play-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-19T05:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the Play ransomware are estimated to have impacted approximately 300 entities as of October 2023, according to a new joint cybersecurity advisory from Australia and the U.S.
"Play ransomware actors employ a double-extortion model, encrypting systems after exfiltrating data and have impacted a wide range of businesses and critical infrastructure organizations in North]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Experts Reveal New Details on Zero-Click Outlook RCE Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/beware-experts-reveal-new-details-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/beware-experts-reveal-new-details-on.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T15:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical details have emerged about two now-patched security flaws in Microsoft Windows that could be chained by threat actors to achieve remote code execution on the Outlook email service sans any user interaction.
"An attacker on the internet can chain the vulnerabilities together to create a full, zero-click remote code execution (RCE) exploit against Outlook clients," Akamai security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 7 Trends Shaping SaaS Security in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/top-7-trends-shaping-saas-security-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/top-7-trends-shaping-saas-security-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past few years, SaaS has developed into the backbone of corporate IT. Service businesses, such as medical practices, law firms, and financial services firms, are almost entirely SaaS based. Non-service businesses, including manufacturers and retailers, have about 70% of their software in the cloud. 
These applications contain a wealth of data, from minimally sensitive general]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rhadamanthys Malware: Swiss Army Knife of Information Stealers Emerges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/rhadamanthys-malware-swiss-army-knife.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/rhadamanthys-malware-swiss-army-knife.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The developers of the information stealer malware known as Rhadamanthys are actively iterating on its features, broadening its information-gathering capabilities and also incorporating a plugin system to make it more customizable.
This approach not only transforms it into a threat capable of delivering "specific distributor needs," but also makes it more potent, Check Point said&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1043 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Zimbra Collaboration (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1043/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1043/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T13:48:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Zimbra Collaboration. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1042 : Vulnérabilités dans MISP (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1042/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1042/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T13:15:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MISP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1041 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nextcloud Server (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1041/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1041/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T13:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nextcloud Server. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1040 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Asterisk (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1040/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1040/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T12:39:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Asterisk. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-ACT-054 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2023-ACT-054 (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-054/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-054/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T12:21:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four U.S. Nationals Charged in $80 Million Pig Butchering Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/four-us-nationals-charged-in-80-million.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/four-us-nationals-charged-in-80-million.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four U.S. nationals have been charged for participating in an illicit scheme that earned them more than $80 million via cryptocurrency investment scams.
The defendants – Lu Zhang, 36, of Alhambra, California; Justin Walker, 31, of Cypress, California; Joseph Wong, 32, Rosemead, California; and Hailong Zhu, 40, Naperville, Illinois – have been charged with conspiracy to commit money laundering,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmasking the Dark Side of Low-Code/No-Code Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/unmasking-dark-side-of-low-codeno-code.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/unmasking-dark-side-of-low-codeno-code.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Low-code/no-code (LCNC) and robotic process automation (RPA) have gained immense popularity, but how secure are they? Is your security team paying enough attention in an era of rapid digital transformation, where business users are empowered to create applications swiftly using platforms like Microsoft PowerApps, UiPath, ServiceNow, Mendix, and OutSystems?
The simple truth is often swept under]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QakBot Malware Resurfaces with New Tactics, Targeting the Hospitality Industry]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/qakbot-malware-resurfaces-with-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/qakbot-malware-resurfaces-with-new.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T09:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new wave of phishing messages distributing the QakBot malware has been observed, more than three months after a law enforcement effort saw its infrastructure dismantled by infiltrating its command-and-control (C2) network.
Microsoft, which made the discovery, described it as a low-volume campaign that began on December 11, 2023, and targeted the hospitality industry.
"Targets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-CTI-010 : État de la menace ciblant le secteur des télécommunications (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2023-CTI-010/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2023-CTI-010/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T09:05:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le secteur des télécommunications intègre une typologie d’acteurs variée allant des opérateurs de communication électroniques (OCE) aux …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1039 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Stormshield Network Security (18 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1039/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1039/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T07:50:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Stormshield Network Security. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Urges Manufacturers Eliminate Default Passwords to Thwart Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cisa-urges-manufacturers-eliminate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/cisa-urges-manufacturers-eliminate.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-18T05:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) is urging manufacturers to get rid of default passwords on internet-exposed systems altogether, citing severe risks that could be exploited by malicious actors to gain initial access to, and move laterally within, organizations.
In an alert published last week, the agency called out Iranian threat actors affiliated with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB Suffers Security Breach, Exposing Customer Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/mongodb-suffers-security-breach.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/mongodb-suffers-security-breach.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-17T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[MongoDB on Saturday disclosed it's actively investigating a security incident that has led to unauthorized access to "certain" corporate systems, resulting in the exposure of customer account metadata and contact information.
The American database software company said it first detected anomalous activity on December 13, 2023, and that it immediately activated its incident response]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China's MIIT Introduces Color-Coded Action Plan for Data Security Incidents]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/chinas-miit-introduces-color-coded.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/chinas-miit-introduces-color-coded.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T07:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's Ministry of Industry and Information Technology (MIIT) on Friday unveiled draft proposals detailing its plans to tackle data security events in the country using a color-coded system.
The effort is designed to "improve the comprehensive response capacity for data security incidents, to ensure timely and effective control, mitigation and elimination of hazards and losses caused]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Storm-0539: The Rising Threat Behind Holiday Gift Card Frauds]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-storm-0539-rising.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-storm-0539-rising.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-16T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning of an uptick in malicious activity from an emerging threat cluster it's tracking as Storm-0539 for orchestrating gift card fraud and theft via highly sophisticated email and SMS phishing attacks against retail entities during the holiday shopping season.
The goal of the attacks is to propagate booby-trapped links that direct victims to adversary-in-the-middle (AiTM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New KV-Botnet Targeting Cisco, DrayTek, and Fortinet Devices for Stealthy Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-kv-botnet-targeting-cisco-draytek.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-kv-botnet-targeting-cisco-draytek.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T14:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new botnet consisting of firewalls and routers from Cisco, DrayTek, Fortinet, and NETGEAR is being used as a covert data transfer network for advanced persistent threat actors, including the China-linked threat actor called Volt Typhoon.
Dubbed KV-botnet by the Black Lotus Labs team at Lumen Technologies, the malicious network is an amalgamation of two complementary activity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1038 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1038/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1038/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T13:20:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1037 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1037/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1037/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T13:17:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Hardware Wallet Ledger's Supply Chain Breach Results in $600,000 Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/crypto-hardware-wallet-ledgers-supply.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/crypto-hardware-wallet-ledgers-supply.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto hardware wallet maker Ledger published a new version of its "@ledgerhq/connect-kit" npm module after unidentified threat actors pushed malicious code that led to the theft of more than $600,000 in virtual assets.
The compromise was the result of a former employee falling victim to a phishing attack, the company said in a statement.
This allowed the attackers to gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1036 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1036/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1036/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T12:36:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un problème de sécurité non spécifié par …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bug or Feature? Hidden Web Application Vulnerabilities Uncovered]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/bug-or-feature-hidden-web-application.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/bug-or-feature-hidden-web-application.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Web Application Security consists of a myriad of security controls that ensure that a web application:

Functions as expected.
Cannot be exploited to operate out of bounds.
Cannot initiate operations that it is not supposed to do.

Web Applications have become ubiquitous after the expansion of Web 2.0, which Social Media Platforms, E-Commerce websites, and email clients saturating the internet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Security Vulnerabilities Uncovered in pfSense Firewall Software - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-security-vulnerabilities-uncovered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-security-vulnerabilities-uncovered.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T11:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security vulnerabilities have been discovered in the open-source Netgate pfSense firewall solution called pfSense that could be chained by an attacker to execute arbitrary commands on susceptible appliances.
The issues relate to two reflected cross-site scripting (XSS) bugs and one command injection flaw, according to new findings from Sonar.
"Security inside a local network is often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1035 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1035/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1035/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T10:12:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la fonctionnalité de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1034 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1034/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1034/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T08:36:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1033 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Security Center (15 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1033/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1033/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T08:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Security Center. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's New Tracking Protection in Chrome Blocks Third-Party Cookies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/googles-new-tracking-protection-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/googles-new-tracking-protection-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Thursday announced that it will start testing a new feature called "Tracking Protection" starting January 4, 2024, to 1% of Chrome users as part of its efforts to deprecate third-party cookies in the web browser.
The setting is designed to limit "cross-site tracking by restricting website access to third-party cookies by default," Anthony Chavez, vice president of Privacy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New NKAbuse Malware Exploits NKN Blockchain Tech for DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-nkabuse-malware-exploits-nkn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-nkabuse-malware-exploits-nkn.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-15T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel multi-platform threat called NKAbuse has been discovered using a decentralized, peer-to-peer network connectivity protocol known as NKN (short for New Kind of Network) as a communications channel.
"The malware utilizes NKN technology for data exchange between peers, functioning as a potent implant, and equipped with both flooder and backdoor capabilities," Russian]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[116 Malware Packages Found on PyPI Repository Infecting Windows and Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/116-malware-packages-found-on-pypi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/116-malware-packages-found-on-pypi.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified a set of 116 malicious packages on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that are designed to infect Windows and Linux systems with a custom backdoor.
"In some cases, the final payload is a variant of the infamous W4SP Stealer, or a simple clipboard monitor to steal cryptocurrency, or both," ESET researchers Marc-Etienne M.Léveillé and Rene]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1032 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1032/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1032/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T15:03:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1031 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1031/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1031/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:53:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1030 : Vulnérabilité dans Squid (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1030/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1030/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:25:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Squid. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Pierogi++ Malware by Gaza Cyber Gang Targeting Palestinian Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-pierogi-malware-by-gaza-cyber-gang.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-pierogi-malware-by-gaza-cyber-gang.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pro-Hamas threat actor known as Gaza Cyber Gang is targeting Palestinian entities using an updated version of a backdoor dubbed Pierogi.
The findings come from SentinelOne, which has given the malware the name Pierogi++ owing to the fact that it's implemented in the C++ programming language unlike its Delphi- and Pascal-based predecessor.
"Recent Gaza Cybergang activities show]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian State-Sponsored OilRig Group Deploys 3 New Malware Downloaders]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/iranian-state-sponsored-oilrig-group.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/iranian-state-sponsored-oilrig-group.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian state-sponsored threat actor known as OilRig deployed three different downloader malware throughout 2022 to maintain persistent access to victim organizations located in Israel.
The three new downloaders have been named ODAgent, OilCheck, and OilBooster by Slovak cybersecurity company ESET. The attacks also involved the use of an updated version of a known OilRig downloader]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1029 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1029/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1029/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T12:24:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagining Network Pentesting With Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/reimagining-network-pentesting-with-automation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/reimagining-network-pentesting-with-automation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network penetration testing plays a crucial role in protecting businesses in the ever-evolving world of cybersecurity. Yet, business leaders and IT pros have misconceptions about this process, which impacts their security posture and decision-making. 
This blog acts as a quick guide on network penetration testing, explaining what it is, debunking common myths and reimagining its role in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Reimagining Network Pentesting With Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/reimagining-network-pentesting-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/reimagining-network-pentesting-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Network penetration testing plays a crucial role in protecting businesses in the ever-evolving world of cybersecurity. Yet, business leaders and IT pros have misconceptions about this process, which impacts their security posture and decision-making. 
This blog acts as a quick guide on network penetration testing, explaining what it is, debunking common myths and reimagining its role in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1028 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Wallix (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1028/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1028/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T10:39:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Wallix. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian SVR-Linked APT29 Targets JetBrains TeamCity Servers in Ongoing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-svr-linked-apt29-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-svr-linked-apt29-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors affiliated with the Russian Foreign Intelligence Service (SVR) have targeted unpatched JetBrains TeamCity servers in widespread attacks since September 2023.
The activity has been tied to a nation-state group known as APT29, which is also tracked as BlueBravo, Cloaked Ursa, Cozy Bear, Midnight Blizzard (formerly Nobelium), and The Dukes. It's notable for the supply chain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1027 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1027/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1027/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T10:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1026 : Vulnérabilité dans VMware Workspace ONE Launcher (14 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1026/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1026/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T09:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Workspace ONE Launcher. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Hacker Group 'GambleForce' Tageting APAC Firms Using SQL Injection Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-hacker-group-gambleforce-tageting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-hacker-group-gambleforce-tageting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown hacker outfit called GambleForce has been attributed to a series of SQL injection attacks against companies primarily in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region since at least September 2023.
"GambleForce uses a set of basic yet very effective techniques, including SQL injections and the exploitation of vulnerable website content management systems (CMS) to steal sensitive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Takes Legal Action to Crack Down on Storm-1152's Cybercrime Network]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-takes-legal-action-to-crack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-takes-legal-action-to-crack.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-14T05:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Wednesday said it obtained a court order to seize infrastructure set up by a group called Storm-1152 that peddled roughly 750 million fraudulent Microsoft accounts and tools through a network of bogus websites and social media pages to other criminal actors, netting them millions of dollars in illicit revenue.
"Fraudulent online accounts act as the gateway to a host of cybercrime,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-ALE-013 : Vulnérabilité dans Apache Struts 2 (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2023-ALE-013/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2023-ALE-013/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T17:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 4 décembre 2023, Apache a publié un avis de sécurité concernant la vulnérabilité critique CVE-2023-50164 concernant le cadriciel Struts 2. Cette vulnérabilité permet à un attaquant non …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BazaCall Phishing Scammers Now Leveraging Google Forms for Deception]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/bazacall-phishing-scammers-now.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/bazacall-phishing-scammers-now.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the BazaCall call back phishing attacks have been observed leveraging Google Forms to lend the scheme a veneer of credibility.
The method is an "attempt to elevate the perceived authenticity of the initial malicious emails," cybersecurity firm Abnormal Security said in a report published today.
BazaCall (aka BazarCall), which was first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1025 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1025/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1025/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:05:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans les produits Microsoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une usurpation d'identité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1024 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1024/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1024/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:05:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une usurpation d'identité, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1023 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1023/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1023/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:05:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Windows. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service, une usurpation d'identité et une …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1022 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1022/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T15:05:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une usurpation d'identité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1021 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits PRIM’X (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1021/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T14:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits PRIM'X. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.
 La très forte …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Using Clang Sanitizers to Protect Android Against Cellular Baseband Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/google-using-clang-sanitizers-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/google-using-clang-sanitizers-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is highlighting the role played by Clang sanitizers in hardening the security of the cellular baseband in the Android operating system and preventing specific kinds of vulnerabilities.
This comprises Integer Overflow Sanitizer (IntSan) and BoundsSanitizer (BoundSan), both of which are part of UndefinedBehaviorSanitizer (UBSan), a tool designed to catch various kinds of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Analyze Malware’s Network Traffic in A Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/how-to-analyze-malwares-network-traffic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/how-to-analyze-malwares-network-traffic.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malware analysis encompasses a broad range of activities, including examining the malware's network traffic. To be effective at it, it's crucial to understand the common challenges and how to overcome them. Here are three prevalent issues you may encounter and the tools you'll need to address them.
Decrypting HTTPS traffic
Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure (HTTPS), the protocol for secure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1020 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1020/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1020/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:56:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Hackers Exploiting OAuth for Cryptocurrency Mining and Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-hackers-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-hackers-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has warned that adversaries are using OAuth applications as an automation tool to deploy virtual machines (VMs) for cryptocurrency mining and launch phishing attacks.
"Threat actors compromise user accounts to create, modify, and grant high privileges to OAuth applications that they can misuse to hide malicious activity," the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team said in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1019 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1019/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1019/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:51:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Cyber Attack Paralyzes Kyivstar - Ukraine's Largest Telecom Operator]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/major-cyber-attack-paralyzes-kyivstar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/major-cyber-attack-paralyzes-kyivstar.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine's biggest telecom operator Kyivstar has become the victim of a cyber attack, disrupting customer access to mobile and internet services.
"The cyberattack on Ukraine's #Kyivstar telecoms operator has impacted all regions of the country with high impact to the capital, metrics show, with knock-on impacts reported to air raid alert network and banking sector as work continues]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1018 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1018/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1018/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T09:05:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1017 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits ElasticSearch (13 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1017/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1017/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T08:40:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits ElasticSearch. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's Final 2023 Patch Tuesday: 33 Flaws Fixed, Including 4 Critical]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsofts-final-2023-patch-tuesday-33.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsofts-final-2023-patch-tuesday-33.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-13T05:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft released its final set of Patch Tuesday updates for 2023, closing out 33 flaws in its software, making it one of the lightest releases in recent years.
Of the 33 shortcomings, four are rated Critical and 29 are rated Important in severity. The fixes are in addition to 18 flaws Microsoft addressed in its Chromium-based Edge browser since the release of Patch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unveiling the Cyber Threats to Healthcare: Beyond the Myths]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/unveiling-cyber-threats-to-healthcare.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/unveiling-cyber-threats-to-healthcare.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T18:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's begin with a thought-provoking question: among a credit card number, a social security number, and an Electronic Health Record (EHR), which commands the highest price on a dark web forum? 
Surprisingly, it's the EHR, and the difference is stark: according to a study, EHRs can sell for up to $1,000 each, compared to a mere $5 for a credit card number and $1 for a social]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian APT28 Hackers Targeting 13 Nations in Ongoing Cyber Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-apt28-hackers-targeting-13.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-apt28-hackers-targeting-13.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T14:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian nation-state threat actor known as APT28 has been observed making use of lures related to the ongoing Israel-Hamas war to facilitate the delivery of a custom backdoor called HeadLace.
IBM X-Force is tracking the adversary under the name ITG05, which is also known as BlueDelta, Fancy Bear, Forest Blizzard (formerly Strontium), FROZENLAKE, Iron Twilight, Sednit, Sofacy, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1016 : Vulnérabilité dans Xen (12 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1016/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1016/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:45:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte Xen. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1015 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (12 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1015/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1015/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T12:28:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Non-Human Access is the Path of Least Resistance: A 2023 Recap]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/non-human-access-is-path-of-least.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/non-human-access-is-path-of-least.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 has seen its fair share of cyber attacks, however there’s one attack vector that proves to be more prominent than others - non-human access. With 11 high-profile attacks in 13 months and an ever-growing ungoverned attack surface, non-human identities are the new perimeter, and 2023 is only the beginning. 
Why non-human access is a cybercriminal’s paradise 
People always]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New MrAnon Stealer Malware Targeting German Users via Booking-Themed Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-mranon-stealer-targeting-german-it.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-mranon-stealer-targeting-german-it.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A phishing campaign has been observed delivering an information stealer malware called MrAnon Stealer to unsuspecting victims via seemingly benign booking-themed PDF lures.
"This malware is a Python-based information stealer compressed with cx-Freeze to evade detection," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researcher Cara Lin said. "MrAnon Stealer steals its victims' credentials, system]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1014 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider (12 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1014/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1014/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T08:47:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1013 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (12 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1013/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1013/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T08:34:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases Security Updates to Patch Critical iOS and macOS Security Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/apple-releases-security-updates-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/apple-releases-security-updates-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T06:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple on Monday released security patches for iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, watchOS, and Safari web browser to address multiple security flaws, in addition to backporting fixes for two recently disclosed zero-days to older devices.
This includes updates for 12 security vulnerabilities in iOS and iPadOS spanning AVEVideoEncoder, ExtensionKit, Find My, ImageIO, Kernel, Safari]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Critical RCE Vulnerability Discovered in Apache Struts 2 - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-critical-rce-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-critical-rce-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-12T05:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apache has released a security advisory warning of a critical security flaw in the Struts 2 open-source web application framework that could result in remote code execution.
Tracked as CVE-2023-50164, the vulnerability is rooted in a flawed "file upload logic" that could enable unauthorized path traversal and could be exploited under the circumstances to upload a malicious file]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Unmask Sandman APT's Hidden Link to China-Based KEYPLUG Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/researchers-unmask-sandman-apts-hidden.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/researchers-unmask-sandman-apts-hidden.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tactical and targeting overlaps have been discovered between the enigmatic advanced persistent threat (APT) called Sandman and a China-based threat cluster that's known to use a backdoor known as KEYPLUG.
The assessment comes jointly from SentinelOne, PwC, and the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team based on the fact that the adversary's Lua-based malware LuaDream and KEYPLUG have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Group Using Log4j Exploits to Deploy Remote Access Trojans]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/lazarus-group-using-log4j-exploits-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/lazarus-group-using-log4j-exploits-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious North Korea-linked threat actor known as the Lazarus Group has been attributed to a new global campaign that involves the opportunistic exploitation of security flaws in Log4j to deploy previously undocumented remote access trojans (RATs) on compromised hosts.
Cisco Talos is tracking the activity under the name Operation Blacksmith, noting the use of three DLang-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1012 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans LibreOffice (11 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1012/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1012/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T12:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans LibreOffice. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Playbook: Your First 100 Days as a vCISO - 5 Steps to Success]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/playbook-your-first-100-days-as-vciso-5.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/playbook-your-first-100-days-as-vciso-5.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T11:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an increasingly digital world, no organization is spared from cyber threats. Yet, not every organization has the luxury of hiring a full-time, in-house CISO. This gap in cybersecurity leadership is where you, as a vCISO, come in. You are the person who will establish, develop, and solidify the organization's cybersecurity infrastructure, blending strategic guidance with actionable]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar — Psychology of Social Engineering: Decoding the Mind of a Cyber Attacker]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/webinar-psychology-of-social.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/webinar-psychology-of-social.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the ever-evolving cybersecurity landscape, one method stands out for its chilling effectiveness – social engineering. But why does it work so well? The answer lies in the intricate dance between the attacker's mind and human psychology.
Our upcoming webinar, "Think Like a Hacker, Defend Like a Pro," highlights this alarming trend. We delve deep into social engineering, exploring its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1011 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (11 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1011/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1011/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T10:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1010 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (11 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1010/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1010/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T10:20:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-ACT-053 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2023-ACT-053 (11 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-053/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-053/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T09:11:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SpyLoan Scandal: 18 Malicious Loan Apps Defraud Millions of Android Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/spyloan-scandal-18-malicious-loan-apps.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/spyloan-scandal-18-malicious-loan-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T07:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered 18 malicious loan apps for Android on the Google Play Store that have been collectively downloaded over 12 million times.
"Despite their attractive appearance, these services are in fact designed to defraud users by offering them high-interest-rate loans endorsed with deceitful descriptions, all while collecting their victims' personal and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PoolParty Process Injection Techniques Outsmart Top EDR Solutions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-poolparty-process-injection.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-poolparty-process-injection.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-11T05:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new collection of eight process injection techniques, collectively dubbed PoolParty, could be exploited to achieve code execution in Windows systems while evading endpoint detection and response (EDR) systems.
SafeBreach researcher Alon Leviev said the methods are "capable of working across all processes without any limitations, making them more flexible than existing process]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SLAM Attack: New Spectre-based Vulnerability Impacts Intel, AMD, and Arm CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/slam-attack-new-spectre-based.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/slam-attack-new-spectre-based.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T11:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers from the Vrije Universiteit Amsterdam have disclosed a new side-channel attack called SLAM that could be exploited to leak sensitive information from kernel memory on current and upcoming CPUs from Intel, AMD, and Arm.
The attack is an end-to-end exploit for Spectre based on a new feature in Intel CPUs called Linear Address Masking (LAM) as well as its analogous]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Unveal GuLoader Malware's Latest Anti-Analysis Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/researchers-unveal-guloader-malwares.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/researchers-unveal-guloader-malwares.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-09T07:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have unmasked the latest tricks adopted by a malware strain called GuLoader in an effort to make analysis more challenging.
"While GuLoader's core functionality hasn't changed drastically over the past few years, these constant updates in their obfuscation techniques make analyzing GuLoader a time-consuming and resource-intensive process," Elastic Security Labs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 5G Modems Flaws Affect iOS Devices and Android Models from Major Brands]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-5g-modems-flaws-affect-ios-devices.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-5g-modems-flaws-affect-ios-devices.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A collection of security flaws in the firmware implementation of 5G mobile network modems from major chipset vendors such as MediaTek and Qualcomm impact USB and IoT modems as well as hundreds of smartphone models running Android and iOS.
Of the 14 flaws – collectively called 5Ghoul (a combination of "5G" and "Ghoul") – 10 affect 5G modems from the two companies, out of which three]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean Kimsuky Targeting South Korean Research Institutes with Backdoor Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/n-korean-kimsuky-targeting-south-korean.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/n-korean-kimsuky-targeting-south-korean.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korean threat actor known as Kimsuky has been observed targeting research institutes in South Korea as part of a spear-phishing campaign with the ultimate goal of distributing backdoors on compromised systems.
"The threat actor ultimately uses a backdoor to steal information and execute commands," the AhnLab Security Emergency Response Center (ASEC) said in an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1009 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (08 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1009/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1009/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1008 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (08 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1008/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1008/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1007 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (08 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1007/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1007/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T12:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware-as-a-Service: The Growing Threat You Can't Ignore]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/ransomware-as-service-growing-threat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/ransomware-as-service-growing-threat.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks have become a significant and pervasive threat in the ever-evolving realm of cybersecurity. Among the various iterations of ransomware, one trend that has gained prominence is Ransomware-as-a-Service (RaaS). This alarming development has transformed the cybercrime landscape, enabling individuals with limited technical expertise to carry out devastating attacks.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1006 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (08 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1006/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1006/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T10:05:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données .]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mac Users Beware: New Trojan-Proxy Malware Spreading via Pirated Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/mac-users-beware-new-trojan-proxy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/mac-users-beware-new-trojan-proxy.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unauthorized websites distributing trojanized versions of cracked software have been found to infect Apple macOS users with a new Trojan-Proxy malware.
"Attackers can use this type of malware to gain money by building a proxy server network or to perform criminal acts on behalf of the victim: to launch attacks on websites, companies and individuals, buy guns, drugs, and other illicit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Releases Update 6.4.2 to Address Critical Remote Attack Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/wordpress-releases-update-642-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/wordpress-releases-update-642-to.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress has released version 6.4.2 with a patch for a critical security flaw that could be exploited by threat actors by combining it with another bug to execute arbitrary PHP code on vulnerable sites.
"A remote code execution vulnerability that is not directly exploitable in core; however, the security team feels that there is a potential for high severity when combined with some plugins,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Founder of Bitzlato Cryptocurrency Exchange Pleads Guilty in Money-Laundering Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/founder-of-bitzlato-cryptocurrency.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/founder-of-bitzlato-cryptocurrency.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-08T05:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian founder of the now-defunct Bitzlato cryptocurrency exchange has pleaded guilty, nearly 11 months after he was arrested in Miami earlier this year.
Anatoly Legkodymov (aka Anatolii Legkodymov, Gandalf, and Tolik), according to the U.S. Justice Department, admitted to operating an unlicensed money-transmitting business that enabled other criminal actors to launder their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of COLDRIVER's Evolving Evading and Credential-Stealing Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-coldrivers-evolving.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-coldrivers-evolving.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T14:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as COLDRIVER has continued to engage in credential theft activities against entities that are of strategic interests to Russia while simultaneously improving its detection evasion capabilities.
The Microsoft Threat Intelligence team is tracking under the cluster as Star Blizzard (formerly SEABORGIUM). It's also called Blue Callisto, BlueCharlie (or TAG-53),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Bluetooth Flaw Let Hackers Take Over Android, Linux, macOS, and iOS Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-bluetooth-flaw-let-hackers-take.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-bluetooth-flaw-let-hackers-take.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T11:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical Bluetooth security flaw could be exploited by threat actors to take control of Android, Linux, macOS and iOS devices.
Tracked as CVE-2023-45866, the issue relates to a case of authentication bypass that enables attackers to connect to susceptible devices and inject keystrokes to achieve code execution as the victim.
"Multiple Bluetooth stacks have authentication bypass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacking the Human Mind: Exploiting Vulnerabilities in the 'First Line of Cyber Defense']]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hacking-human-mind-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hacking-human-mind-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Humans are complex beings with consciousness, emotions, and the capacity to act based on thoughts. In the ever-evolving realm of cybersecurity, humans consistently remain primary targets for attackers. Over the years, these attackers have developed their expertise in exploiting various human qualities, sharpening their skills to manipulate biases and emotional triggers with the objective of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1005 : Vulnérabilité dans Apache Struts 2 (07 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1005/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1005/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T11:37:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Apache Struts 2. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building a Robust Threat Intelligence with Wazuh]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/building-robust-threat-intelligence.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/building-robust-threat-intelligence.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat intelligence refers to gathering, processing, and analyzing cyber threats, along with proactive defensive measures aimed at strengthening security. It enables organizations to gain a comprehensive insight into historical, present, and anticipated threats, providing context about the constantly evolving threat landscape.
Importance of threat intelligence in the cybersecurity ecosystem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Governments May Spy on You by Requesting Push Notifications from Apple and Google]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/governments-may-spy-on-you-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/governments-may-spy-on-you-by.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unspecified governments have demanded mobile push notification records from Apple and Google users to pursue people of interest, according to U.S. Senator Ron Wyden.
"Push notifications are alerts sent by phone apps to users' smartphones," Wyden said.
"These alerts pass through a digital post office run by the phone operating system provider -- overwhelmingly Apple or Google. Because of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1004 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nagios XI (07 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1004/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1004/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T09:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nagios XI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1003 : Vulnérabilité dans WordPress (07 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1003/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1003/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T09:46:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans WordPress. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1002 : Vulnérabilité dans MISP (07 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1002/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1002/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T09:41:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MISP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Stealthy 'Krasue' Linux Trojan Targeting Telecom Firms in Thailand]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-stealthy-krasue-linux-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-stealthy-krasue-linux-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown Linux remote access trojan called Krasue has been observed targeting telecom companies in Thailand by threat actors to main covert access to victim networks at lease since 2021.
Named after a nocturnal female spirit of Southeast Asian folklore, the malware is "able to conceal its own presence during the initialization phase," Group-IB said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Launches Default End-to-End Encryption for Chats and Calls on Messenger]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/meta-launches-default-end-to-end.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/meta-launches-default-end-to-end.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-07T05:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has officially begun to roll out support for end-to-end encryption (E2EE) in Messenger for personal calls and one-to-one personal messages by default in what it called the "most significant milestone yet."
"This isn't a routine security update: we rebuilt the app from the ground up, in close consultation with privacy and safety experts," Loredana Crisan, vice president of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1001 : Vulnérabilité dans Atlassian Confluence (06 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1001/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1001/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:57:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Atlassian Confluence. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-1000 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Progress MOVEit Transfer (06 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1000/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-1000/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:43:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Progress MOVEit <span class="uiOutputText" data-aura-rendered-by="9:485;a" …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Threat Actors Can Leverage AWS STS to Infiltrate Cloud Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/alert-threat-actors-can-leverage-aws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/alert-threat-actors-can-leverage-aws.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors can take advantage of Amazon Web Services Security Token Service (AWS STS) as a way to infiltrate cloud accounts and conduct follow-on attacks.
The service enables threat actors to impersonate user identities and roles in cloud environments, Red Canary researchers Thomas Gardner and Cody Betsworth said in a Tuesday analysis.
AWS STS is a web service that enables]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0999 : Vulnérabilité dans ElasticSearch pour Hadoop (06 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0999/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0999/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T13:34:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans ElasticSearch pour Hadoop. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Report: Unveiling the Threat of Malicious Browser Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-report-unveiling-threat-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-report-unveiling-threat-of.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compromising the browser is a high-return target for adversaries. Browser extensions, which are small software modules that are added to the browser and can enhance browsing experiences, have become a popular browser attack vector. This is because they are widely adopted among users and can easily turn malicious through developer actions or attacks on legitimate extensions.
Recent incidents like]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sierra:21 - Flaws in Sierra Wireless Routers Expose Critical Sectors to Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/sierra21-flaws-in-sierra-wireless.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/sierra21-flaws-in-sierra-wireless.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A collection of 21 security flaws have been discovered in Sierra Wireless AirLink cellular routers and open-source software components like TinyXML and OpenNDS.
Collectively tracked as Sierra:21, the issues expose over 86,000 devices across critical sectors like energy, healthcare, waste management, retail, emergency services, and vehicle tracking to cyber threats, according]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0998 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (06 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0998/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0998/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T11:13:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0997 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Serv-U (06 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0997/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0997/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:43:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Serv-U. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Scaling Security Operations with Automation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/scaling-security-operations-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/scaling-security-operations-with.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an increasingly complex and fast-paced digital landscape, organizations strive to protect themselves from various security threats. However, limited resources often hinder security teams when combatting these threats, making it difficult to keep up with the growing number of security incidents and alerts. Implementing automation throughout security operations helps security teams alleviate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploited ColdFusion Vulnerability to Breach Federal Agency Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-exploited-coldfusion.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/hackers-exploited-coldfusion.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) warned of active exploitation of a high-severity Adobe ColdFusion vulnerability by unidentified threat actors to gain initial access to government servers.
"The vulnerability in ColdFusion (CVE-2023-26360) presents as an improper access control issue and exploitation of this CVE can result in arbitrary code execution,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Releases Critical Software Fixes to Prevent Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/atlassian-releases-critical-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/atlassian-releases-critical-software.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T09:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian has released software fixes to address four critical flaws in its software that, if successfully exploited, could result in remote code execution.
The list of vulnerabilities is below -

CVE-2022-1471 (CVSS score: 9.8) - Deserialization vulnerability in SnakeYAML library that can lead to remote code execution in multiple products
CVE-2023-22522 (CVSS score]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Releases Details on Chip Vulnerabilities Exploited in Targeted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/qualcomm-releases-details-on-chip.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/qualcomm-releases-details-on-chip.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-06T05:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chipmaker Qualcomm has released more information about three high-severity security flaws that it said came under "limited, targeted exploitation" back in October 2023.
The vulnerabilities are as follows -

CVE-2023-33063 (CVSS score: 7.8) - Memory corruption in DSP Services during a remote call from HLOS to DSP.
CVE-2023-33106 (CVSS score: 8.4) - Memory corruption in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning for iPhone Users: Experts Warn of Sneaky Fake Lockdown Mode Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/warning-for-iphone-users-experts-warn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/warning-for-iphone-users-experts-warn.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new "post-exploitation tampering technique" can be abused by malicious actors to visually deceive a target into believing that their Apple iPhone is running in Lockdown Mode when it's actually not and carry out covert attacks.
The novel, detailed by Jamf Threat Labs in a report shared with The Hacker News, "shows that if a hacker has already infiltrated your device, they can cause]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia's AI-Powered Disinformation Operation Targeting Ukraine, US, and Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russias-ai-powered-disinformation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russias-ai-powered-disinformation.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russia-linked influence operation called Doppelganger has targeted Ukrainian, U.S., and German audiences through a combination of inauthentic news sites and social media accounts.
These campaigns are designed to amplify content designed to undermine Ukraine as well as propagate anti-LGBTQ+ sentiment, U.S. military competence, and Germany's economic and social issues, according to a new]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0996 : Vulnérabilité dans TheGreenBow VPN Client (05 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0996/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0996/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T12:13:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans TheGreenBow VPN Client. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Security: Preventing Microsoft Copilot Data Exposure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/generative-ai-security-preventing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/generative-ai-security-preventing.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Copilot has been called one of the most powerful productivity tools on the planet.
Copilot is an AI assistant that lives inside each of your Microsoft 365 apps — Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Teams, Outlook, and so on. Microsoft's dream is to take the drudgery out of daily work and let humans focus on being creative problem-solvers.
What makes Copilot a different beast than ChatGPT and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[15,000 Go Module Repositories on GitHub Vulnerable to Repojacking Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/15000-go-module-repositories-on-github.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/15000-go-module-repositories-on-github.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T10:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research has found that over 15,000 Go module repositories on GitHub are vulnerable to an attack called repojacking.
"More than 9,000 repositories are vulnerable to repojacking due to GitHub username changes," Jacob Baines, chief technology officer at VulnCheck, said in a report shared with The Hacker News. "More than 6,000 repositories were vulnerable to repojacking due to account]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0995 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android (05 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0995/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0995/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T09:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-AVI-0994 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans SonicWall SMA (05 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0994/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2023-AVI-0994/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T09:14:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SonicWall SMA. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Threat Actor 'AeroBlade' Emerges in Espionage Attack on U.S. Aerospace]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-threat-actor-aeroblade-emerges-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-threat-actor-aeroblade-emerges-in.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T07:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat actor has been linked to a cyber attack targeting an aerospace organization in the U.S. as part of what's suspected to be a cyber espionage mission.
The BlackBerry Threat Research and Intelligence team is tracking the activity cluster as AeroBlade. Its origin is currently unknown and it's not clear if the attack was successful.
"The actor used spear-phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Kremlin-Backed APT28 Exploiting Critical Outlook Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-kremlin-backed-apt28.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-kremlin-backed-apt28.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-05T06:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Monday said it detected Kremlin-backed nation-state activity exploiting a critical security flaw in its Outlook email service to gain unauthorized access to victims' accounts within Exchange servers.
The tech giant attributed the intrusions to a threat actor it called Forest Blizzard (formerly Strontium), which is also widely tracked under the monikers APT28,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New BLUFFS Bluetooth Attack Expose Devices to Adversary-in-the-Middle Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-bluffs-bluetooth-attack-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-bluffs-bluetooth-attack-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research has unearthed multiple novel attacks that break Bluetooth Classic's forward secrecy and future secrecy guarantees, resulting in adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) scenarios between two already connected peers.
The issues, collectively named BLUFFS, impact Bluetooth Core Specification 4.2 through 5.4. They are tracked under the identifier CVE-2023-24023 (CVSS score: 6.8)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Make a Fresh Start for 2024: Clean Out Your User Inventory to Reduce SaaS Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/make-fresh-start-for-2024-clean-out.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/make-fresh-start-for-2024-clean-out.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As work ebbs with the typical end-of-year slowdown, now is a good time to review user roles and privileges and remove anyone who shouldn’t have access as well as trim unnecessary permissions. In addition to saving some unnecessary license fees, a clean user inventory significantly enhances the security of your SaaS applications. From reducing risk to protecting against data leakage, here is how]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New P2PInfect Botnet MIPS Variant Targeting Routers and IoT Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-p2pinfect-botnet-mips-variant.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/new-p2pinfect-botnet-mips-variant.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new variant of an emerging botnet called P2PInfect that's capable of targeting routers and IoT devices.
The latest version, per Cado Security Labs, is compiled for Microprocessor without Interlocked Pipelined Stages (MIPS) architecture, broadening its capabilities and reach.
"It's highly likely that by targeting MIPS, the P2PInfect developers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2023-ACT-052 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2023-ACT-052 (04 décembre 2023)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-052/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2023-ACT-052/"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T09:17:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LogoFAIL: UEFI Vulnerabilities Expose Devices to Stealth Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/logofail-uefi-vulnerabilities-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/logofail-uefi-vulnerabilities-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) code from various independent firmware/BIOS vendors (IBVs) has been found vulnerable to potential attacks through high-impact flaws in image parsing libraries embedded into the firmware.
The shortcomings, collectively labeled LogoFAIL by Binarly, "can be used by threat actors to deliver a malicious payload and bypass Secure Boot, Intel]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Malvertising Scheme Spreading CACTUS Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-malvertising-scheme.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/microsoft-warns-of-malvertising-scheme.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-04T04:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has warned of a new wave of CACTUS ransomware attacks that leverage malvertising lures to deploy DanaBot as an initial access vector.
The DanaBot infections led to "hands-on-keyboard activity by ransomware operator Storm-0216 (Twisted Spider, UNC2198), culminating in the deployment of CACTUS ransomware," the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team said in a series of posts on X (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agent Racoon Backdoor Targets Organizations in Middle East, Africa, and U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/agent-racoon-backdoor-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/agent-racoon-backdoor-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T08:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations in the Middle East, Africa, and the U.S. have been targeted by an unknown threat actor to distribute a new backdoor called Agent Racoon.
"This malware family is written using the .NET framework and leverages the domain name service (DNS) protocol to create a covert channel and provide different backdoor functionalities," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 researcher Chema Garcia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacker Vladimir Dunaev Convicted for Creating TrickBot Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-hacker-vladimir-dunaev.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/12/russian-hacker-vladimir-dunaev.html"/>
        <updated>2023-12-02T07:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian national has been found guilty in connection with his role in developing and deploying a malware known as TrickBot, the U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) announced.
Vladimir Dunaev, 40, was arrested in South Korea in September 2021 and extradited to the U.S. a month later.
"Dunaev developed browser modifications and malicious tools that aided in credential harvesting and data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>