<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-10-22T20:14:03.268Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gophish Framework Used in Phishing Campaigns to Deploy Remote Access Trojans]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/gophish-framework-used-in-phishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/gophish-framework-used-in-phishing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T17:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-speaking users have become the target of a new phishing campaign that leverages an open-source phishing toolkit called Gophish to deliver DarkCrystal RAT (aka DCRat) and a previously undocumented remote access trojan dubbed PowerRAT.
"The campaign involves modular infection chains that are either Maldoc or HTML-based infections and require the victim's intervention to trigger the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Security Flaw in Styra's OPA Exposes NTLM Hashes to Remote Attackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/security-flaw-in-styras-opa-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/security-flaw-in-styras-opa-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a now-patched security flaw in Styra's Open Policy Agent (OPA) that, if successfully exploited, could have led to leakage of New Technology LAN Manager (NTLM) hashes.
"The vulnerability could have allowed an attacker to leak the NTLM credentials of the OPA server's local user account to a remote server, potentially allowing the attacker to relay the authentication or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploiting Docker API Servers for SRBMiner Crypto Mining Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cybercriminals-exploiting-docker-api.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cybercriminals-exploiting-docker-api.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bad actors have been observed targeting Docker remote API servers to deploy the SRBMiner crypto miner on compromised instances, according to new findings from Trend Micro.
"In this attack, the threat actor used the gRPC protocol over h2c to evade security solutions and execute their crypto mining operations on the Docker host," researchers Abdelrahman Esmail and Sunil Bharti said in a technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Moxa (22 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0911/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0911/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T11:15:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Moxa. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Comprehensive Guide to Finding Service Accounts in Active Directory]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/a-comprehensive-guide-to-finding.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/a-comprehensive-guide-to-finding.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Service accounts are vital in any enterprise, running automated processes like managing applications or scripts. However, without proper monitoring, they can pose a significant security risk due to their elevated privileges. This guide will walk you through how to locate and secure these accounts within Active Directory (AD), and explore how Silverfort’s solutions can help enhance your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bumblebee and Latrodectus Malware Return with Sophisticated Phishing Strategies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/bumblebee-and-latrodectus-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/bumblebee-and-latrodectus-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two malware families that suffered setbacks in the aftermath of a coordinated law enforcement operation called Endgame have resurfaced as part of new phishing campaigns.
Bumblebee and Latrodectus, which are both malware loaders, are designed to steal personal data, along with downloading and executing additional payloads onto compromised hosts.
Tracked under the names BlackWidow, IceNova, Lotus,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB (22 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0910/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0910/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T09:47:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Target Developers' Ethereum Wallets with SSH Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/malicious-npm-packages-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/malicious-npm-packages-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T09:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a number of suspicious packages published to the npm registry that are designed to harvest Ethereum private keys and gain remote access to the machine via the secure shell (SSH) protocol.
The packages attempt to "gain SSH access to the victim's machine by writing the attacker’s SSH public key in the root user’s authorized_keys file," software supply]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Releases vCenter Server Update to Fix Critical RCE Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/vmware-releases-vcenter-server-update.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/vmware-releases-vcenter-server-update.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released software updates to address an already patched security flaw in vCenter Server that could pave the way for remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38812 (CVSS score: 9.8), concerns a case of heap-overflow vulnerability in the implementation of the DCE/RPC protocol.
"A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Adds ScienceLogic SL1 Vulnerability to Exploited Catalog After Active Zero-Day Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-adds-sciencelogic-sl1.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-adds-sciencelogic-sl1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T04:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday added a critical security flaw impacting ScienceLogic SL1 to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, following reports of active exploitation as a zero-day.
The vulnerability in question, tracked as CVE-2024-9537 (CVSS v4 score: 9.3), refers to a bug involving an unspecified third-party component that could]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exploitations de vulnérabilités dans Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance (CSA) (22 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-013/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-013/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-22T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti a publié plusieurs avis de sécurité sur des vulnérabilités affectant CSA qui sont activement exploitées : * le 10 septembre 2024, Ivanti a publié un avis de sécurité concernant la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-8190 qui permet à un attaquant, authentifié en tant qu'administrateur, d'exécuter du...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-046 (21 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-046/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-046/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Nation-State Hackers APT41 Hit Gambling Sector for Financial Gain]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/chinese-nation-state-hackers-apt41-hit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/chinese-nation-state-hackers-apt41-hit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The prolific Chinese nation-state actor known as APT41 (aka Brass Typhoon, Earth Baku, Wicked Panda, or Winnti) has been attributed to a sophisticated cyber attack targeting the gambling and gaming industry.
"Over a period of at least six months, the attackers stealthily gathered valuable information from the targeted company including, but not limited to, network configurations, user passwords,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Synology (21 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0909/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0909/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T12:07:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Synology. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (21 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0908/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0908/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T12:06:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Guide:  The Ultimate Pentest Checklist for Full-Stack Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/guide-ultimate-pentest-checklist-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/guide-ultimate-pentest-checklist-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pentest Checklists Are More Important Than Ever
Given the expanding attack surface coupled with the increasing sophistication of attacker tactics and techniques, penetration testing checklists have become essential for ensuring thorough assessments across an organization’s attack surface, both internal and external. By providing a structured approach, these checklists help testers systematically]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Top Threats, Tools and News (Oct 14 - Oct 20)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats_21.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats_21.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hi there! Here’s your quick update on the latest in cybersecurity.
Hackers are using new tricks to break into systems we thought were secure—like finding hidden doors in locked houses. But the good news? Security experts are fighting back with smarter tools to keep data safe.
Some big companies were hit with attacks, while others fixed their vulnerabilities just in time. It's a constant battle.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Discover Severe Security Flaws in Major E2EE Cloud Storage Providers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-discover-severe-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-discover-severe-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-21T06:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered severe cryptographic issues in various end-to-end encrypted (E2EE) cloud storage platforms that could be exploited to leak sensitive data.
"The vulnerabilities range in severity: in many cases a malicious server can inject files, tamper with file data, and even gain direct access to plaintext," ETH Zurich researchers Jonas Hofmann and Kien Tuong Truong]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Roundcube Webmail XSS Vulnerability to Steal Login Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/hackers-exploit-roundcube-webmail-xss.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/hackers-exploit-roundcube-webmail-xss.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-20T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unknown threat actors have been observed attempting to exploit a now-patched security flaw in the open-source Roundcube webmail software as part of a phishing attack designed to steal user credentials.
Russian cybersecurity company Positive Technologies said it discovered last month that an email was sent to an unspecified governmental organization located in one of the Commonwealth of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Acronym Overdose – Navigating the Complex Data Security Landscape]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/acronym-overdose-navigating-complex.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/acronym-overdose-navigating-complex.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the modern enterprise, data security is often discussed using a complex lexicon of acronyms—DLP, DDR, DSPM, and many others. While these acronyms represent critical frameworks, architectures, and tools for protecting sensitive information, they can also overwhelm those trying to piece together an effective security strategy. This article aims to demystify some of the most important acronyms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypt Ghouls Targets Russian Firms with LockBit 3.0 and Babuk Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/crypt-ghouls-targets-russian-firms-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/crypt-ghouls-targets-russian-firms-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-19T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A nascent threat actor known as Crypt Ghouls has been linked to a set of cyber attacks targeting Russian businesses and government agencies with ransomware with the twin goals of disrupting business operations and financial gain.
"The group under review has a toolkit that includes utilities such as Mimikatz, XenAllPasswordPro, PingCastle, Localtonet, resocks, AnyDesk, PsExec, and others,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean IT Workers in Western Firms Now Demanding Ransom for Stolen Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-it-workers-in-western.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-it-workers-in-western.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean information technology (IT) workers who obtain employment under false identities in Western companies are not only stealing intellectual property, but are also stepping up by demanding ransoms in order to not leak it, marking a new twist to their financially motivated attacks.
"In some instances, fraudulent workers demanded ransom payments from their former employers after gaining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0907/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0907/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:04:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0906/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0906/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T12:00:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0905/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0905/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:55:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Foxit PDF Editor (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0904/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0904/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans FoxIT PDF Editor. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate DSPM Guide: Webinar on Building a Strong Data Security Posture]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-ultimate-dspm-guide-webinar-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-ultimate-dspm-guide-webinar-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Picture your company's data as a vast, complex jigsaw puzzle—scattered across clouds, devices, and networks. Some pieces are hidden, some misplaced, and others might even be missing entirely. Keeping your data secure in today’s fast-evolving landscape can feel like an impossible challenge.
But there’s a game-changing solution: Data Security Posture Management (DSPM). Think of it as a high-tech,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. and Allies Warn of Iranian Cyberattacks on Critical Infrastructure in Year-Long Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-and-allies-warn-of-iranian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-and-allies-warn-of-iranian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity and intelligence agencies from Australia, Canada, and the U.S. have warned about a year-long campaign undertaken by Iranian cyber actors to infiltrate critical infrastructure organizations via brute-force attacks.
"Since October 2023, Iranian actors have used brute force and password spraying to compromise user accounts and obtain access to organizations in the healthcare and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Fake Google Meet Pages Deliver Infostealers in Ongoing ClickFix Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/beware-fake-google-meet-pages-deliver.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/beware-fake-google-meet-pages-deliver.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are leveraging fake Google Meet web pages as part of an ongoing malware campaign dubbed ClickFix to deliver infostealers targeting Windows and macOS systems.
"This tactic involves displaying fake error messages in web browsers to deceive users into copying and executing a given malicious PowerShell code, finally infecting their systems," French cybersecurity company Sekoia said in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0903/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0903/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:34:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0902/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0902/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:09:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0901/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0901/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T06:02:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Spring Framework (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0900/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0900/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:53:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Spring Framework. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (18 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0899/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0899/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:48:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Reveals macOS Vulnerability that Bypasses Privacy Controls in Safari Browser]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-reveals-macos-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-reveals-macos-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-18T05:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has disclosed details about a now-patched security flaw in Apple's Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) framework in macOS that has likely come under exploitation to get around a user's privacy preferences and access data.
The shortcoming, codenamed HM Surf by the tech giant, is tracked as CVE-2024-44133. It was addressed by Apple as part of macOS Sequoia 15 by removing the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian RomCom Attacks Target Ukrainian Government with New SingleCamper RAT Variant]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/russian-romcom-attacks-target-ukrainian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/russian-romcom-attacks-target-ukrainian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian threat actor known as RomCom has been linked to a new wave of cyber attacks aimed at Ukrainian government agencies and unknown Polish entities since at least late 2023.
The intrusions are characterized by the use of a variant of the RomCom RAT dubbed SingleCamper (aka SnipBot or RomCom 5.0), said Cisco Talos, which is monitoring the activity cluster under the moniker UAT-5647.
"This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Cicada3301 Ransomware Operations and Its Affiliate Program]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cross-platform-cicada3301-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cross-platform-cicada3301-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T13:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have gleaned additional insights into a nascent ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) called Cicada3301 after successfully gaining access to the group's affiliate panel on the dark web.
Singapore-headquartered Group-IB said it contacted the threat actor behind the Cicada3301 persona on the RAMP cybercrime forum via the Tox messaging service after the latter put out an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Ways to Reduce SaaS Security Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/5-ways-to-reduce-saas-security-risks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/5-ways-to-reduce-saas-security-risks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As technology adoption has shifted to be employee-led, just in time, and from any location or device, IT and security teams have found themselves contending with an ever-sprawling SaaS attack surface, much of which is often unknown or unmanaged. This greatly increases the risk of identity-based threats, and according to a recent report from CrowdStrike, 80% of breaches today use compromised]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SideWinder APT Strikes Middle East and Africa With Stealthy Multi-Stage Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/sidewinder-apt-strikes-middle-east-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/sidewinder-apt-strikes-middle-east-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An advanced persistent threat (APT) actor with suspected ties to India has sprung forth with a flurry of attacks against high-profile entities and strategic infrastructures in the Middle East and Africa.
The activity has been attributed to a group tracked as SideWinder, which is also known as APT-C-17, Baby Elephant, Hardcore Nationalist, Leafperforator, Rattlesnake, Razor Tiger, and T-APT-04.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Charges Two Sudanese Brothers for Record 35,000 DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-charges-two-sudanese-brothers-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-charges-two-sudanese-brothers-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T09:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Federal prosecutors in the U.S. have charged two Sudanese brothers with running a distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) botnet for hire that conducted a record 35,000 DDoS attacks in a single year, including those that targeted Microsoft's services in June 2023.
The attacks, which were facilitated by Anonymous Sudan's "powerful DDoS tool," singled out critical infrastructure, corporate networks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Pixel (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0898/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0898/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:11:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Pixel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0897/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0897/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:06:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans VMware HCX (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0896/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0896/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T06:00:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware HCX. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0895/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0895/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:56:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Drupal Core (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0894/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0894/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:51:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité ont été découverte dans Drupal Core. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits F5 (17 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0893/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0893/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:43:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits F5. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Kubernetes Image Builder Vulnerability Exposes Nodes to Root Access Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-kubernetes-image-builder.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-kubernetes-image-builder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-17T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the Kubernetes Image Builder that, if successfully exploited, could be abused to gain root access under certain circumstances.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-9486 (CVSS score: 9.8), has been addressed in version 0.1.38. The project maintainers acknowledged Nicolai Rybnikar for discovering and reporting the vulnerability.
"A security issue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Abuse EDRSilencer Tool to Bypass Security and Hide Malicious Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/hackers-abuse-edrsilencer-tool-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/hackers-abuse-edrsilencer-tool-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T16:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are attempting to abuse the open-source EDRSilencer tool as part of efforts to tamper endpoint detection and response (EDR) solutions and hide malicious activity.
Trend Micro said it detected "threat actors attempting to integrate EDRSilencer in their attacks, repurposing it as a means of evading detection."
EDRSilencer, inspired by the NightHawk FireBlock tool from MDSec, is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIDO Alliance Drafts New Protocol to Simplify Passkey Transfers Across Different Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fido-alliance-drafts-new-protocol-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fido-alliance-drafts-new-protocol-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T13:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FIDO Alliance said it's working to make passkeys and other credentials more easier to export across different providers and improve credential provider interoperability, as more than 12 billion online accounts become accessible with the passwordless sign-in method.
To that end, the alliance said it has published a draft for a new set of specifications for secure credential exchange,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SolarWinds (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0892/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0892/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:12:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SolarWinds. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0891/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0891/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T12:09:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Misuse to Abuse: AI Risks and Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/from-misuse-to-abuse-ai-risks-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/from-misuse-to-abuse-ai-risks-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[AI from the attacker’s perspective: See how cybercriminals are leveraging AI and exploiting its vulnerabilities to compromise systems, users, and even other AI applications
Cybercriminals and AI: The Reality vs. Hype
“AI will not replace humans in the near future. But humans who know how to use AI are going to replace those humans who don't know how to use AI,” says Etay Maor, Chief Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean ScarCruft Exploits Windows Zero-Day to Spread RokRAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-scarcruft-exploits-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-scarcruft-exploits-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korean threat actor known as ScarCruft has been linked to the zero-day exploitation of a now-patched security flaw in Windows to infect devices with malware known as RokRAT.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-38178 (CVSS score: 7.5), a memory corruption bug in the Scripting Engine that could result in remote code execution when using the Edge browser in Internet Explorer Mode.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Techniques for Collecting Cyber Threat Intelligence]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-techniques-for-collecting-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-techniques-for-collecting-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T09:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To defend your organization against cyber threats, you need a clear picture of the current threat landscape. This means constantly expanding your knowledge about new and ongoing threats.
There are many techniques analysts can use to collect crucial cyber threat intelligence. Let’s consider five that can greatly improve your threat investigations.
Pivoting on С2 IP addresses to pinpoint malware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0890/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0890/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T07:43:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ruby on Rails (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0889/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0889/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T07:36:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ruby on Rails. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Astaroth Banking Malware Resurfaces in Brazil via Spear-Phishing Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/astaroth-banking-malware-resurfaces-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/astaroth-banking-malware-resurfaces-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new spear-phishing campaign targeting Brazil has been found delivering a banking malware called Astaroth (aka Guildma) by making use of obfuscated JavaScript to slip past security guardrails.
"The spear-phishing campaign's impact has targeted various industries, with manufacturing companies, retail firms, and government agencies being the most affected," Trend Micro said in a new analysis.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Weblogic (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0888/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0888/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Weblogic. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Systems (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0886/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0886/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Systems. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Virtualization (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0887/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0887/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Virtualization. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle PeopleSoft (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0885/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0885/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle PeopleSoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle MySQL (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0884/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0884/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle MySQL. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Java SE (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0883/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0883/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Java SE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Database Server (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0882/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0882/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:33:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Database Server. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0881/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0881/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:24:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Trend Micro (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0880/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0880/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T06:13:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Trend Micro. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Juniper Networks Junos OS (16 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0879/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0879/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:56:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Juniper Networks June OS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Patches Critical Flaw in Enterprise Server Allowing Unauthorized Instance Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/github-patches-critical-flaw-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/github-patches-critical-flaw-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T05:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has released security updates for Enterprise Server (GHES) to address multiple issues, including a critical bug that could allow unauthorized access to an instance.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-9487, carries a CVS score of 9.5 out of a maximum of 10.0
"An attacker could bypass SAML single sign-on (SSO) authentication with the optional encrypted assertions feature, allowing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Active Exploitation in SolarWinds Help Desk Software Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-16T04:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Tuesday added a critical security flaw impacting SolarWinds Web Help Desk (WHD) software to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2024-28987 (CVSS score: 9.1), the vulnerability relates to a case of hard-coded credentials that could be abused to gain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrickMo Banking Trojan Can Now Capture Android PINs and Unlock Patterns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/trickmo-banking-trojan-can-now-capture.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/trickmo-banking-trojan-can-now-capture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New variants of an Android banking trojan called TrickMo have been found to harbor previously undocumented features to steal a device's unlock pattern or PIN.
"This new addition enables the threat actor to operate on the device even while it is locked," Zimperium security researcher Aazim Yaswant said in an analysis published last week.
First spotted in the wild in 2019, TrickMo is so named for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Campaign Uses PureCrypter Loader to Deliver DarkVision RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-malware-campaign-uses-purecrypter.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-malware-campaign-uses-purecrypter.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a new malware campaign that leverages a malware loader named PureCrypter to deliver a commodity remote access trojan (RAT) called DarkVision RAT.
The activity, observed by Zscaler ThreatLabz in July 2024, involves a multi-stage process to deliver the RAT payload.
"DarkVision RAT communicates with its command-and-control (C2) server using a custom network]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Variant of FASTCash Malware Targets Payment Switches in ATM Heists]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-linux-variant-of-fastcash-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-linux-variant-of-fastcash-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors have been observed using a Linux variant of a known malware family called FASTCash to steal funds as part of a financially-motivated campaign.
The malware is "installed on payment switches within compromised networks that handle card transactions for the means of facilitating the unauthorized withdrawal of cash from ATMs," a security researcher who goes by HaxRob said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Rise of Zero-Day Vulnerabilities: Why Traditional Security Solutions Fall Short]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/rise-of-zero-day-vulnerabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/rise-of-zero-day-vulnerabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In recent years, the number and sophistication of zero-day vulnerabilities have surged, posing a critical threat to organizations of all sizes. A zero-day vulnerability is a security flaw in software that is unknown to the vendor and remains unpatched at the time of discovery. Attackers exploit these flaws before any defensive measures can be implemented, making zero-days a potent weapon for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China Accuses U.S. of Fabricating Volt Typhoon to Hide Its Own Hacking Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/china-accuses-us-of-fabricating-volt.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/china-accuses-us-of-fabricating-volt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T08:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[China's National Computer Virus Emergency Response Center (CVERC) has doubled down on claims that the threat actor known as the Volt Typhoon is a fabrication of the U.S. and its allies.
The agency, in collaboration with the National Engineering Laboratory for Computer Virus Prevention Technology, went on to accuse the U.S. federal government, intelligence agencies, and Five Eyes countries of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Hijack Loader Malware Using Stolen Code-Signing Certificates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-uncover-hijack-loader.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-uncover-hijack-loader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T06:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a new malware campaign that delivers Hijack Loader artifacts that are signed with legitimate code-signing certificates.
French cybersecurity company HarfangLab, which detected the activity at the start of the month, said the attack chains aim to deploy an information stealer known as Lumma.
Hijack Loader, also known as DOILoader, IDAT Loader, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Splunk (15 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0878/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0878/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:28:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Splunk. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mozilla Firefox (15 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0877/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0877/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T05:16:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mozilla Firefox. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Plugin Jetpack Patches Major Vulnerability Affecting 27 Million Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/wordpress-plugin-jetpack-patches-major.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/wordpress-plugin-jetpack-patches-major.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-15T04:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of the Jetpack WordPress plugin have released a security update to remediate a critical vulnerability that could allow logged-in users to access forms submitted by others on a site.
Jetpack, owned by WordPress maker Automattic, is an all-in-one plugin that offers a comprehensive suite of tools to improve site safety, performance, and traffic growth. It's used on 27 million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (14 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0876/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0876/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T12:02:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (14 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0875/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0875/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T11:51:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-State Attackers Exploiting Ivanti CSA Flaws for Network Infiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/nation-state-attackers-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/nation-state-attackers-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T11:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected nation-state adversary has been observed weaponizing three security flaws in Ivanti Cloud Service Appliance (CSA) a zero-day to perform a series of malicious actions.
That's according to findings from Fortinet FortiGuard Labs, which said the vulnerabilities were abused to gain unauthenticated access to the CSA, enumerate users configured in the appliance, and attempt to access the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Steps to Boost Detection and Response in a Multi-Layered Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-steps-to-boost-detection-and-response.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-steps-to-boost-detection-and-response.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T11:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The link between detection and response (DR) practices and cloud security has historically been weak. As global organizations increasingly adopt cloud environments, security strategies have largely focused on "shift-left" practices—securing code, ensuring proper cloud posture, and fixing misconfigurations. However, this approach has led to an over-reliance on a multitude of DR tools spanning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Supply Chain Attacks Exploit Entry Points in Python, npm, and Open-Source Ecosystems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/supply-chain-attacks-exploit-entry.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/supply-chain-attacks-exploit-entry.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have found that entry points could be abused across multiple programming ecosystems like PyPI, npm, Ruby Gems, NuGet, Dart Pub, and Rust Crates to stage software supply chain attacks.
"Attackers can leverage these entry points to execute malicious code when specific commands are run, posing a widespread risk in the open-source landscape," Checkmarx researchers Yehuda]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Top Threats, Tools and Trends (Oct 7 - Oct 13)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hey there, it's your weekly dose of "what the heck is going on in cybersecurity land" – and trust me, you NEED to be in the loop this time. We've got everything from zero-day exploits and AI gone rogue to the FBI playing crypto kingpin – it's full of stuff they don't 🤫 want you to know.
So let's jump in before we get FOMO.
⚡ Threat of the Week
GoldenJackal Hacks Air-Gapped Systems: Meet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Veeam Vulnerability Exploited to Spread Akira and Fog Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-veeam-vulnerability-exploited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-veeam-vulnerability-exploited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively attempting to exploit a now-patched security flaw in Veeam Backup & Replication to deploy Akira and Fog ransomware.
Cybersecurity vendor Sophos said it has been tracking a series of attacks in the past month leveraging compromised VPN credentials and CVE-2024-40711 to create a local account and deploy the ransomware.
CVE-2024-40711, rated 9.8 out of 10.0 on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-045 (14 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-045/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-045/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-14T08:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OilRig Exploits Windows Kernel Flaw in Espionage Campaign Targeting UAE and Gulf]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/oilrig-exploits-windows-kernel-flaw-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/oilrig-exploits-windows-kernel-flaw-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-13T09:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian threat actor known as OilRig has been observed exploiting a now-patched privilege escalation flaw impacting the Windows Kernel as part of a cyber espionage campaign targeting the U.A.E. and the broader Gulf region.
"The group utilizes sophisticated tactics that include deploying a backdoor that leverages Microsoft Exchange servers for credentials theft, and exploiting vulnerabilities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Creates Fake Cryptocurrency to Expose Widespread Crypto Market Manipulation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fbi-creates-fake-cryptocurrency-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fbi-creates-fake-cryptocurrency-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-12T05:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has announced arrests and charges against several individuals and entities in connection with allegedly manipulating digital asset markets as part of a widespread fraud operation.
The law enforcement action – codenamed Operation Token Mirrors – is the result of the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) taking the "unprecedented step" of creating its own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub, Telegram Bots, and QR Codes Abused in New Wave of Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/github-telegram-bots-and-qr-codes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/github-telegram-bots-and-qr-codes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new tax-themed malware campaign targeting insurance and finance sectors has been observed leveraging GitHub links in phishing email messages as a way to bypass security measures and deliver Remcos RAT, indicating that the method is gaining traction among threat actors.
"In this campaign, legitimate repositories such as the open-source tax filing software, UsTaxes, HMRC, and InlandRevenue were]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0874/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0874/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:58:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0873/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0873/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:58:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian LTS (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0872/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0872/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:58:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian LTS. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0871/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0871/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:55:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0870/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0870/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:55:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mozilla Thunderbird (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0869/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0869/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:52:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mozilla Thunderbird. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance. Mozilla indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-9680 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0868/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0868/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:36:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Hybrid Password Attacks Work and How to Defend Against Them]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/how-hybrid-password-attacks-work-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/how-hybrid-password-attacks-work-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors constantly change tactics to bypass cybersecurity measures, developing innovative methods to steal user credentials. Hybrid password attacks merge multiple cracking techniques to amplify their effectiveness. These combined approaches exploit the strengths of various methods, accelerating the password-cracking process. 
In this post, we’ll explore hybrid attacks — what they are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SonicWall (11 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0867/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0867/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T08:58:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SonicWall. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Threat Actors Exploiting F5 BIG-IP Cookies for Network Reconnaissance]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-threat-actors-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-threat-actors-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T08:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) is warning that it has observed threat actors leveraging unencrypted persistent cookies managed by the F5 BIG-IP Local Traffic Manager (LTM) module to conduct reconnaissance of target networks.
It said the module is being used to enumerate other non-internet-facing devices on the network. The agency, however, did not disclose who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Critical GitLab Vulnerability Could Allow Arbitrary CI/CD Pipeline Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-critical-gitlab-vulnerability-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-critical-gitlab-vulnerability-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab has released security updates for Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE) to address eight security flaws, including a critical bug that could allow running Continuous Integration and Continuous Delivery (CI/CD) pipelines on arbitrary branches.
Tracked as CVE-2024-9164, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.6 out of 10.

"An issue was discovered in GitLab EE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bohemia and Cannabia Dark Web Markets Taken Down After Joint Police Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/bohemia-and-cannabia-dark-web-markets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/bohemia-and-cannabia-dark-web-markets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-11T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dutch police have announced the takedown of Bohemia and Cannabia, which has been described as the world's largest and longest-running dark web market for illegal goods, drugs, and cybercrime services.
The takedown is the result of a collaborative investigation with Ireland, the United Kingdom, and the United States that began towards the end of 2022, the Politie said.
The marketplace]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Blocks 20 Global Malicious Campaigns Using AI for Cybercrime and Disinformation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/openai-blocks-20-global-malicious.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/openai-blocks-20-global-malicious.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T13:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI on Wednesday said it has disrupted more than 20 operations and deceptive networks across the world that attempted to use its platform for malicious purposes since the start of the year.
This activity encompassed debugging malware, writing articles for websites, generating biographies for social media accounts, and creating AI-generated profile pictures for fake accounts on X.
"Threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Juniper Networks (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0866/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0866/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T12:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Warn of Critical Unpatched Vulnerability in Linear eMerge E3 Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/experts-warn-of-critical-unpatched.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/experts-warn-of-critical-unpatched.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T12:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity security researchers are warning about an unpatched vulnerability in Nice Linear eMerge E3 access controller systems that could allow for the execution of arbitrary operating system (OS) commands.
The flaw, assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-9441, carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0, according to VulnCheck.
"A vulnerability in the Nortek Linear eMerge E3 allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mozilla Firefox (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0865/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0865/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:51:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mozilla Firefox. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance. Mozilla indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-9680 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0864/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0864/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:49:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synology DSM (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0863/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0863/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:39:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synology DSM. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0862/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0862/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:15:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Wireshark (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0861/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0861/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Wireshark. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Simple Steps to Eliminate SOC Analyst Burnout]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/6-simple-steps-to-eliminate-soc-analyst.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/6-simple-steps-to-eliminate-soc-analyst.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The current SOC model relies on a scarce resource: human analysts. These professionals are expensive, in high demand, and increasingly difficult to retain. Their work is not only highly technical and high-risk, but also soul-crushingly repetitive, dealing with a constant flood of alerts and incidents. As a result, SOC analysts often leave in search of better pay, the opportunity to move beyond]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0860/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0860/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T09:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0859/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0859/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T09:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mitel Micollab (10 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0858/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0858/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T09:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mitel Micollab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Use Unicode to Hide Mongolian Skimmer in E-Commerce Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cybercriminals-use-unicode-to-hide.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cybercriminals-use-unicode-to-hide.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T07:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a new digital skimmer campaign that leverages Unicode obfuscation techniques to conceal a skimmer dubbed Mongolian Skimmer.
"At first glance, the thing that stood out was the script's obfuscation, which seemed a bit bizarre because of all the accented characters," Jscrambler researchers said in an analysis. "The heavy use of Unicode characters, many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Critical Fortinet Flaw as Palo Alto and Cisco Issue Urgent Security Patches]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-critical-fortinet-flaw-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cisa-warns-of-critical-fortinet-flaw-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T05:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Wednesday added a critical security flaw impacting Fortinet products to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23113 (CVSS score: 9.8), relates to cases of remote code execution that affects FortiOS, FortiPAM, FortiProxy, and FortiWeb.
"A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Firefox Zero-Day Under Attack: Update Your Browser Immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/mozilla-warns-of-active-exploitation-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/mozilla-warns-of-active-exploitation-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-10T04:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla has revealed that a critical security flaw impacting Firefox and Firefox Extended Support Release (ESR) has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-9680, has been described as a use-after-free bug in the Animation timeline component.
"An attacker was able to achieve code execution in the content process by exploiting a use-after-free in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Joins Forces with GASA and DNS RF to Tackle Online Scams at Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/google-joins-forces-with-gasa-and-dns.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/google-joins-forces-with-gasa-and-dns.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Wednesday announced a new partnership with the Global Anti-Scam Alliance (GASA) and DNS Research Federation (DNS RF) to combat online scams.
The initiative, which has been codenamed the Global Signal Exchange (GSE), is designed to create real-time insights into scams, fraud, and other forms of cybercrime pooling together threat signals from different data sources in order to create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Major Security Vulnerabilities in Industrial MMS Protocol Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-uncover-major-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-uncover-major-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about multiple security vulnerabilities in two implementations of the Manufacturing Message Specification (MMS) protocol that, if successfully exploited, could have severe impacts in industrial environments.
"The vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to crash an industrial device or in some cases, enable remote code execution," Claroty researchers Mashav Sapir and Vera]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean Hackers Use Fake Interviews to Infect Developers with Cross-Platform Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/n-korean-hackers-use-fake-interviews-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/n-korean-hackers-use-fake-interviews-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed targeting job seekers in the tech industry to deliver updated versions of known malware families tracked as BeaverTail and InvisibleFerret.
The activity cluster, tracked as CL-STA-0240, is part of a campaign dubbed Contagious Interview that Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 first disclosed in November 2023.
"The threat actor behind CL-STA-0240]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0857/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0857/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:35:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0856/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0856/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:35:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0854/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0854/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance. Microsoft indique que les vulnérabilités CVE-2024-43572...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0855/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0855/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0853/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0853/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:35:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Intel TDX Module (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0852/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0852/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:30:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Intel TDX Module. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0851/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0851/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:09:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données. Ivanti indique que les vulnérabilités...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Social Media Accounts: The Weak Link in Organizational SaaS Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/social-media-accounts-weak-link-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/social-media-accounts-weak-link-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Social media accounts help shape a brand’s identity and reputation. These public forums engage directly with customers as they are a hub to connect, share content and answer questions. However, despite the high profile role these accounts have, many organizations overlook social media account security. Many lack the safeguards to prevent unauthorized access — a situation no organization wants as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0850/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0850/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T09:36:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0849/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0849/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T09:32:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Adobe Commerce et Magento (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0848/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0848/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T09:24:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (09 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0847/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0847/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T09:02:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues Security Update Fixing 118 Flaws, Two Actively Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-issues-security-update-fixing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-issues-security-update-fixing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates to fix a total of 118 vulnerabilities across its software portfolio, two of which have come under active exploitation in the wild.
Of the 118 flaws, three are rated Critical, 113 are rated Important, and two are rated Moderate in severity. The Patch Tuesday update doesn't include the 25 additional flaws that the tech giant addressed in its Chromium-based]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Detects Growing Use of File Hosting Services in Business Email Compromise Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-detects-growing-use-of-file.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/microsoft-detects-growing-use-of-file.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-09T04:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning of cyber attack campaigns that abuse legitimate file hosting services such as SharePoint, OneDrive, and Dropbox that are widely used in enterprise environments as a defense evasion tactic.
The end goal of the campaigns are broad and varied, allowing threat actors to compromise identities and devices and conduct business email compromise (BEC) attacks, which ultimately result]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Alert: Three Critical Ivanti CSA Vulnerabilities Actively Exploited]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/zero-day-alert-three-critical-ivanti.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/zero-day-alert-three-critical-ivanti.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has warned that three new security vulnerabilities impacting its Cloud Service Appliance (CSA) have come under active exploitation in the wild.
The zero-day flaws are being weaponized in conjunction with another flaw in CSA that the company patched last month, the Utah-based software services provider said.
Successful exploitation of these vulnerabilities could allow an authenticated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gamers Tricked Into Downloading Lua-Based Malware via Fake Cheating Script Engines]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/gamers-tricked-into-downloading-lua.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/gamers-tricked-into-downloading-lua.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T16:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users searching for game cheats are being tricked into downloading a Lua-based malware that is capable of establishing persistence on infected systems and delivering additional payloads.
"These attacks capitalize on the popularity of Lua gaming engine supplements within the student gamer community," Morphisec researcher Shmuel Uzan said in a new report published today, adding "this malware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (08 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0846/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0846/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T12:32:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider Electric (08 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0845/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0845/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:28:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider Electric. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (08 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0844/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0844/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:23:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Typo3 (08 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0843/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0843/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:17:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Typo3. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattack Group 'Awaken Likho' Targets Russian Government with Advanced Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cyberattack-group-awaken-likho-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cyberattack-group-awaken-likho-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian government agencies and industrial entities are the target of an ongoing activity cluster dubbed Awaken Likho.
"The attackers now prefer using the agent for the legitimate MeshCentral platform instead of the UltraVNC module, which they had previously used to gain remote access to systems," Kaspersky said, detailing a new campaign that began in June 2024 and continued at least until]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Case Study: The Evil Twin Checkout Page]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-case-study-evil-twin-checkout-page.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-case-study-evil-twin-checkout-page.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Is your store at risk? Discover how an innovative web security solution saved one global online retailer and its unsuspecting customers from an “evil twin” disaster. Read the full real-life case study here.

The Invisible Threat in Online Shopping
When is a checkout page, not a checkout page? When it's an “evil twin”! Malicious redirects can send unsuspecting shoppers to these perfect-looking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Value of AI-Powered Identity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-value-of-ai-powered-identity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-value-of-ai-powered-identity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction 
Artificial intelligence (AI) deepfakes and misinformation may cause worry in the world of technology and investment, but this powerful, foundational technology has the potential to benefit organizations of all kinds when harnessed appropriately. 
In the world of cybersecurity, one of the most important areas of application of AI is augmenting and enhancing identity management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GoldenJackal Target Embassies and Air-Gapped Systems Using Malware Toolsets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/goldenjackal-target-embassies-and-air.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/goldenjackal-target-embassies-and-air.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little-known threat actor tracked as GoldenJackal has been linked to a series of cyber attacks targeting embassies and governmental organizations with an aim to infiltrate air-gapped systems using two disparate bespoke toolsets.
Victims included a South Asian embassy in Belarus and a European Union government (E.U.) organization, Slovak cybersecurity company ESET said.
"The ultimate goal of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pro-Ukrainian Hackers Strike Russian State TV on Putin's Birthday]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/pro-ukrainian-hackers-strike-russian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/pro-ukrainian-hackers-strike-russian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T05:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine has claimed responsibility for a cyber attack that targeted Russia state media company VGTRK and disrupted its operations, according to reports from Bloomberg and Reuters.
The incident took place on the night of October 7, VGTRK confirmed, describing it as an "unprecedented hacker attack." However, it said "no significant damage" was caused and that everything was working normally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm Urges OEMs to Patch Critical DSP and WLAN Flaws Amid Active Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/qualcomm-urges-oems-to-patch-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/qualcomm-urges-oems-to-patch-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-08T04:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Qualcomm has rolled out security updates to address nearly two dozen flaws spanning proprietary and open-source components, including one that has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-43047 (CVSS score: 7.8), has been described as a user-after-free bug in the Digital Signal Processor (DSP) Service that could lead to "memory corruption]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnerable APIs and Bot Attacks Costing Businesses Up to $186 Billion Annually]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/vulnerable-apis-and-bot-attacks-costing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/vulnerable-apis-and-bot-attacks-costing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations are losing between $94 - $186 billion annually to vulnerable or insecure APIs (Application Programming Interfaces) and automated abuse by bots. That’s according to The Economic Impact of API and Bot Attacks report from Imperva, a Thales company. The report highlights that these security threats account for up to 11.8% of global cyber events and losses, emphasizing the escalating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Modernization of Authentication: Webinar on MFA, Passwords, and the Shift to Passwordless]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/modernization-of-authentication-webinar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/modernization-of-authentication-webinar.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The interest in passwordless authentication has increased due to the rise of hybrid work environments and widespread digitization. This has led to a greater need for reliable data security and user-friendly interfaces. Without these measures, organizations are at risk of experiencing data breaches, leaks, and significant financial losses. 
While traditional password-based systems offer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Gorilla Botnet Launches Over 300,000 DDoS Attacks Across 100 Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-gorilla-botnet-launches-over-300000.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-gorilla-botnet-launches-over-300000.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new botnet malware family called Gorilla (aka GorillaBot) that is a variant of the leaked Mirai botnet source code.
Cybersecurity firm NSFOCUS, which identified the activity last month, said the botnet "issued over 300,000 attack commands, with a shocking attack density" between September 4 and September 27, 2024. No less than 20,000 commands designed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Apache Avro SDK Flaw Allows Remote Code Execution in Java Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-apache-avro-sdk-flaw-allows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/critical-apache-avro-sdk-flaw-allows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the Apache Avro Java Software Development Kit (SDK) that, if successfully exploited, could allow the execution of arbitrary code on susceptible instances.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-47561, impacts all versions of the software prior to 1.11.4.
"Schema parsing in the Java SDK of Apache Avro 1.11.3 and previous versions allows bad actors to execute]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Top Threats and Trends (Sep 30 - Oct 6)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/thn-cybersecurity-recap-top-threats-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ever heard of a "pig butchering" scam? Or a DDoS attack so big it could melt your brain? This week's cybersecurity recap has it all – government showdowns, sneaky malware, and even a dash of app store shenanigans.
Get the scoop before it's too late!
⚡ Threat of the Week
Double Trouble: Evil Corp & LockBit Fall: A consortium of international law enforcement agencies took steps to arrest four]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Blocks Unsafe Android App Sideloading in India for Improved Fraud Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/google-blocks-unsafe-android-app.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/google-blocks-unsafe-android-app.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's piloting a new security initiative that automatically blocks sideloading of potentially unsafe Android apps in India, after similar tests in Singapore, Thailand, and Brazil.
The enhanced fraud protection feature aims to keep users safe when they attempt to install malicious apps from sources other than the Google Play Store, such as web browsers, messaging apps,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-044 (07 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-044/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-044/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T08:46:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (07 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0842/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0842/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T07:47:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[E.U. Court Limits Meta's Use of Personal Facebook Data for Targeted Ads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/eu-court-limits-metas-use-of-personal.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/eu-court-limits-metas-use-of-personal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-07T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europe's top court has ruled that Meta Platforms must restrict the use of personal data harvested from Facebook for serving targeted ads even when users consent to their information being used for advertising purposes, a move that could have serious consequences for ad-driven companies operating in the region.
"An online social network such as Facebook cannot use all of the personal data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Releases Critical iOS and iPadOS Updates to Fix VoiceOver Password Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/apple-releases-critical-ios-and-ipados.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/apple-releases-critical-ios-and-ipados.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-05T04:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has released iOS and iPadOS updates to address two security issues, one of which could have allowed a user's passwords to be read out aloud by its VoiceOver assistive technology.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-44204, has been described as a logic problem in the new Passwords app impacting a slew of iPhones and iPads. Security researcher Bistrit Daha has been credited with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. and Microsoft Seize 107 Russian Domains in Major Cyber Fraud Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-and-microsoft-seize-107-russian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/us-and-microsoft-seize-107-russian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft and the U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Thursday announced the seizure of 107 internet domains used by state-sponsored threat actors with ties to Russia to facilitate computer fraud and abuse in the country.
"The Russian government ran this scheme to steal Americans' sensitive information, using seemingly legitimate email accounts to trick victims into revealing account credentials]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0841/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0841/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T12:08:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0840/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0840/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T12:03:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0839/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0839/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T12:02:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, un déni de service et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0838/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0838/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T12:00:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0837/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0837/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T11:56:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits WithSecure (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0836/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0836/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T11:48:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits WithSecure. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Get Going with CTEM When You Don't Know Where to Start]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/how-to-get-going-with-ctem-when-you.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/how-to-get-going-with-ctem-when-you.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Continuous Threat Exposure Management (CTEM) is a strategic framework that helps organizations continuously assess and manage cyber risk. It breaks down the complex task of managing security threats into five distinct stages: Scoping, Discovery, Prioritization, Validation, and Mobilization. Each of these stages plays a crucial role in identifying, addressing, and mitigating vulnerabilities -]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Thwarts Largest-Ever 3.8 Tbps DDoS Attack Targeting Global Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cloudflare-thwarts-largest-ever-38-tbps.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/cloudflare-thwarts-largest-ever-38-tbps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare has disclosed that it mitigated a record-breaking distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack that peaked at 3.8 terabits per second (Tbps) and lasted 65 seconds.
The web infrastructure and security company said it fended off "over one hundred hyper-volumetric L3/4 DDoS attacks throughout the month, with many exceeding 2 billion packets per second (Bpps) and 3 terabits per second (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress LiteSpeed Cache Plugin Security Flaw Exposes Sites to XSS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/wordpress-litespeed-cache-plugin.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/wordpress-litespeed-cache-plugin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new high-severity security flaw has been disclosed in the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress that could enable malicious actors to execute arbitrary JavaScript code under certain conditions.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-47374 (CVSS score: 7.2), has been described as a stored cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerability impacting all versions of the plugin up to and including 6.5.0.2.
It was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0835/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0835/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T07:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (04 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0834/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0834/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-04T07:32:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 14 Adds New Security Features to Block 2G Exploits and Baseband Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/android-14-adds-new-security-features.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/android-14-adds-new-security-features.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has revealed the various security guardrails that have been incorporated into its latest Pixel devices to counter the rising threat posed by baseband security attacks.
The cellular baseband (i.e., modem) refers to a processor on the device that's responsible for handling all connectivity, such as LTE, 4G, and 5G, with a mobile phone cell tower or base station over a radio interface.
"This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secret Weakness Execs Are Overlooking: Non-Human Identities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-secret-weakness-execs-are.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/the-secret-weakness-execs-are.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T15:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[For years, securing a company’s systems was synonymous with securing its “perimeter.” There was what was safe “inside” and the unsafe outside world. We built sturdy firewalls and deployed sophisticated detection systems, confident that keeping the barbarians outside the walls kept our data and systems safe.
The problem is that we no longer operate within the confines of physical on-prem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Perfctl Malware Targets Linux Servers for Cryptocurrency Mining and Proxyjacking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-perfctl-malware-targets-linux.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-perfctl-malware-targets-linux.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Linux servers are the target of an ongoing campaign that delivers a stealthy malware dubbed perfctl with the primary aim of running a cryptocurrency miner and proxyjacking software.
"Perfctl is particularly elusive and persistent, employing several sophisticated techniques," Aqua security researchers Assaf Morag and Idan Revivo said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
"When a new user logs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Using New VeilShell Backdoor in Stealthy Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-hackers-using-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/north-korean-hackers-using-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed delivering a previously undocumented backdoor and remote access trojan (RAT) called VeilShell as part of a campaign targeting Cambodia and likely other Southeast Asian countries.
The activity, dubbed SHROUDED#SLEEP by Securonix, is believed to be the handiwork of APT37, which is also known as InkySquid, Reaper, RedEyes, Ricochet Chollima,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (03 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0833/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0833/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T09:35:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL Arrests 8 in Major Phishing and Romance Fraud Crackdown in West Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/interpol-arrests-8-in-major-phishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/interpol-arrests-8-in-major-phishing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL has announced the arrest of eight individuals in Côte d'Ivoire and Nigeria as part of a crackdown on phishing scams and romance cyber fraud.
Dubbed Operation Contender 2.0, the initiative is designed to tackle cyber-enabled crimes in West Africa, the agency said.
One such threat involved a large-scale phishing scam targeting Swiss citizens that resulted in financial losses to the tune]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Sophos Intercept X (03 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0832/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0832/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T08:05:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Sophos Intercept X. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Suricata (03 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0831/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0831/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T08:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Suricata. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware and Evil Corp Leaders Arrested and Sanctioned in Joint Global Effort]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/lockbit-ransomware-and-evil-corp.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/lockbit-ransomware-and-evil-corp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new wave of international law enforcement actions has led to four arrests and the takedown of nine servers linked to the LockBit (aka Bitwise Spider) ransomware operation, marking the latest salvo against what was once a prolific financially motivated group.
This includes the arrest of a suspected LockBit developer in France while on holiday outside of Russia, two individuals in the U.K. who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Endpoint Manager Flaw Actively Targeted, CISA Warns Agencies to Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/ivanti-endpoint-manager-flaw-actively.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/ivanti-endpoint-manager-flaw-actively.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-03T06:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Wednesday added a security flaw impacting Endpoint Manager (EPM) that the company patched in May to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-29824, carries a CVSS score of 9.6 out of a maximum of 10.0, indicating critical severity.
"An]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Trading Apps Target Victims Globally via Apple App Store and Google Play]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fake-trading-apps-target-victims.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fake-trading-apps-target-victims.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large-scale fraud campaign leveraged fake trading apps published on the Apple App Store and Google Play Store, as well as phishing sites, to defraud victims, per findings from Group-IB.
The campaign is part of a consumer investment fraud scheme that's also widely known as pig butchering, in which prospective victims are lured into making investments in cryptocurrency or other financial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked CeranaKeeper Targeting Southeast Asia with Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/china-linked-ceranakeeper-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/china-linked-ceranakeeper-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat actor called CeranaKeeper has been linked to a string of data exfiltration attacks targeting Southeast Asia.
Slovak cybersecurity firm ESET, which observed campaigns targeting governmental institutions in Thailand starting in 2023, attributed the activity cluster as aligned to China, leveraging tools previously identified as used by the Mustang Panda actor.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Job Applications Deliver Dangerous More_eggs Malware to HR Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fake-job-applications-deliver-dangerous.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/fake-job-applications-deliver-dangerous.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A spear-phishing email campaign has been observed targeting recruiters with a JavaScript backdoor called More_eggs, indicating persistent efforts to single out the sector under the guise of fake job applicant lures.
"A sophisticated spear-phishing lure tricked a recruitment officer into downloading and executing a malicious file disguised as a resume, leading to a more_eggs backdoor infection,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Over 700,000 DrayTek Routers Exposed to Hacking via 14 New Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/alert-over-700000-draytek-routers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/alert-over-700000-draytek-routers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A little over a dozen new security vulnerabilities have been discovered in residential and enterprise routers manufactured by DrayTek that could be exploited to take over susceptible devices.
"These vulnerabilities could enable attackers to take control of a router by injecting malicious code, allowing them to persist on the device and use it as a gateway into enterprise networks," Forescout]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Adobe Commerce and Magento Stores Under Attack from CosmicSting Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/alert-adobe-commerce-and-magento-stores.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/alert-adobe-commerce-and-magento-stores.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed that 5% of all Adobe Commerce and Magento stores have been hacked by malicious actors by exploiting a security vulnerability dubbed CosmicSting.
Tracked as CVE-2024-34102 (CVSS score: 9.8), the critical flaw relates to an improper restriction of XML external entity reference (XXE) vulnerability that could result in remote code execution. The shortcoming,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Must-Have Tools for Effective Dynamic Malware Analysis]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-must-have-tools-for-effective-dynamic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-must-have-tools-for-effective-dynamic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Dynamic malware analysis is a key part of any threat investigation. It involves executing a sample of a malicious program in the isolated environment of a malware sandbox to monitor its behavior and gather actionable indicators. Effective analysis must be fast, in-depth, and precise. These five tools will help you achieve it with ease.
1. Interactivity
Having the ability to interact with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andariel Hacking Group Shifts Focus to Financial Attacks on U.S. Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/andariel-hacker-group-shifts-focus-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/andariel-hacker-group-shifts-focus-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three different organizations in the U.S. were targeted in August 2024 by a North Korean state-sponsored threat actor called Andariel as part of a likely financially motivated attack.
"While the attackers didn't succeed in deploying ransomware on the networks of any of the organizations affected, it is likely that the attacks were financially motivated," Symantec, part of Broadcom, said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Axis (02 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0830/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0830/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T09:46:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Axis. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (02 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0829/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0829/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T07:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (02 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0828/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0828/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T07:32:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Sound Alarm on Active Attacks Exploiting Critical Zimbra Postjournal Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-sound-alarm-on-active.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/researchers-sound-alarm-on-active.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about active exploitation attempts targeting a newly disclosed security flaw in Synacor's Zimbra Collaboration.
Enterprise security firm Proofpoint said it began observing the activity starting September 28, 2024. The attacks seek to exploit CVE-2024-45519, a severe security flaw in its postjournal service that could enable unauthenticated attackers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PyPI Repository Found Hosting Fake Crypto Wallet Recovery Tools That Steal User Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/pypi-repository-found-hosting-fake.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/pypi-repository-found-hosting-fake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-02T05:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of malicious packages has been unearthed in the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that masqueraded as cryptocurrency wallet recovery and management services, only to siphon sensitive data and facilitate the theft of valuable digital assets.
"The attack targeted users of Atomic, Trust Wallet, Metamask, Ronin, TronLink, Exodus, and other prominent wallets in the crypto ecosystem,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI-Powered Rhadamanthys Stealer Targets Crypto Wallets with Image Recognition]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/ai-powered-rhadamanthys-stealer-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/ai-powered-rhadamanthys-stealer-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T16:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the Rhadamanthys information stealer have added new advanced features to the malware, including using artificial intelligence (AI) for optical character recognition (OCR) as part of what's called "Seed Phrase Image Recognition."
"This allows Rhadamanthys to extract cryptocurrency wallet seed phrases from images, making it a highly potent threat for anyone dealing in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[5 Actionable Steps to Prevent GenAI Data Leaks Without Fully Blocking AI Usage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-actionable-steps-to-prevent-genai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/5-actionable-steps-to-prevent-genai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since its emergence, Generative AI has revolutionized enterprise productivity. GenAI tools enable faster and more effective software development, financial analysis, business planning, and customer engagement. However, this business agility comes with significant risks, particularly the potential for sensitive data leakage. As organizations attempt to balance productivity gains with security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Juniper Networks (01 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0827/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0827/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T08:47:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Juniper Networks. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Splunk (01 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0826/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0826/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T08:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Splunk. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans NetApp StorageGRID (01 octobre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0825/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0825/"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T08:25:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans NetApp StorageGRID. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Free Sniper Dz Phishing Tools Fuel 140,000+ Cyber Attacks Targeting User Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/free-sniper-dz-phishing-tools-fuel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/free-sniper-dz-phishing-tools-fuel.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 140,000 phishing websites have been found linked to a phishing-as-a-service (PhaaS) platform named Sniper Dz over the past year, indicating that it's being used by a large number of cybercriminals to conduct credential theft.
"For prospective phishers, Sniper Dz offers an online admin panel with a catalog of phishing pages," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 researchers Shehroze Farooqi,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cryptojacking Attack Targets Docker API to Create Malicious Swarm Botnet]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-cryptojacking-attack-targets-docker.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/new-cryptojacking-attack-targets-docker.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new cryptojacking campaign targeting the Docker Engine API with the goal of co-opting the instances to join a malicious Docker Swarm controlled by the threat actor.
This enabled the attackers to "use Docker Swarm's orchestration features for command-and-control (C2) purposes," Datadog researchers Matt Muir and Andy Giron said in an analysis.
The attacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.K. Hacker Charged in $3.75 Million Insider Trading Scheme Using Hacked Executive Emails]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/uk-hacker-charged-in-375-million.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/10/uk-hacker-charged-in-375-million.html"/>
        <updated>2024-10-01T02:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has charged a 39-year-old U.K. national for perpetrating a hack-to-trade fraud scheme that netted him nearly $3.75 million in illegal profits.
Robert Westbrook of London was arrested last week and is expected to be extradited to the U.S. to face charges related to securities fraud, wire fraud, and five counts of computer fraud. 
According to the court]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Last Week's Top Threats and Trends (September 23-29)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top_30.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top_30.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T13:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hold onto your hats, folks, because the cybersecurity world is anything but quiet! Last week, we dodged a bullet when we discovered vulnerabilities in CUPS that could've opened the door to remote attacks. Google's switch to Rust is paying off big time, slashing memory-related vulnerabilities in Android.
But it wasn't all good news – Kaspersky's forced exit from the US market left users with more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws in Tank Gauge Systems Expose Gas Stations to Remote Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaws-in-tank-gauge-systems.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaws-in-tank-gauge-systems.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T11:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Critical security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in six different Automatic Tank Gauge (ATG) systems from five manufacturers that could expose them to remote attacks.
"These vulnerabilities pose significant real-world risks, as they could be exploited by malicious actors to cause widespread damage, including physical damage, environmental hazards, and economic losses," Bitsight researcher]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Session Hijacking 2.0 — The Latest Way That Attackers are Bypassing MFA]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/session-hijacking-20-latest-way-that.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/session-hijacking-20-latest-way-that.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are increasingly turning to session hijacking to get around widespread MFA adoption. The data supports this, as:

147,000 token replay attacks were detected by Microsoft in 2023, a 111% increase year-over-year (Microsoft). 
Attacks on session cookies now happen in the same order of magnitude as password-based attacks (Google).

But session hijacking isn’t a new technique – so]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A Hacker's Era: Why Microsoft 365 Protection Reigns Supreme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-microsoft-365-protection-reigns-supreme.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-microsoft-365-protection-reigns-supreme.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a sophisticated cyberattack cripples your organization’s most critical productivity and collaboration tool — the platform you rely on for daily operations. In the blink of an eye, hackers encrypt your emails, files, and crucial business data stored in Microsoft 365, holding it hostage using ransomware. Productivity grinds to a halt and your IT team races to assess the damage as the clock]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Foxit PDF Editor (30 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0824/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0824/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T09:31:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Foxit PDF Editor. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-043 (30 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-043/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-043/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T07:46:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d'actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l'analyse de l'ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d'une analyse de risques pour prioriser l'application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Fined €91 Million for Storing Millions of Facebook and Instagram Passwords in Plaintext]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/meta-fined-91-million-for-storing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/meta-fined-91-million-for-storing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-30T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC) has fined Meta €91 million ($101.56 million) as part of a probe into a security lapse in March 2019, when the company disclosed that it had mistakenly stored users' passwords in plaintext in its systems.
The investigation, launched by the DPC the next month, found that the social media giant violated four different articles under the European Union's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto Scam App Disguised as WalletConnect Steals $70K in Five-Month Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/crypto-scam-app-disguised-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/crypto-scam-app-disguised-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a malicious Android app on the Google Play Store that enabled the threat actors behind it to steal approximately $70,000 in cryptocurrency from victims over a period of nearly five months.
The dodgy app, identified by Check Point, masqueraded as the legitimate WalletConnect open-source protocol to trick unsuspecting users into downloading it.
"Fake]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Charges Three Iranian Nationals for Election Interference and Cybercrimes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-charges-three-iranian-nationals-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-charges-three-iranian-nationals-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-28T06:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. federal prosecutors on Friday unsealed criminal charges against three Iranian nationals who are allegedly employed with the Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps (IRGC) for their targeting of current and former officials to steal sensitive data.
The Department of Justice (DoJ) accused Masoud Jalili, 36, Seyyed Ali Aghamiri, 34, and Yasar (Yaser) Balaghi, 37, of participating in a conspiracy]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software Releases Patches for 6 Flaws in WhatsUp Gold – Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-releases-patches-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-releases-patches-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has released another round of updates to address six security flaws in WhatsUp Gold, including two critical vulnerabilities.
The issues, the company said, have been resolved in version 24.0.1 released on September 20, 2024. The company has yet to release any details about what the flaws are other than listing their CVE identifiers -

CVE-2024-46905 (CVSS score: 8.8)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilités affectant OpenPrinting CUPS (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-012/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-012/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans OpenPrinting CUPS et dans le composant cups-browsed. Celui-ci permet notamment de découvrir automatiquement des imprimantes partagées sur le réseau. Au total, quatre vulnérabilités ont été identifiées. Elles permettent : de récupérer des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Linux CUPS Printing System Flaws Could Allow Remote Command Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-linux-cups-printing-system.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-linux-cups-printing-system.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T12:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of security vulnerabilities has been disclosed in the OpenPrinting Common Unix Printing System (CUPS) on Linux systems that could permit remote command execution under certain conditions.
"A remote unauthenticated attacker can silently replace existing printers' (or install new ones) IPP urls with a malicious one, resulting in arbitrary command execution (on the computer) when a print]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Plan and Prepare for Penetration Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-plan-and-prepare-for-penetration.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-plan-and-prepare-for-penetration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As security technology and threat awareness among organizations improves so do the adversaries who are adopting and relying on new techniques to maximize speed and impact while evading detection.
Ransomware and malware continue to be the method of choice by big game hunting (BGH) cyber criminals, and the increased use of hands-on or “interactive intrusion” techniques is especially alarming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Identifies Storm-0501 as Major Threat in Hybrid Cloud Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-identifies-storm-0501-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-identifies-storm-0501-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Storm-0501 has targeted government, manufacturing, transportation, and law enforcement sectors in the U.S. to stage ransomware attacks.
The multi-stage attack campaign is designed to compromise hybrid cloud environments and perform lateral movement from on-premises to cloud environment, ultimately resulting in data exfiltration, credential theft, tampering, persistent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Certifications: The Gateway to Career Advancement]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-certifications-gateway-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-certifications-gateway-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's fast-evolving digital landscape, cybersecurity has become a cornerstone of organizational resilience. As cyber threats grow increasingly sophisticated, the demand for skilled cybersecurity professionals has never been higher. Whether you're a seasoned cyber professional or just starting your journey, signing up for the GIAC Newsletter ensures you're always informed and equipped for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HTML Smuggling Campaign Delivers DCRat Malware to Russian-Speaking Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-html-smuggling-campaign-delivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-html-smuggling-campaign-delivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-speaking users have been targeted as part of a new campaign distributing a commodity trojan called DCRat (aka DarkCrystal RAT) by means of a technique known as HTML smuggling.
The development marks the first time the malware has been deployed using this method, a departure from previously observed delivery vectors such as compromised or fake websites, or phishing emails bearing PDF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0823/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0823/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0822/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0822/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0821/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0821/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités IBM Cognos Transformer (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0820/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0820/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0819/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0819/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans PHP (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0818/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0818/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PHP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions Two Crypto Exchanges for Facilitating Cybercrime and Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-sanctions-two-crypto-exchanges-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-sanctions-two-crypto-exchanges-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Thursday sanctioned two cryptocurrency exchanges and unsealed an indictment against a Russian national for his alleged involvement in the operation of several money laundering services that were offered to cybercriminals.
The virtual currency exchanges, Cryptex and PM2BTC, have been alleged to facilitate the laundering of cryptocurrencies possibly obtained through]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0817/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0817/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical NVIDIA Container Toolkit Vulnerability Could Grant Full Host Access to Attackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the NVIDIA Container Toolkit that, if successfully exploited, could allow threat actors to break out of the confines of a container and gain full access to the underlying host.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-0132, carries a CVSS score of 9.0 out of a maximum of 10.0. It has been addressed in NVIDIA Container Toolkit version v1.16.2 and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Could Have Remotely Controlled Kia Cars Using Only License Plates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-could-have-remotely-controlled.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-could-have-remotely-controlled.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a set of now patched vulnerabilities in Kia vehicles that, if successfully exploited, could have allowed remote control over key functions simply by using only a license plate.
"These attacks could be executed remotely on any hardware-equipped vehicle in about 30 seconds, regardless of whether it had an active Kia Connect subscription," security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overloaded with SIEM Alerts? Discover Effective Strategies in This Expert-Led Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/overloaded-with-siem-alerts-discover.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/overloaded-with-siem-alerts-discover.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine trying to find a needle in a haystack, but the haystack is on fire, and there are a million other needles you also need to find. That's what dealing with security alerts can feel like.
SIEM was supposed to make this easier, but somewhere along the way, it became part of the problem. Too many alerts, too much noise, and not enough time to actually stop threats.
It's time for a change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean Hackers Deploy New KLogEXE and FPSpy Malware in Targeted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/n-korean-hackers-deploy-new-klogexe-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/n-korean-hackers-deploy-new-klogexe-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed leveraging two new malware strains dubbed KLogEXE and FPSpy.
The activity has been attributed to an adversary tracked as Kimsuky, which is also known as APT43, ARCHIPELAGO, Black Banshee, Emerald Sleet (formerly Thallium), Sparkling Pisces, Springtail, and Velvet Chollima.
"These samples enhance Sparkling Pisces' already extensive arsenal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Foxit (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0816/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0816/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T11:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Foxit. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPSS vs. CVSS: What’s the Best Approach to Vulnerability Prioritization?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/epss-vs-cvss-whats-best-approach-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/epss-vs-cvss-whats-best-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many businesses rely on the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) to assess the severity of vulnerabilities for prioritization. While these scores provide some insight into the potential impact of a vulnerability, they don’t factor in real-world threat data, such as the likelihood of exploitation. With new vulnerabilities discovered daily, teams don’t have the time - or the budget - to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watering Hole Attack on Kurdish Sites Distributing Malicious APKs and Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/watering-hole-attack-on-kurdish-sites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/watering-hole-attack-on-kurdish-sites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 25 websites linked to the Kurdish minority have been compromised as part of a watering hole attack designed to harvest sensitive information for over a year and a half.
French cybersecurity firm Sekoia, which disclosed details of the campaign dubbed SilentSelfie, described the intrusion set as long-running, with first signs of infection detected as far back as December 2022.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Synology (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0815/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0815/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T08:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Synology. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0814/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0814/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T07:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0813/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0813/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T06:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Warns of India-Linked Hackers Targeting South and East Asian Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cloudflare-warns-of-india-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cloudflare-warns-of-india-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An advanced threat actor with an India nexus has been observed using multiple cloud service providers to facilitate credential harvesting, malware delivery, and command-and-control (C2).
Web infrastructure and security company Cloudflare is tracking the activity under the name SloppyLemming, which is also called Outrider Tiger and Fishing Elephant.
"Between late 2022 to present, SloppyLemming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Infiltrate U.S. Internet Providers in Cyber Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-infiltrate-us-internet.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-infiltrate-us-internet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T04:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-state threat actors backed by Beijing broke into a "handful" of U.S. internet service providers (ISPs) as part of a cyber espionage campaign orchestrated to glean sensitive information, The Wall Street Journal reported Wednesday.
The activity has been attributed to a threat actor that Microsoft tracks as Salt Typhoon, which is also known as FamousSparrow and GhostEmperor.
"Investigators]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Shift to Rust Programming Cuts Android Memory Vulnerabilities by 52%]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/googles-shift-to-rust-programming-cuts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/googles-shift-to-rust-programming-cuts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has revealed that its transition to memory-safe languages such as Rust as part of its secure-by-design approach has led to the percentage of memory-safe vulnerabilities discovered in Android dropping from 76% to 24% over a period of six years.
The tech giant said focusing on Safe Coding for new features not only reduces the overall security risk of a codebase, but also makes the switch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Faces Privacy Complaint for Enabling Tracking in Firefox Without User Consent]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mozilla-faces-privacy-complaint-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mozilla-faces-privacy-complaint-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vienna-based privacy non-profit noyb (short for None Of Your Business) has filed a complaint with the Austrian data protection authority (DPA) against Firefox maker Mozilla for enabling a new feature called Privacy Preserving Attribution (PPA) without explicitly seeking users' consent.
"Contrary to its reassuring name, this technology allows Firefox to track user behavior on websites," noyb said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Traefik (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0812/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0812/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Traefik. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Trend Micro (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0811/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0811/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Trend Micro. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Researchers Warn of New Rust-Based Splinter Post-Exploitation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-researchers-warn-of-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-researchers-warn-of-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have flagged the discovery of a new post-exploitation red team tool called Splinter in the wild.
Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 shared its findings after it discovered the program on several customers' systems.
"It has a standard set of features commonly found in penetration testing tools and its developer created it using the Rust programming language," Unit 42's Dominik]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Tips on How to Spot a Phishing Link]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/expert-tips-on-how-to-spot-phishing-link.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/expert-tips-on-how-to-spot-phishing-link.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing attacks are becoming more advanced and harder to detect, but there are still telltale signs that can help you spot them before it's too late. See these key indicators that security experts use to identify phishing links:1. Check Suspicious URLs 

Phishing URLs are often long, confusing, or filled with random characters. Attackers use these to disguise the link's true destination]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI in SOCs: A Solution to SOAR's Unfulfilled Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/agentic-ai-in-socs-solution-to-soars.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/agentic-ai-in-socs-solution-to-soars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security Orchestration, Automation, and Response (SOAR) was introduced with the promise of revolutionizing Security Operations Centers (SOCs) through automation, reducing manual workloads and enhancing efficiency. However, despite three generations of technology and 10 years of advancements, SOAR hasn’t fully delivered on its potential, leaving SOCs still grappling with many of the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT macOS Flaw Could've Enabled Long-Term Spyware via Memory Function]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chatgpt-macos-flaw-couldve-enabled-long.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chatgpt-macos-flaw-couldve-enabled-long.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security vulnerability in OpenAI's ChatGPT app for macOS could have made it possible for attackers to plant long-term persistent spyware into the artificial intelligence (AI) tool's memory.
The technique, dubbed SpAIware, could be abused to facilitate "continuous data exfiltration of any information the user typed or responses received by ChatGPT, including any future chat sessions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Xen (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0810/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0810/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Xen. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0809/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0809/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0808/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0808/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nessus Network Monitor (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0807/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0807/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nessus Network Monitor. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0806/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0806/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T08:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Nagios XI (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0805/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0805/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T07:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Nagios XI. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transportation Companies Hit by Cyberattacks Using Lumma Stealer and NetSupport Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/transportation-companies-hit-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/transportation-companies-hit-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transportation and logistics companies in North America are the target of a new phishing campaign that delivers a variety of information stealers and remote access trojans (RATs).
The activity cluster, per Proofpoint, makes use of compromised legitimate email accounts belonging to transportation and shipping companies so as to inject malicious content into existing email conversations.
As many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0804/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0804/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T06:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Stormshield. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Flags Critical Ivanti vTM Vulnerability Amid Active Exploitation Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisa-flags-critical-ivanti-vtm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisa-flags-critical-ivanti-vtm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Tuesday added a critical security flaw impacting Ivanti Virtual Traffic Manager (vTM) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-7593 (CVSS score: 9.8), which could be exploited by a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Necro Android Malware Found in Popular Camera and Browser Apps on Play Store]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/necro-android-malware-found-in-popular.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/necro-android-malware-found-in-popular.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altered versions of legitimate Android apps associated with Spotify, WhatsApp, and Minecraft have been used to deliver a new version of a known malware loader called Necro.
Kaspersky said some of the malicious apps have also been found on the Google Play Store. They have been cumulatively downloaded 11 million times. They include -

Wuta Camera - Nice Shot Always (com.benqu.wuta) - 10+ million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Proposes Ban on Connected Vehicles Using Chinese and Russian Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-proposes-ban-on-connected-vehicles.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-proposes-ban-on-connected-vehicles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Commerce (DoC) said it's proposing a ban on the import or sale of connected vehicles that integrate software and hardware made by foreign adversaries, particularly that of the People's Republic of China (PRC) and Russia.
"The proposed rule focuses on hardware and software integrated into the Vehicle Connectivity System (VCS) and software integrated into the Automated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Latest Ransomware Tactics and Zero Trust Strategies in This Expert Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discover-latest-ransomware-tactics-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discover-latest-ransomware-tactics-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware is no longer just a threat; it's an entire industry. Cybercriminals are growing more sophisticated, and their tactics are evolving rapidly.
This persistent danger is a major concern for business leaders.
But there's good news: you don't have to be defenseless. What if you could gain a strategic edge?
Join our exclusive webinar, "Unpacking the 2024 Ransomware Landscape: Insights and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky Exits U.S., Automatically Replaces Software With UltraAV, Raising Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/kaspersky-exits-us-automatically.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/kaspersky-exits-us-automatically.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antivirus vendor Kaspersky has formally begun pulling back its offerings in the U.S., migrating existing users to UltraAV, effective September 19, 2024, ahead of its formal exit at the end of the month.
"Kaspersky antivirus customers received a software update facilitating the transition to UltraAV," the company said in a post announcing the move on September 21.
"This update ensured that users]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans TheGreenBow VPN Client  (24 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0803/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0803/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans TheGreenBow VPN Client. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SSPM Justification Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-sspm-justification-kit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-sspm-justification-kit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications contain a wealth of sensitive data and are central to business operations. Despite this, far too many organizations rely on half measures and hope their SaaS stack will remain secure. Unfortunately, this approach is lacking and will leave security teams blind to threat prevention and detection, as well as open to regulatory violations, data leaks, and significant breaches.
If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Octo2 Android Banking Trojan Emerges with Device Takeover Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-octo2-android-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-octo2-android-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new version of an Android banking trojan called Octo that comes with improved capabilities to conduct device takeover (DTO) and perform fraudulent transactions.
The new version has been codenamed Octo2 by the malware author, Dutch security firm ThreatFabric said in a report shared with The Hacker News, adding campaigns distributing the malware have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exfiltration de données du secteur social - Retour d’expérience du CERT-FR (24 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-009/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-009/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L’année 2023 et le début de l’année 2024 ont été marqués par de nombreux incidents ciblant des entités du secteur social gérant des données à caractère personnel . Compte tenu des impacts qu’ont eu ces exfiltrations de données, le CERT-FR propose un retour d’expérience sur la gestion de ces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Agrees to Share User Data With Authorities for Criminal Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/telegram-agrees-to-share-user-data-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/telegram-agrees-to-share-user-data-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a major policy reversal, the popular messaging app Telegram has announced it will give users' IP addresses and phone numbers to authorities in response to valid legal requests in an attempt to rein in criminal activity on the platform.
"We've made it clear that the IP addresses and phone numbers of those who violate our rules can be disclosed to relevant authorities in response to valid legal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-042 (23 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-042/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-042/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Last Week's Top Threats and Trends (September 16-22)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hold on tight, folks, because last week's cybersecurity landscape was a rollercoaster! We witnessed everything from North Korean hackers dangling "dream jobs" to expose a new malware, to a surprising twist in the Apple vs. NSO Group saga. Even the seemingly mundane world of domain names and cloud configurations had its share of drama. Let's dive into the details and see what lessons we can glean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Never Expire' Passwords Can Be a Risky Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-never-expire-passwords-can-be-risky.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-never-expire-passwords-can-be-risky.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password resets can be frustrating for end users. Nobody likes being interrupted by the ‘time to change your password’ notification – and they like it even less when the new passwords they create are rejected by their organization’s password policy. IT teams share the pain, with resetting passwords via service desk tickets and support calls being an everyday burden. Despite this, it’s commonly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Microchip ASF Exposes IoT Devices to Remote Code Execution Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaw-in-microchip-asf-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaw-in-microchip-asf-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the Microchip Advanced Software Framework (ASF) that, if successfully exploited, could lead to remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7490, carries a CVSS score of 9.5 out of a maximum of 10.0. It has been described as a stack-based overflow vulnerability in ASF's implementation of the tinydhcp server stemming from a lack of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord Introduces DAVE Protocol for End-to-End Encryption in Audio and Video Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discord-introduces-dave-protocol-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discord-introduces-dave-protocol-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular social messaging platform Discord has announced that it's rolling out a new custom end-to-end encrypted (E2EE) protocol to secure audio and video calls.
The protocol has been dubbed DAVE, short for Discord's audio and video end-to-end encryption ("E2EE A/V").
As part of the change introduced last week, voice and video in DMs, Group DMs, voice channels, and Go Live streams are expected to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>