<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-05-08T11:23:48.605Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Fundamentals of Cloud Security Stress Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-fundamentals-of-cloud-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-fundamentals-of-cloud-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[״Defenders think in lists, attackers think in graphs,” said John Lambert from Microsoft, distilling the fundamental difference in mindset between those who defend IT systems and those who try to compromise them.
The traditional approach for defenders is to list security gaps directly related to their assets in the network and eliminate as many as possible, starting with the most critical.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hijack Loader Malware Employs Process Hollowing, UAC Bypass in Latest Version]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hijack-loader-malware-employs-process.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hijack-loader-malware-employs-process.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newer version of a malware loader called Hijack Loader has been observed incorporating an updated set of anti-analysis techniques to fly under the radar.
"These enhancements aim to increase the malware's stealthiness, thereby remaining undetected for longer periods of time," Zscaler ThreatLabz researcher Muhammed Irfan V A said in a technical report.
"Hijack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting LiteSpeed Cache Bug to Gain Full Control of WordPress Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-exploiting-litespeed-cache-bug.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-exploiting-litespeed-cache-bug.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-08T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A high-severity flaw impacting the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress is being actively exploited by threat actors to create rogue admin accounts on susceptible websites.
The findings come from WPScan, which said that the vulnerability (CVE-2023-40000, CVSS score: 8.3) has been leveraged to set up bogus admin users with the names wpsupp‑user]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacker Dmitry Khoroshev Unmasked as LockBit Ransomware Administrator]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-hacker-dmitry-khoroshev.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-hacker-dmitry-khoroshev.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. National Crime Agency (NCA) has unmasked the administrator and developer of the LockBit ransomware operation, revealing it to be a 31-year-old Russian national named Dmitry Yuryevich Khoroshev.
In addition, Khoroshev has been sanctioned by the U.K. Foreign, Commonwealth and Development Office (FCD), the U.S. Department of the Treasury’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0369 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits GLPI (07 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0369/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0369/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T14:00:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits GLPI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT42 Hackers Pose as Journalists to Harvest Credentials and Access Cloud Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/apt42-hackers-pose-as-journalists-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/apt42-hackers-pose-as-journalists-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian state-backed hacking outfit called APT42 is making use of enhanced social engineering schemes to infiltrate target networks and cloud environments.
Targets of the attack include Western and Middle Eastern NGOs, media organizations, academia, legal services and activists, Google Cloud subsidiary Mandiant said in a report published last week.
"APT42 was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Used ROOTROT Webshell in MITRE Network Intrusion]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-used-rootrot.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-used-rootrot.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MITRE Corporation has offered more details into the recently disclosed cyber attack, stating that the first evidence of the intrusion now dates back to December 31, 2023.
The attack, which came to light last month, singled out MITRE's Networked Experimentation, Research, and Virtualization Environment (NERVE) through the exploitation of two Ivanti Connect Secure zero-day]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Case Study: The Malicious Comment]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-case-study-malicious-comment.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-case-study-malicious-comment.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How safe is your comments section? Discover how a seemingly innocent 'thank you' comment on a product page concealed a malicious vulnerability, underscoring the necessity of robust security measures. Read the full real-life case study here. 
When is a ‘Thank you’ not a ‘Thank you’? When it’s a sneaky bit of code that’s been hidden inside a ‘Thank You’]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Simplifies 2-Factor Authentication Setup (It's More Important Than Ever)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-simplifies-2-factor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-simplifies-2-factor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Monday announced that it's simplifying the process of enabling two-factor authentication (2FA) for users with personal and Workspace accounts.
Also called, 2-Step Verification (2SV), it aims to add an extra layer of security to users' accounts to prevent takeover attacks in case the passwords are stolen.
The new change entails adding a second step method, such as an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Operator of BTC-e Crypto Exchange Pleads Guilty to Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-operator-of-btc-e-crypto.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-operator-of-btc-e-crypto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T09:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russian operator of a now-dismantled BTC-e cryptocurrency exchange has pleaded guilty to money laundering charges from 2011 to 2017.
Alexander Vinnik, 44, was charged in January 2017 and taken into custody in Greece in July 2017. He was subsequently extradited to the U.S. in August 2022. Vinnik and his co-conspirators have been accused of owning and managing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0368 : [SCADA] Vulnérabilité dans Moxa NPort (07 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0368/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0368/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-07T07:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Moxa NPort. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Tinyproxy Flaw Opens Over 50,000 Hosts to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-tinyproxy-flaw-opens-over.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-tinyproxy-flaw-opens-over.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 50% of the 90,310 hosts have been found exposing a Tinyproxy service on the internet that's vulnerable to a critical unpatched security flaw in the HTTP/HTTPS proxy tool.

The issue, tracked as CVE-2023-49606, carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10, per Cisco Talos, which described it as a use-after-free bug impacting versions 1.10.0 and 1.11.1, which is the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Suspected in ArcaneDoor Cyberattacks Targeting Network Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-suspected-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-suspected-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The recently uncovered cyber espionage campaign targeting perimeter network devices from several vendors, including Cisco, may have been the work of China-linked actors, according to new findings from attack surface management firm Censys.

Dubbed ArcaneDoor, the activity is said to have commenced around July 2023, with the first confirmed attack against an unnamed victim]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-020 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-020 (06 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-020/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-020/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T11:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It Costs How Much?!? The Financial Pitfalls of Cyberattacks on SMBs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/it-costs-how-much-financial-pitfalls-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/it-costs-how-much-financial-pitfalls-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals are vipers. They’re like snakes in the grass, hiding behind their keyboards, waiting to strike. And if you're a small- and medium-sized business (SMB), your organization is the ideal lair for these serpents to slither into. 
With cybercriminals becoming more sophisticated, SMBs like you must do more to protect themselves. But at what price? That’s the daunting question]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xiaomi Android Devices Hit by Multiple Flaws Across Apps and System Components]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/xiaomi-android-devices-hit-by-multiple.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/xiaomi-android-devices-hit-by-multiple.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in various applications and system components within Xiaomi devices running Android.
"The vulnerabilities in Xiaomi led to access to arbitrary activities, receivers and services with system privileges, theft of arbitrary files with system privileges, [and] disclosure of phone, settings and Xiaomi account data," mobile security firm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0367 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Serv-U (06 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0367/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0367/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T08:42:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Serv-U. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'Cuckoo' Persistent macOS Spyware Targeting Intel and Arm Macs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-cuckoo-persistent-macos-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-cuckoo-persistent-macos-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-06T07:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new information stealer targeting Apple macOS systems that's designed to set up persistence on the infected hosts and act as a spyware.
Dubbed Cuckoo by Kandji, the malware is a universal Mach-O binary that's capable of running on both Intel- and Arm-based Macs.
The exact distribution vector is currently unclear, although there are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Outlook Flaw Exploited by Russia's APT28 to Hack Czech, German Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-outlook-flaw-exploited-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-outlook-flaw-exploited-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-04T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Czechia and Germany on Friday revealed that they were the target of a long-term cyber espionage campaign conducted by the Russia-linked nation-state actor known as APT28, drawing condemnation from the European Union (E.U.), the North Atlantic Treaty Organization (NATO), the U.K., and the U.S.
The Czech Republic's Ministry of Foreign Affairs (MFA), in a statement, said some unnamed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert-Led Webinar - Uncovering Latest DDoS Tactics and Learn How to Fight Back]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/expert-led-webinar-learn-latest-ddos.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/expert-led-webinar-learn-latest-ddos.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T12:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly evolving digital landscape, the threat of Distributed Denial of Service (DDoS) attacks looms more significant than ever. As these cyber threats grow in sophistication, understanding and countering them becomes crucial for any business seeking to protect its online presence.
To address this urgent need, we are thrilled to announce our upcoming webinar, "Uncovering Contemporary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Increasingly Abusing Microsoft Graph API for Stealthy Malware Communications]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-increasingly-abusing-microsoft.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-increasingly-abusing-microsoft.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been increasingly weaponizing Microsoft Graph API for malicious purposes with the aim of evading detection.
This is done to "facilitate communications with command-and-control (C&C) infrastructure hosted on Microsoft cloud services," the Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0366 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0366/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0366/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:31:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0365 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0365/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0365/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0364 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0364/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0364/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:22:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0363 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0363/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0363/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:13:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0362 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le greffon Media Streaming de Qnap (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0362/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0362/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T11:09:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le greffon Media Streaming de Qnap. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Guide Explains How to Eliminate the Risk of Shadow SaaS and Protect Corporate Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-guide-explains-how-to-eliminate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-guide-explains-how-to-eliminate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications are dominating the corporate landscape. Their increased use enables organizations to push the boundaries of technology and business. At the same time, these applications also pose a new security risk that security leaders need to address, since the existing security stack does not enable complete control or comprehensive monitoring of their usage.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSA, FBI Alert on N. Korean Hackers Spoofing Emails from Trusted Sources]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/nsa-fbi-alert-on-n-korean-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/nsa-fbi-alert-on-n-korean-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Thursday published a new cybersecurity advisory warning of North Korean threat actors' attempts to send emails in a manner that makes them appear like they are from legitimate and trusted parties.
The joint bulletin was published by the National Security Agency (NSA), the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), and the Department of State.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Announces Passkeys Adopted by Over 400 Million Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-announces-passkeys-adopted-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-announces-passkeys-adopted-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T06:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Thursday announced that passkeys are being used by over 400 million Google accounts, authenticating users more than 1 billion times over the past two years.
"Passkeys are easy to use and phishing resistant, only relying on a fingerprint, face scan or a pin making them 50% faster than passwords," Heather Adkins, vice president of security engineering at Google, said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0361 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans PostgreSQL pgAdmin (03 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0361/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0361/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T05:38:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PostgreSQL pgAdmin. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Four Critical Vulnerabilities Expose HPE Aruba Devices to RCE Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/four-critical-vulnerabilities-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/four-critical-vulnerabilities-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-03T04:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[HPE Aruba Networking (formerly Aruba Networks) has released security updates to address critical flaws impacting ArubaOS that could result in remote code execution (RCE) on affected systems.
Of the 10 security defects, four are rated critical in severity -

CVE-2024-26304 (CVSS score: 9.8) - Unauthenticated Buffer Overflow Vulnerability in the L2/L3 Management Service Accessed via]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Android Apps Like Xiaomi, WPS Office Vulnerable to File Overwrite Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/popular-android-apps-like-xiaomi-wps.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/popular-android-apps-like-xiaomi-wps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several popular Android applications available in Google Play Store are susceptible to a path traversal-affiliated vulnerability that could be exploited by a malicious app to overwrite arbitrary files in the vulnerable app's home directory.
"The implications of this vulnerability pattern include arbitrary code execution and token theft, depending on an application’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukrainian REvil Hacker Sentenced to 13 Years and Ordered to Pay $16 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ukrainian-revil-hacker-sentenced-to-13.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ukrainian-revil-hacker-sentenced-to-13.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T12:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Ukrainian national has been sentenced to more than 13 years in prison and ordered to pay $16 million in restitution for carrying out thousands of ransomware attacks and extorting victims.
Yaroslav Vasinskyi (aka Rabotnik), 24, along with his co-conspirators part of the REvil ransomware group orchestrated more than 2,500 ransomware attacks and demanded ransom payments in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[When is One Vulnerability Scanner Not Enough?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/when-is-one-vulnerability-scanner-not.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/when-is-one-vulnerability-scanner-not.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Like antivirus software, vulnerability scans rely on a database of known weaknesses.
That’s why websites like VirusTotal exist, to give cyber practitioners a chance to see whether a malware sample is detected by multiple virus scanning engines, but this concept hasn’t existed in the vulnerability management space.
The benefits of using multiple scanning engines 
Generally speaking]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dropbox Discloses Breach of Digital Signature Service Affecting All Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/dropbox-discloses-breach-of-digital.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/dropbox-discloses-breach-of-digital.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud storage services provider Dropbox on Wednesday disclosed that Dropbox Sign (formerly HelloSign) was breached by unidentified threat actors, who accessed emails, usernames, and general account settings associated with all users of the digital signature product.
The company, in a filing with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC), said it became aware of the "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New "Goldoon" Botnet Targets D-Link Routers With Decade-Old Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-goldoon-botnet-targets-d-link.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-goldoon-botnet-targets-d-link.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A never-before-seen botnet called Goldoon has been observed targeting D-Link routers with a nearly decade-old critical security flaw with the goal of using the compromised devices for further attacks.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2015-2051 (CVSS score: 9.8), which affects D-Link DIR-645 routers and allows remote attackers to execute arbitrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0360 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans dans SonicWall GMS (02 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0360/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0360/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T07:13:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SonicWall GMS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0359 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (02 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0359/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0359/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T06:50:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0358 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (02 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0358/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0358/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T06:48:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0357 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Cisco IP Phone (02 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0357/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0357/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T06:33:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Cisco IP Phone. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Active Exploitation of Severe GitLab Password Reset Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T06:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical flaw impacting GitLab to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, owing to active exploitation in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2023-7028 (CVSS score: 10.0), the maximum severity vulnerability could facilitate account takeover by sending password reset emails to an unverified email]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cuttlefish Malware Hijacks Router Connections, Sniffs for Cloud Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-cuttlefish-malware-hijacks-router.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-cuttlefish-malware-hijacks-router.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-02T05:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware called Cuttlefish is targeting small office and home office (SOHO) routers with the goal of stealthily monitoring all traffic through the devices and gather authentication data from HTTP GET and POST requests.
"This malware is modular, designed primarily to steal authentication material found in web requests that transit the router from the adjacent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bitcoin Forensic Analysis Uncovers Money Laundering Clusters and Criminal Proceeds]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/bitcoin-forensic-analysis-uncovers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/bitcoin-forensic-analysis-uncovers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A forensic analysis of a graph dataset containing transactions on the Bitcoin blockchain has revealed clusters associated with illicit activity and money laundering, including detecting criminal proceeds sent to a crypto exchange and previously unknown wallets belonging to a Russian darknet market.
The findings come from Elliptic in collaboration with researchers from the&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android Malware Wpeeper Uses Compromised WordPress Sites to Hide C2 Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/android-malware-wpeeper-uses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/android-malware-wpeeper-uses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T13:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a previously undocumented malware targeting Android devices that uses compromised WordPress sites as relays for its actual command-and-control (C2) servers for detection evasion.
The malware, codenamed Wpeeper, is an ELF binary that leverages the HTTPS protocol to secure its C2 communications.
"Wpeeper is a typical backdoor Trojan for Android]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone's an Expert: How to Empower Your Employees for Cybersecurity Success]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/everyones-expert-how-to-empower-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/everyones-expert-how-to-empower-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[There’s a natural human desire to avoid threatening scenarios. The irony, of course, is if you hope to attain any semblance of security, you’ve got to remain prepared to confront those very same threats.
As a decision-maker for your organization, you know this well. But no matter how many experts or trusted cybersecurity tools your organization has a standing guard,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZLoader Malware Evolves with Anti-Analysis Trick from Zeus Banking Trojan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/zloader-malware-evolves-with-anti.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/zloader-malware-evolves-with-anti.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T10:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The authors behind the resurfaced ZLoader malware have added a feature that was originally present in the Zeus banking trojan that it's based on, indicating that it's being actively developed.
"The latest version, 2.4.1.0, introduces a feature to prevent execution on machines that differ from the original infection," Zscaler ThreatLabz researcher Santiago]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-NSA Employee Sentenced to 22 Years for Trying to Sell U.S. Secrets to Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ex-nsa-employee-sentenced-to-22-years.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ex-nsa-employee-sentenced-to-22-years.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-01T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former employee of the U.S. National Security Agency (NSA) has been sentenced to nearly 22 years (262 months) in prison for attempting to transfer classified documents to Russia.
"This sentence should serve as a stark warning to all those entrusted with protecting national defense information that there are consequences to betraying that trust," said FBI Director Christopher Wray.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Millions of Malicious 'Imageless' Containers Planted on Docker Hub Over 5 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/millions-of-malicious-imageless.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/millions-of-malicious-imageless.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered multiple campaigns targeting Docker Hub by planting millions of malicious "imageless" containers over the past five years, once again underscoring how open-source registries could pave the way for supply chain attacks.
"Over four million of the repositories in Docker Hub are imageless and have no content except for the repository]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Government Releases New AI Security Guidelines for Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-government-releases-new-ai-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-government-releases-new-ai-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T10:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government has unveiled new security guidelines aimed at bolstering critical infrastructure against artificial intelligence (AI)-related threats.
"These guidelines are informed by the whole-of-government effort to assess AI risks across all sixteen critical infrastructure sectors, and address threats both to and from, and involving AI systems," the Department of Homeland Security (DHS)&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Considerations for Operational Technology Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/considerations-for-operational.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/considerations-for-operational.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Operational Technology (OT) refers to the hardware and software used to change, monitor, or control the enterprise's physical devices, processes, and events. Unlike traditional Information Technology (IT) systems, OT systems directly impact the physical world. This unique characteristic of OT brings additional cybersecurity considerations not typically present in conventional IT security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New U.K. Law Bans Default Passwords on Smart Devices Starting April 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-uk-law-bans-default-passwords-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-uk-law-bans-default-passwords-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T05:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. National Cyber Security Centre (NCSC) is calling on manufacturers of smart devices to comply with new legislation that prohibits them from using default passwords, effective April 29, 2024.
"The law, known as the Product Security and Telecommunications Infrastructure act (or PSTI act), will help consumers to choose smart devices that have been designed to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0356 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Nessus Network Monitor (30 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0356/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0356/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-30T05:19:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Nessus Network Monitor. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Prevented 2.28 Million Malicious Apps from Reaching Play Store in 2023]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/google-prevented-228-million-malicious.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/google-prevented-228-million-malicious.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T17:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Monday revealed that almost 200,000 app submissions to its Play Store for Android were either rejected or remediated to address issues with access to sensitive data such as location or SMS messages over the past year.
The tech giant also said it blocked 333,000 bad accounts from the app storefront in 2023 for attempting to distribute malware or for repeated policy violations.
"In 2023,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked 'Muddling Meerkat' Hijacks DNS to Map Internet on Global Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/china-linked-muddling-meerkat-hijacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/china-linked-muddling-meerkat-hijacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented cyber threat dubbed Muddling Meerkat has been observed undertaking sophisticated domain name system (DNS) activities in a likely effort to evade security measures and conduct reconnaissance of networks across the world since October 2019.
Cloud security firm Infoblox described the threat actor as likely affiliated with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0355 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (29 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0355/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0355/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T12:41:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-019 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-019 (29 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-019/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-019/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T11:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Navigating the Threat Landscape: Understanding Exposure Management, Pentesting, Red Teaming and RBVM]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/navigating-threat-landscape.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/navigating-threat-landscape.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It comes as no surprise that today's cyber threats are orders of magnitude more complex than those of the past. And the ever-evolving tactics that attackers use demand the adoption of better, more holistic and consolidated ways to meet this non-stop challenge. Security teams constantly look for ways to reduce risk while improving security posture, but many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New R Programming Vulnerability Exposes Projects to Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-r-programming-vulnerability-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-r-programming-vulnerability-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security vulnerability has been discovered in the R programming language that could be exploited by a threat actor to create a malicious RDS (R Data Serialization) file such that it results in code execution when loaded and referenced.
The flaw, assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-27322, "involves the use of promise objects and lazy evaluation in R," AI application security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sandbox Escape Vulnerabilities in Judge0 Expose Systems to Complete Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/sandbox-escape-vulnerabilities-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/sandbox-escape-vulnerabilities-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple critical security flaws have been disclosed in the Judge0 open-source online code execution system that could be exploited to obtain code execution on the target system.
The three flaws, all critical in nature, allow an "adversary with sufficient access to perform a sandbox escape and obtain root permissions on the host machine," Australian]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0354 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (29 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0354/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0354/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-29T07:58:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta Warns of Unprecedented Surge in Proxy-Driven Credential Stuffing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/okta-warns-of-unprecedented-surge-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/okta-warns-of-unprecedented-surge-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-28T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identity and access management (IAM) services provider Okta has warned of a spike in the "frequency and scale" of credential stuffing attacks aimed at online services.
These unprecedented attacks, observed over the last month, are said to be facilitated by "the broad availability of residential proxy services, lists of previously stolen credentials ('combo lists'), and scripting tools," the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Targeted in Cyberattack Exploiting 7-Year-Old Microsoft Office Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ukraine-targeted-in-cyberattack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ukraine-targeted-in-cyberattack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T12:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a targeted operation against Ukraine that has been found leveraging a nearly seven-year-old flaw in Microsoft Office to deliver Cobalt Strike on compromised systems.
The attack chain, which took place at the end of 2023 according to Deep Instinct, employs a PowerPoint slideshow file ("signal-2023-12-20-160512.ppsx") as the starting point, with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bogus npm Packages Used to Trick Software Developers into Installing Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/bogus-npm-packages-used-to-trick.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/bogus-npm-packages-used-to-trick.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-27T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing social engineering campaign is targeting software developers with bogus npm packages under the guise of a job interview to trick them into downloading a Python backdoor.
Cybersecurity firm Securonix is tracking the activity under the name DEV#POPPER, linking it to North Korean threat actors.
"During these fraudulent interviews, the developers are often asked]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Severe Flaws Disclosed in Brocade SANnav SAN Management Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/severe-flaws-disclosed-in-brocade.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/severe-flaws-disclosed-in-brocade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T14:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several security vulnerabilities disclosed in Brocade SANnav storage area network (SAN) management application could be exploited to compromise susceptible appliances.
The 18 flaws impact all versions up to and including 2.3.0, according to independent security researcher Pierre Barre, who discovered and reported them.
The issues range from incorrect firewall rules,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0353 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (26 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0353/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0353/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:39:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0352 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (26 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0352/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0352/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T12:36:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0351 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (26 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0351/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0351/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:51:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0350 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (26 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0350/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0350/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:27:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0349 : [SCADA] Vulnérabilité dans les produits Belden (26 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0349/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0349/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T11:11:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Belden. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité..]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10 Critical Endpoint Security Tips You Should Know]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/10-critical-endpoint-security-tips-you.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/10-critical-endpoint-security-tips-you.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T10:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, where connectivity is rules all, endpoints serve as the gateway to a business’s digital kingdom. And because of this, endpoints are one of hackers' favorite targets. 
According to the IDC, 70% of successful breaches start at the endpoint. Unprotected endpoints provide vulnerable entry points to launch devastating cyberattacks. With IT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'Brokewell' Android Malware Spread Through Fake Browser Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-brokewell-android-malware-spread.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-brokewell-android-malware-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fake browser updates are being used to push a previously undocumented Android malware called Brokewell.
"Brokewell is a typical modern banking malware equipped with both data-stealing and remote-control capabilities built into the malware," Dutch security firm ThreatFabric said in an analysis published Thursday.
The malware is said to be in active development,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks Outlines Remediation for Critical PAN-OS Flaw Under Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-outlines-remediation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-outlines-remediation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks has shared remediation guidance for a recently disclosed critical security flaw impacting PAN-OS that has come under active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-3400 (CVSS score: 10.0), could be weaponized to obtain unauthenticated remote shell command execution on susceptible devices. It has been addressed in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting WP-Automatic Plugin Bug to Create Admin Accounts on WordPress Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploiting-wp-automatic-plugin.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploiting-wp-automatic-plugin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-26T05:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are attempting to actively exploit a critical security flaw in the WP‑Automatic plugin for WordPress that could allow site takeovers.
The shortcoming, tracked as CVE-2024-27956, carries a CVSS score of 9.9 out of a maximum of 10. It impacts all versions of the plugin prior to 3.9.2.0.
"This vulnerability, a SQL injection (SQLi) flaw, poses a severe threat as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea's Lazarus Group Deploys New Kaolin RAT via Fake Job Lures]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/north-koreas-lazarus-group-deploys-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/north-koreas-lazarus-group-deploys-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Lazarus Group employed its time-tested fabricated job lures to deliver a new remote access trojan called Kaolin RAT.
The malware could, "aside from standard RAT functionality, change the last write timestamp of a selected file and load any received DLL binary from [command-and-control] server," Avast security researcher Luigino]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ALE-007 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-007/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-007/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T16:18:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 24 avril 2024, Cisco a publié trois avis de sécurité concernant des vulnérabilités affectant les équipements de sécurité ASA et FTD.
 Deux d'entre eux concernent les vulnérabilités CVE-2024-20353 et CVE-2024-20359 qui sont activement exploitées dans le cadre d'attaques ciblées.
 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0348 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits MongoDB (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0348/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0348/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits MongoDB. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Network Threats: A Step-by-Step Attack Demonstration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/network-threats-step-by-step-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/network-threats-step-by-step-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T11:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Follow this real-life network attack simulation, covering 6 steps from Initial Access to Data Exfiltration. See how attackers remain undetected with the simplest tools and why you need multiple choke points in your defense strategy.
Surprisingly, most network attacks are not exceptionally sophisticated, technologically advanced, or reliant on zero-day tools that exploit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Arrests Founders of Crypto Mixer Samourai for $2 Billion in Illegal Transactions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/doj-arrests-founders-of-crypto-mixer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/doj-arrests-founders-of-crypto-mixer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Wednesday announced the arrest of two co-founders of a cryptocurrency mixer called Samourai and seized the service for allegedly facilitating over $2 billion in illegal transactions and for laundering more than $100 million in criminal proceeds.
To that end, Keonne Rodriguez, 35, and William Lonergan Hill, 65, have been charged]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0347 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0347/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0347/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T09:05:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service à distance.
 Cisco indique que les vulnérabilités CVE-2024-20353 et CVE-2024-20359 …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0346 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0346/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0346/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T09:00:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0345 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0345/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0345/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T08:48:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une preuve de concept a été publiée affectant l'agent Cortex XDR de Palo Alto Networks. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0344 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (25 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0344/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0344/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T08:33:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Postpones Third-Party Cookie Deprecation Amid U.K. Regulatory Scrutiny]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/google-postpones-third-party-cookie.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/google-postpones-third-party-cookie.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T06:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has once again pushed its plans to deprecate third-party tracking cookies in its Chrome web browser as it works to address outstanding competition concerns from U.K. regulators over its Privacy Sandbox initiative.
The tech giant said it's working closely with the U.K. Competition and Markets Authority (CMA) and hopes to achieve an agreement by the end of the year.
As part of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[State-Sponsored Hackers Exploit Two Cisco Zero-Day Vulnerabilities for Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/state-sponsored-hackers-exploit-two.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/state-sponsored-hackers-exploit-two.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-25T05:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware campaign leveraged two zero-day flaws in Cisco networking gear to deliver custom malware and facilitate covert data collection on target environments.
Cisco Talos, which dubbed the activity ArcaneDoor, attributing it as the handiwork of a previously undocumented sophisticated state-sponsored actor it tracks under the name UAT4356 (aka Storm-1849 by Microsoft).
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Sanctions Iranian Firms and Individuals Tied to Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-treasury-sanctions-iranian-firms-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-treasury-sanctions-iranian-firms-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) on Monday sanctioned two firms and four individuals for their involvement in malicious cyber activities on behalf of the Iranian Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps Cyber Electronic Command (IRGC-CEC) from at least 2016 to April 2021.
This includes the front companies Mehrsam Andisheh Saz Nik (MASN) and Dadeh]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Detail Multistage Attack Hijacking Systems with SSLoad, Cobalt Strike]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-detail-multistage-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-detail-multistage-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an ongoing attack campaign that's leveraging phishing emails to deliver malware called SSLoad.
The campaign, codenamed FROZEN#SHADOW by Securonix, also involves the deployment of Cobalt Strike and the ConnectWise ScreenConnect remote desktop software.
"SSLoad is designed to stealthily infiltrate systems, gather sensitive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0343 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (24 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0343/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0343/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T11:37:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Major Security Flaws Expose Keystrokes of Over 1 Billion Chinese Keyboard App Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/major-security-flaws-expose-keystrokes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/major-security-flaws-expose-keystrokes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security vulnerabilities uncovered in cloud-based pinyin keyboard apps could be exploited to reveal users' keystrokes to nefarious actors.
The findings come from the Citizen Lab, which discovered weaknesses in eight of nine apps from vendors like Baidu, Honor, iFlytek, OPPO, Samsung, Tencent, Vivo, and Xiaomi. The only vendor whose keyboard app did not have any security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISO Perspectives on Complying with Cybersecurity Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ciso-perspectives-on-complying-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ciso-perspectives-on-complying-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Compliance requirements are meant to increase cybersecurity transparency and accountability. As cyber threats increase, so do the number of compliance frameworks and the specificity of the security controls, policies, and activities they include.
For CISOs and their teams, that means compliance is a time-consuming, high-stakes process that demands strong organizational and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0342 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans NagiosXI (24 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0342/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0342/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T09:22:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans NagiosXI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[eScan Antivirus Update Mechanism Exploited to Spread Backdoors and Miners]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/escan-antivirus-update-mechanism.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/escan-antivirus-update-mechanism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware campaign has been exploiting the updating mechanism of the eScan antivirus software to distribute backdoors and cryptocurrency miners like XMRig through a long-standing threat codenamed GuptiMiner targeting large corporate networks.
Cybersecurity firm Avast said the activity is the work of a threat actor with possible connections to a North Korean hacking group dubbed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CoralRaider Malware Campaign Exploits CDN Cache to Spread Info-Stealers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/coralraider-malware-campaign-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/coralraider-malware-campaign-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-24T04:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new ongoing malware campaign has been observed distributing three different stealers, such as CryptBot, LummaC2, and Rhadamanthys hosted on Content Delivery Network (CDN) cache domains since at least February 2024.
Cisco Talos has attributed the activity with moderate confidence to a threat actor tracked as CoralRaider, a suspected Vietnamese-origin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache Cordova App Harness Targeted in Dependency Confusion Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/apache-cordova-app-harness-targeted-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/apache-cordova-app-harness-targeted-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have identified a dependency confusion vulnerability impacting an archived Apache project called Cordova App Harness.
Dependency confusion attacks take place owing to the fact that package managers check the public repositories before private registries, thus allowing a threat actor to publish a malicious package with the same name to a public package repository.
This&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Learn Proactive Supply Chain Threat Hunting Techniques]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/webinar-learn-proactive-supply-chain.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/webinar-learn-proactive-supply-chain.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T11:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the high-stakes world of cybersecurity, the battleground has shifted. Supply chain attacks have emerged as a potent threat, exploiting the intricate web of interconnected systems and third-party dependencies to breach even the most formidable defenses. But what if you could turn the tables and proactively hunt these threats before they wreak havoc?
We invite you to join us for an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unmasking the True Cost of Cyberattacks: Beyond Ransom and Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/unmasking-true-cost-of-cyberattacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/unmasking-true-cost-of-cyberattacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T10:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity breaches can be devastating for both individuals and businesses alike. While many people tend to focus on understanding how and why they were targeted by such breaches, there's a larger, more pressing question: What is the true financial impact of a cyberattack? According to research by Cybersecurity Ventures, the global cost of cybercrime is projected to reach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Police Chiefs Call for Solutions to Access Encrypted Data in Serious Crime Cases]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/police-chiefs-call-for-solutions-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/police-chiefs-call-for-solutions-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[European Police Chiefs said that the complementary partnership between law enforcement agencies and the technology industry is at risk due to end-to-end encryption (E2EE).
They called on the industry and governments to take urgent action to ensure public safety across social media platforms.
"Privacy measures currently being rolled out, such as end-to-end encryption, will stop tech companies]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Authorities Issue Arrest Warrants for Three Suspected Chinese Spies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/german-authorities-issue-arrest.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/german-authorities-issue-arrest.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German authorities said they have issued arrest warrants against three citizens on suspicion of spying for China.
The full names of the defendants were not disclosed by the Office of the Federal Prosecutor (aka Generalbundesanwalt), but it includes Herwig F., Ina F., and Thomas R.
"The suspects are strongly suspected of working for a Chinese secret service since an unspecified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Imposes Visa Restrictions on 13 Linked to Commercial Spyware Misuse]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-imposes-visa-restrictions-on-13.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-imposes-visa-restrictions-on-13.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T06:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of State on Monday said it's taking steps to impose visa restrictions on 13 individuals who are allegedly involved in the development and sale of commercial spyware or who are immediately family members of those involved in such businesses.
"These individuals have facilitated or derived financial benefit from the misuse of this technology, which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia's APT28 Exploited Windows Print Spooler Flaw to Deploy 'GooseEgg' Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russias-apt28-exploited-windows-print.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russias-apt28-exploited-windows-print.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-23T04:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russia-linked nation-state threat actor tracked as APT28 weaponized a security flaw in the Microsoft Windows Print Spooler component to deliver a previously unknown custom malware called GooseEgg.
The post-compromise tool, which is said to have been used since at least June 2020 and possibly as early as April 2019, leveraged a now-patched flaw that allowed for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacker Group ToddyCat Uses Advanced Tools for Industrial-Scale Data Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russian-hacker-group-toddycat-uses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russian-hacker-group-toddycat-uses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T15:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as ToddyCat has been observed using a wide range of tools to retain access to compromised environments and steal valuable data.
Russian cybersecurity firm Kaspersky characterized the adversary as relying on various programs to harvest data on an "industrial scale" from primarily governmental organizations, some of them defense related, located in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-018 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-018 (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-018/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-018/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T13:17:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0341 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0341/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0341/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T11:44:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pentera's 2024 Report Reveals Hundreds of Security Events per Week, Highlighting the Criticality of Continuous Validation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/penteras-2024-report-reveals-hundreds.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/penteras-2024-report-reveals-hundreds.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over the past two years, a shocking 51% of organizations surveyed in a leading industry report have been compromised by a cyberattack. Yes, over half. 
And this, in a world where enterprises deploy an average of 53 different security solutions to safeguard their digital domain. 
Alarming? Absolutely.
A recent survey of CISOs and CIOs, commissioned by Pentera and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0340 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0340/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0340/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T11:27:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE Corporation Breached by Nation-State Hackers Exploiting Ivanti Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/mitre-corporation-breached-by-nation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/mitre-corporation-breached-by-nation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MITRE Corporation revealed that it was the target of a nation-state cyber attack that exploited two zero-day flaws in Ivanti Connect Secure appliances starting in January 2024.
The intrusion led to the compromise of its Networked Experimentation, Research, and Virtualization Environment (NERVE), an unclassified research and prototyping network.
The unknown adversary "performed reconnaissance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Double-Dip: Re-Victimization in Cyber Extortion]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ransomware-double-dip-re-victimization.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ransomware-double-dip-re-victimization.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T10:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Between crossovers - Do threat actors play dirty or desperate? 
In our dataset of over 11,000 victim organizations that have experienced a Cyber Extortion / Ransomware attack, we noticed that some victims re-occur. Consequently, the question arises why we observe a re-victimization and whether or not this is an actual second attack, an affiliate crossover (meaning an affiliate has gone to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Windows Flaws Granting Hackers Rootkit-Like Powers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-uncover-windows-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-uncover-windows-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research has found that the DOS-to-NT path conversion process could be exploited by threat actors to achieve rootkit-like capabilities to conceal and impersonate files, directories, and processes.
"When a user executes a function that has a path argument in Windows, the DOS path at which the file or folder exists is converted to an NT path," SafeBreach security researcher Or Yair said&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0339 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0339/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0339/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T08:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0338 : [SCADA] Vulnérabilité dans Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808 (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0338/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0338/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T08:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Siemens RUGGEDCOM APE1808. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0337 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mozilla Thunderbird (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0337/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0337/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T08:14:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mozilla Thunderbird. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0336 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits OwnCloud (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0336/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0336/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T08:09:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits OwnCloud. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0335 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Platform (22 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0335/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0335/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T08:06:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Platform. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns: North Korean Hackers Turn to AI-Fueled Cyber Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/microsoft-warns-north-korean-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/microsoft-warns-north-korean-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-22T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has revealed that North Korea-linked state-sponsored cyber actors has begun to use artificial intelligence (AI) to make its operations more effective and efficient.
"They are learning to use tools powered by AI large language models (LLM) to make their operations more efficient and effective," the tech giant said in its latest report on East Asia hacking groups.
The company]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New RedLine Stealer Variant Disguised as Game Cheats Using Lua Bytecode for Stealth]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-redline-stealer-variant-disguised.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-redline-stealer-variant-disguised.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-21T08:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new information stealer has been found leveraging Lua bytecode for added stealth and sophistication, findings from McAfee Labs reveal.
The cybersecurity firm has assessed it to be a variant of a known malware called RedLine Stealer owing to the fact that the command-and-control (C2) server IP address has been previously identified as associated with the malware.
RedLine Stealer,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks Discloses More Details on Critical PAN-OS Flaw Under Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-discloses-more.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-discloses-more.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-20T05:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks has shared more details of a critical security flaw impacting PAN-OS that has come under active exploitation in the wild by malicious actors.
The company described the vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-3400 (CVSS score: 10.0), as "intricate" and a combination of two bugs in versions PAN-OS 10.2, PAN-OS 11.0, and PAN-OS 11.1 of the software.
"In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Update: CrushFTP Zero-Day Flaw Exploited in Targeted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-update-crushftp-zero-day-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-update-crushftp-zero-day-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-20T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of the CrushFTP enterprise file transfer software are being urged to update to the latest version following the discovery of a security flaw that has come under targeted exploitation in the wild.
"CrushFTP v11 versions below 11.1 have a vulnerability where users can escape their VFS and download system files," CrushFTP said in an advisory released Friday.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackTech Targets Tech, Research, and Gov Sectors New 'Deuterbear' Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/blacktech-targets-tech-research-and-gov.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/blacktech-targets-tech-research-and-gov.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T13:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technology, research, and government sectors in the Asia-Pacific region have been targeted by a threat actor called BlackTech as part of a recent cyber attack wave.
The intrusions pave the way for an updated version of modular backdoor dubbed Waterbear as well as its enhanced successor referred to as Deuterbear.
"Waterbear is known for its complexity, as it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0334 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0334/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0334/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T12:57:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0333 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0333/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0333/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T12:42:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un déni de service à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0332 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Red Hat (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0332/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0332/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T12:25:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0331 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans SolarWinds Platform (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0331/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0331/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T12:13:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SolarWinds Platform. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0330 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0330/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0330/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:51:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0329 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0329/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0329/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:40:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Attackers Can Own a Business Without Touching the Endpoint]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/showcasing-networkless-identity-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/showcasing-networkless-identity-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are increasingly making use of “networkless” attack techniques targeting cloud apps and identities. Here’s how attackers can (and are) compromising organizations – without ever needing to touch the endpoint or conventional networked systems and services. 
Before getting into the details of the attack techniques being used, let’s discuss why]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Akira Ransomware Gang Extorts $42 Million; Now Targets Linux Servers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/akira-ransomware-gang-extorts-42.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/akira-ransomware-gang-extorts-42.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors behind the Akira ransomware group have extorted approximately $42 million in illicit proceeds after breaching the networks of more than 250 victims as of January 1, 2024.
"Since March 2023, Akira ransomware has impacted a wide range of businesses and critical infrastructure entities in North America, Europe, and Australia," cybersecurity agencies from the Netherlands and the U.S.,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0328 : Vulnérabilité dans Citrix uberAgent (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0328/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0328/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T07:26:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Citrix uberAgent. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0327 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (19 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0327/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0327/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T07:09:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target Middle East Governments with Evasive "CR4T" Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-target-middle-east-governments.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-target-middle-east-governments.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-19T06:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Government entities in the Middle East have been targeted as part of a previously undocumented campaign to deliver a new backdoor dubbed CR4T.
Russian cybersecurity company Kaspersky said it discovered the activity in February 2024, with evidence suggesting that it may have been active since at least a year prior. The campaign has been codenamed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OfflRouter Malware Evades Detection in Ukraine for Almost a Decade]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/offlrouter-malware-evades-detection-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/offlrouter-malware-evades-detection-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Select Ukrainian government networks have remained infected with a malware called OfflRouter since 2015.
Cisco Talos said its findings are based on an analysis of over 100 confidential documents that were infected with the VBA macro virus and uploaded to the VirusTotal malware scanning platform.
"The documents contained VBA code to drop and run an executable with the name 'ctrlpanel.exe,'"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIN7 Cybercrime Group Targeting U.S. Auto Industry with Carbanak Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/fin7-cybercrime-group-targeting-us-auto.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/fin7-cybercrime-group-targeting-us-auto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous cybercrime syndicate known as FIN7 has been linked to a spear-phishing campaign targeting the U.S. automotive industry to deliver a known backdoor called Carbanak (aka Anunak).
"FIN7 identified employees at the company who worked in the IT department and had higher levels of administrative rights," the BlackBerry research and intelligence team said in a new write-up.
"They]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0326 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle MySQL (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0326/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0326/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:46:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle MySQL. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0325 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle PeopleSoft (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0325/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0325/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:45:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle PeopleSoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0324 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Systems (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0324/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0324/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:45:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Systems. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0323 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Weblogic (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0323/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0323/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Weblogic. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0322 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Database Server (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0322/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0322/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:44:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Database Server. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0321 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle Java SE (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0321/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0321/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle Java SE . Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0320 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Oracle VirtualBox (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0320/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0320/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T13:42:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Oracle VirtualBox. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recover from Ransomware in 5 Minutes—We will Teach You How!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/recover-from-ransomware-in-5-minuteswe.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/recover-from-ransomware-in-5-minuteswe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Super Low RPO with Continuous Data Protection:Dial Back to Just Seconds Before an Attack
Zerto, a Hewlett Packard Enterprise company, can help you detect and recover from ransomware in near real-time. This solution leverages continuous data protection (CDP) to ensure all workloads have the lowest recovery point objective (RPO) possible. The most valuable thing about CDP is that it does not use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Trojan 'SoumniBot' Evades Detection with Clever Tricks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-android-trojan-soumnibot-evades.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/new-android-trojan-soumnibot-evades.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Android trojan called SoumniBot has been detected in the wild targeting users in South Korea by leveraging weaknesses in the manifest extraction and parsing procedure.
The malware is "notable for an unconventional approach to evading analysis and detection, namely obfuscation of the Android manifest," Kaspersky researcher Dmitry Kalinin said in a technical analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Conduct Advanced Static Analysis in a Malware Sandbox]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/how-to-conduct-advanced-static-analysis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/how-to-conduct-advanced-static-analysis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sandboxes are synonymous with dynamic malware analysis. They help to execute malicious files in a safe virtual environment and observe their behavior. However, they also offer plenty of value in terms of static analysis. See these five scenarios where a sandbox can prove to be a useful tool in your investigations.
Detecting Threats in PDFs
PDF files are frequently exploited by threat actors to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Police Operation Disrupts 'LabHost' Phishing Service, Over 30 Arrested Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/global-police-operation-disrupts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/global-police-operation-disrupts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 37 individuals have been arrested as part of an international crackdown on a cybercrime service called LabHost that has been used by criminal actors to steal personal credentials from victims around the world.
Described as one of the largest Phishing-as-a-Service (PhaaS) providers, LabHost offered phishing pages targeting banks, high-profile organizations, and other service]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0319 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0319/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0319/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T07:30:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.
 Cisco a indiqué avoir connaissance d'une preuve de concept …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0318 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0318/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0318/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T07:09:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0317 : Vulnérabilité dans Cisco ClamAV (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0317/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0317/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T07:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Cisco ClamAV. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0316 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Xen (18 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0316/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0316/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T06:54:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Xen. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit OpenMetadata Flaws to Mine Crypto on Kubernetes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploit-openmetadata-flaws-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploit-openmetadata-flaws-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively exploiting critical vulnerabilities in OpenMetadata to gain unauthorized access to Kubernetes workloads and leverage them for cryptocurrency mining activity.
That's according to the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team, which said the flaws have been weaponized since the start of April 2024.
OpenMetadata is an open-source platform that operates as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Google Ads Pushing Fake IP Scanner Software with Hidden Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/malicious-google-ads-pushing-fake-ip.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/malicious-google-ads-pushing-fake-ip.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-18T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Google malvertising campaign is leveraging a cluster of domains mimicking a legitimate IP scanner software to deliver a previously unknown backdoor dubbed MadMxShell.
"The threat actor registered multiple look-alike domains using a typosquatting technique and leveraged Google Ads to push these domains to the top of search engine results targeting specific search keywords, thereby]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian APT Deploys New 'Kapeka' Backdoor in Eastern European Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russian-apt-deploys-new-kapeka-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/russian-apt-deploys-new-kapeka-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented "flexible" backdoor called Kapeka has been "sporadically" observed in cyber attacks targeting Eastern Europe, including Estonia and Ukraine, since at least mid-2022.
The findings come from Finnish cybersecurity firm WithSecure, which attributed the malware to the Russia-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) group tracked as Sandworm (aka APT44 or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-CTI-003 : Grands évènements sportifs en France – Évaluation de la menace 2024 (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-003/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-003/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T11:24:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Depuis plus d’une décennie, les compétitions sportives internationales majeures font régulièrement l’objet d’attaques informatiques. Ces …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0315 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Serv-U (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0315/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0315/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T11:14:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Serv-U. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GenAI: A New Headache for SaaS Security Teams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/genai-new-headache-for-saas-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/genai-new-headache-for-saas-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The introduction of Open AI’s ChatGPT was a defining moment for the software industry, touching off a GenAI race with its November 2022 release. SaaS vendors are now rushing to upgrade tools with enhanced productivity capabilities that are driven by generative AI.
Among a wide range of uses, GenAI tools make it easier for developers to build software, assist sales teams in mundane email writing,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Atlassian Flaw Exploited to Deploy Linux Variant of Cerber Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-atlassian-flaw-exploited-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-atlassian-flaw-exploited-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T10:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are exploiting unpatched Atlassian servers to deploy a Linux variant of Cerber (aka C3RB3R) ransomware.
The attacks leverage CVE-2023-22518 (CVSS score: 9.1), a critical security vulnerability impacting the Atlassian Confluence Data Center and Server that allows an unauthenticated attacker to reset Confluence and create an administrator account.
Armed with this access, a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Fortinet Flaw, Deploy ScreenConnect, Metasploit in New Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploit-fortinet-flaw-deploy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-exploit-fortinet-flaw-deploy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new campaign that's exploiting a recently disclosed security flaw in Fortinet FortiClient EMS devices to deliver ScreenConnect and Metasploit Powerfun payloads.
The activity entails the exploitation of CVE-2023-48788 (CVSS score: 9.3), a critical SQL injection flaw that could permit an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0314 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ivanti Avalanche (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0314/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0314/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T09:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ivanti Avalanche. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0313 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0313/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0313/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T09:16:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Warns of Global Surge in Brute-Force Attacks Targeting VPN and SSH Services]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/cisco-warns-of-global-surge-in-brute.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/cisco-warns-of-global-surge-in-brute.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T08:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco is warning about a global surge in brute-force attacks targeting various devices, including Virtual Private Network (VPN) services, web application authentication interfaces, and SSH services, since at least March 18, 2024.
"These attacks all appear to be originating from TOR exit nodes and a range of other anonymizing tunnels and proxies," Cisco Talos said.
Successful attacks could]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0312 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0312/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0312/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T08:30:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0311 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (17 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0311/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0311/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-17T07:36:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenJS Foundation Targeted in Potential JavaScript Project Takeover Attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/openjs-foundation-targeted-in-potential.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/openjs-foundation-targeted-in-potential.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have uncovered a "credible" takeover attempt targeting the OpenJS Foundation in a manner that evokes similarities to the recently uncovered incident aimed at the open-source XZ Utils project.
"The OpenJS Foundation Cross Project Council received a suspicious series of emails with similar messages, bearing different names and overlapping GitHub-associated emails," OpenJS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TA558 Hackers Weaponize Images for Wide-Scale Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ta558-hackers-weaponize-images-for-wide.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ta558-hackers-weaponize-images-for-wide.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T13:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor tracked as TA558 has been observed leveraging steganography as an obfuscation technique to deliver a wide range of malware such as Agent Tesla, FormBook, Remcos RAT, LokiBot, GuLoader, Snake Keylogger, and XWorm, among others.
"The group made extensive use of steganography by sending VBSs, PowerShell code, as well as RTF documents with an embedded exploit, inside]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS, Google, and Azure CLI Tools Could Leak Credentials in Build Logs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/aws-google-and-azure-cli-tools-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/aws-google-and-azure-cli-tools-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New cybersecurity research has found that command-line interface (CLI) tools from Amazon Web Services (AWS) and Google Cloud can expose sensitive credentials in build logs, posing significant risks to organizations.
The vulnerability has been codenamed LeakyCLI by cloud security firm Orca.
"Some commands on Azure CLI, AWS CLI, and Google Cloud CLI can expose sensitive information in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0310 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Juniper (16 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0310/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0310/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T11:47:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Juniper. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Widely-Used PuTTY SSH Client Found Vulnerable to Key Recovery Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/widely-used-putty-ssh-client-found.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/widely-used-putty-ssh-client-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of the PuTTY Secure Shell (SSH) and Telnet client are alerting users of a critical vulnerability impacting versions from 0.68 through 0.80 that could be exploited to achieve full recovery of NIST P-521 (ecdsa-sha2-nistp521) private keys.
The flaw has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-31497, with the discovery credited to researchers Fabian Bäumer and Marcus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identity in the Shadows: Shedding Light on Cybersecurity's Unseen Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/identity-in-shadows-shedding-light-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/identity-in-shadows-shedding-light-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly evolving digital landscape, organizations face an increasingly complex array of cybersecurity threats. The proliferation of cloud services and remote work arrangements has heightened the vulnerability of digital identities to exploitation, making it imperative for businesses to fortify their identity security measures.
Our recent research report, The Identity Underground]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC Fines Mental Health Startup Cerebral $7 Million for Major Privacy Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ftc-fines-mental-health-startup.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ftc-fines-mental-health-startup.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T08:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has ordered the mental telehealth company Cerebral from using or disclosing personal data for advertising purposes.
It has also been fined more than $7 million over charges that it revealed users' sensitive personal health information and other data to third parties for advertising purposes and failed to honor its easy cancellation policies.
"Cerebral and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hive RAT Creators and $3.5M Cryptojacking Mastermind Arrested in Global Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hive-rat-creators-and-35m-cryptojacking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hive-rat-creators-and-35m-cryptojacking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two individuals have been arrested in Australia and the U.S. in connection with an alleged scheme to develop and distribute a remote access trojan called Hive RAT (previously Firebird).
The U.S. Justice Department (DoJ) said the malware "gave the malware purchasers control over victim computers and enabled them to access victims' private communications, their login credentials, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0309 : Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (16 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0309/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0309/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-16T06:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Stormshield Network Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Intel and Lenovo BMCs Contain Unpatched Lighttpd Server Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/intel-and-lenovo-bmcs-contain-unpatched.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/intel-and-lenovo-bmcs-contain-unpatched.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T16:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A security flaw impacting the Lighttpd web server used in baseboard management controllers (BMCs) has remained unpatched by device vendors like Intel and Lenovo, new findings from Binarly reveal.
While the original shortcoming was discovered and patched by the Lighttpd maintainers way back in August 2018 with version 1.4.51, the lack of a CVE identifier or an advisory meant that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-017 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-017 (15 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-017/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-017/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T14:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Copilot: Launching Innovation Rockets, But Beware of the Darkness Ahead]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ai-copilot-launching-innovation-rockets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ai-copilot-launching-innovation-rockets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a world where the software that powers your favorite apps, secures your online transactions, and keeps your digital life could be outsmarted and taken over by a cleverly disguised piece of code. This isn't a plot from the latest cyber-thriller; it's actually been a reality for years now. How this will change – in a positive or negative direction – as artificial intelligence (AI) takes on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muddled Libra Shifts Focus to SaaS and Cloud for Extortion and Data Theft Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/muddled-libra-shifts-focus-to-saas-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/muddled-libra-shifts-focus-to-saas-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Muddled Libra has been observed actively targeting software-as-a-service (SaaS) applications and cloud service provider (CSP) environments in a bid to exfiltrate sensitive data.
"Organizations often store a variety of data in SaaS applications and use services from CSPs," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 said in a report published last week.
"The threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0308 : Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (15 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0308/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0308/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T11:43:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Stormshield Network Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Timing is Everything: The Role of Just-in-Time Privileged Access in Security Evolution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/timing-is-everything-role-of-just-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/timing-is-everything-role-of-just-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[To minimize the risk of privilege misuse, a trend in the privileged access management (PAM) solution market involves implementing just-in-time (JIT) privileged access. This approach to privileged identity management aims to mitigate the risks associated with prolonged high-level access by granting privileges temporarily and only when necessary, rather than providing users with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-Linked LightSpy iOS Spyware Targets South Asian iPhone Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/chinese-linked-lightspy-ios-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/chinese-linked-lightspy-ios-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a "renewed" cyber espionage campaign targeting users in South Asia with the aim of delivering an Apple iOS spyware implant called LightSpy.
"The latest iteration of LightSpy, dubbed 'F_Warehouse,' boasts a modular framework with extensive spying features," the BlackBerry Threat Research and Intelligence Team said in a report published last]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0307 : Vulnérabilité dans Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect (15 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0307/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0307/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T08:23:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Palo Alto Networks Global Protect. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks Releases Urgent Fixes for Exploited PAN-OS Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-releases-urgent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/palo-alto-networks-releases-urgent.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks has released hotfixes to address a maximum-severity security flaw impacting PAN-OS software that has come under active exploitation in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-3400 (CVSS score: 10.0), the critical vulnerability is a case of command injection in the GlobalProtect feature that an unauthenticated attacker could weaponize to execute arbitrary code with root]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0306 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (15 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0306/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0306/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-15T07:49:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Security Engineer Jailed 3 Years for $12.3 Million Crypto Exchange Thefts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ex-security-engineer-jailed-3-years-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ex-security-engineer-jailed-3-years-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former security engineer has been sentenced to three years in prison in the U.S. for charges relating to hacking two decentralized cryptocurrency exchanges in July 2022 and stealing over $12.3 million.
Shakeeb Ahmed, the defendant in question, pled guilty to one count of computer fraud in December 2023 following his arrest in July.
"At the time of both attacks,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Hamas Spokesperson for Cyber Influence Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-treasury-hamas-spokesperson-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-treasury-hamas-spokesperson-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T13:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) on Friday announced sanctions against an official associated with Hamas for his involvement in cyber influence operations.
Hudhayfa Samir ‘Abdallah al-Kahlut, 39, also known as Abu Ubaida, has served as the public spokesperson of Izz al-Din al-Qassam Brigades, the military wing of Hamas, since at least 2007.
"He publicly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Deploy Python Backdoor in Palo Alto Zero-Day Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-deploy-python-backdoor-in-palo.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-deploy-python-backdoor-in-palo.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-13T08:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been exploiting the newly disclosed zero-day flaw in Palo
  Alto Networks PAN-OS software dating back to March 26, 2024, nearly three
  weeks before it came to light yesterday.



  The network security company's Unit 42 division is tracking the activity under the name Operation MidnightEclipse, attributing it as the work of a single threat actor of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Popular Rust Crate liblzma-sys Compromised with XZ Utils Backdoor Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/popular-rust-crate-liblzma-sys.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/popular-rust-crate-liblzma-sys.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T14:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Test files" associated with the XZ Utils backdoor have made their way to a Rust crate known as liblzma-sys, new findings from Phylum reveal.
liblzma-sys, which has been downloaded over 21,000 times to date, provides Rust developers with bindings to the liblzma implementation, an underlying library that is part of the XZ Utils data compression software. The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0305 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0305/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0305/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T13:02:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0304 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Debian LTS buster (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0304/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0304/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:38:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits DebianLTS. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0303 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0303/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0303/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:38:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0302 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0302/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0302/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:37:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0301 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0301/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0301/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:36:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ALE-006 : Vulnérabilité dans Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-006/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-006/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T12:28:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.
 L'éditeur indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-3400 est utilisée dans des attaques ciblées.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Code Keepers: Mastering Non-Human Identity Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/code-keepers-mastering-non-human.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/code-keepers-mastering-non-human.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T11:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identities now transcend human boundaries. Within each line of code and every API call lies a non-human identity. These entities act as programmatic access keys, enabling authentication and facilitating interactions among systems and services, which are essential for every API call, database query, or storage account access. As we depend on multi-factor authentication and passwords to safeguard]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian MuddyWater Hackers Adopt New C2 Tool 'DarkBeatC2' in Latest Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/iranian-muddywater-hackers-adopt-new-c2.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/iranian-muddywater-hackers-adopt-new-c2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian threat actor known as MuddyWater has been attributed to a new command-and-control (C2) infrastructure called DarkBeatC2, becoming the latest such tool in its arsenal after SimpleHarm, MuddyC3, PhonyC2, and MuddyC2Go.
"While occasionally switching to a new remote administration tool or changing their C2 framework, MuddyWater’s methods remain constant," Deep]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zero-Day Alert: Critical Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS Flaw Under Active Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/zero-day-alert-critical-palo-alto.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/zero-day-alert-critical-palo-alto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T08:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Palo Alto Networks is warning that a critical flaw impacting its PAN-OS software used in its GlobalProtect gateways is being exploited in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-3400, the issue has a CVSS score of 10.0, indicating maximum severity.
"A command injection vulnerability in the GlobalProtect feature of Palo Alto Networks PAN-OS software for specific PAN-OS versions and distinct feature]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0300 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans PHP (12 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0300/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0300/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T06:56:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PHP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sneaky Credit Card Skimmer Disguised as Harmless Facebook Tracker]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/sneaky-credit-card-skimmer-disguised-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/sneaky-credit-card-skimmer-disguised-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T05:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a credit card skimmer that's concealed within a fake Meta Pixel tracker script in an attempt to evade detection.
Sucuri said that the malware is injected into websites through tools that allow for custom code, such as WordPress plugins like Simple Custom CSS and JS or the "Miscellaneous Scripts" section of the Magento admin panel.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Federal Agencies Ordered to Hunt for Signs of Microsoft Breach and Mitigate Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-federal-agencies-ordered-to-hunt-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/us-federal-agencies-ordered-to-hunt-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-12T04:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday issued an emergency directive (ED 24-02) urging federal agencies to hunt for signs of compromise and enact preventive measures following the recent compromise of Microsoft's systems that led to the theft of email correspondence with the company.
The attack, which came to light earlier this year, has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0299 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0299/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0299/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T12:28:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0298 : Vulnérabilité dans Spring Framework (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0298/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0298/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T12:21:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Framework. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python's PyPI Reveals Its Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/gitguardian-report-pypi-secrets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/gitguardian-report-pypi-secrets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitGuardian is famous for its annual State of Secrets Sprawl report. In their 2023 report, they found over 10 million exposed passwords, API keys, and other credentials exposed in public GitHub commits. The takeaways in their 2024 report did not just highlight 12.8 million new exposed secrets in GitHub, but a number in the popular Python package repository PyPI.
PyPI,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Python's PyPI Reveals Its Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/blog-post.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/blog-post.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitGuardian is famous for its annual State of Secrets Sprawl report. In their 2023 report, they found over 10 million exposed passwords, API keys, and other credentials exposed in public GitHub commits. The takeaways in their 2024 report did not just highlight 12.8 million new exposed secrets in GitHub, but a number in the popular Python package repository PyPI.
PyPI,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TA547 Phishing Attack Hits German Firms with Rhadamanthys Stealer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ta547-phishing-attack-hits-german-firms.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/ta547-phishing-attack-hits-german-firms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T11:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor tracked as TA547 has targeted dozens of German organizations with an information stealer called Rhadamanthys as part of an invoice-themed phishing campaign.
"This is the first time researchers observed TA547 use Rhadamanthys, an information stealer that is used by multiple cybercriminal threat actors," Proofpoint said. "Additionally, the actor appeared to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0297 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0297/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0297/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T09:17:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Juniper. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0296 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0296/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0296/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T07:39:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Expands Spyware Alert System to Warn Users of Mercenary Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/apple-expands-spyware-alert-system-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/apple-expands-spyware-alert-system-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple on Wednesday revised its documentation pertaining to its mercenary spyware threat notification system to mention that it alerts users when they may have been individually targeted by such attacks.
It also specifically called out companies like NSO Group for developing commercial surveillance tools such as Pegasus that are used by state actors to pull off "individually targeted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0295 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0295/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0295/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:34:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0294 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0294/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0294/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:26:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0293 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mitel MiCollab (11 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0293/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0293/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T06:16:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mitel MiCollab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet Rolls Out Critical Security Patches for FortiClientLinux Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/fortinet-has-released-patches-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/fortinet-has-released-patches-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-11T05:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has released patches to address a critical security flaw impacting FortiClientLinux that could be exploited to achieve arbitrary code execution.
Tracked as CVE-2023-45590, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.4 out of a maximum of 10.
"An Improper Control of Generation of Code ('Code Injection') vulnerability [CWE-94] in FortiClientLinux may allow an unauthenticated attacker to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['eXotic Visit' Spyware Campaign Targets Android Users in India and Pakistan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/exotic-visit-spyware-campaign-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/exotic-visit-spyware-campaign-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An active Android malware campaign dubbed eXotic Visit has been primarily targeting users in South Asia, particularly those in India and Pakistan, with malware distributed via dedicated websites and Google Play Store.
Slovak cybersecurity firm said the activity, ongoing since November 2021, is not linked to any known threat actor or group. It's tracking the group behind the operation under the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Robin Returns: New Malware Campaign Spreading Through WSF Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/raspberry-robin-returns-new-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/raspberry-robin-returns-new-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T13:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new Raspberry Robin campaign wave that propagates the malware through malicious Windows Script Files (WSFs) since March 2024.
"Historically, Raspberry Robin was known to spread through removable media like USB drives, but over time its distributors have experimented with other initial infection vectors," HP Wolf Security said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: GitHub's Fake Popularity Scam Tricking Developers into Downloading Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/beware-githubs-fake-popularity-scam.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/beware-githubs-fake-popularity-scam.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are now taking advantage of GitHub's search functionality to trick unsuspecting users looking for popular repositories into downloading spurious counterparts that serve malware.
The latest assault on the open-source software supply chain involves concealing malicious code within Microsoft Visual Code project files that's designed to download next-stage payloads from a remote URL,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on Review: Cynomi AI-powered vCISO Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hands-on-review-cynomi-ai-powered-vciso.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hands-on-review-cynomi-ai-powered-vciso.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The need for vCISO services is growing. SMBs and SMEs are dealing with more third-party risks, tightening regulatory demands and stringent cyber insurance requirements than ever before. However, they often lack the resources and expertise to hire an in-house security executive team. By outsourcing security and compliance leadership to a vCISO, these organizations can more easily obtain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover First Native Spectre v2 Exploit Against Linux Kernel]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-uncover-first-native.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-uncover-first-native.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed what they say is the "first native Spectre v2 exploit" against the Linux kernel on Intel systems that could be exploited to read sensitive data from the memory.
The exploit, called Native Branch History Injection (BHI), can be used to leak arbitrary kernel memory at 3.5 kB/sec by bypassing existing Spectre v2/BHI mitigations, researchers from Systems and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Learn How to Stop Hackers from Exploiting Hidden Identity Weaknesses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/webinar-learn-how-to-stop-hackers-from.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/webinar-learn-how-to-stop-hackers-from.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We all know passwords and firewalls are important, but what about the invisible threats lurking beneath the surface of your systems?
Identity Threat Exposures (ITEs) are like secret tunnels for hackers – they make your security way more vulnerable than you think.
Think of it like this: misconfigurations, forgotten accounts, and old settings are like cracks in your digital fortress walls. Hackers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0292 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0292/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0292/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:29:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une usurpation d'identité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0291 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0291/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0291/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:29:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0290 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft .Net (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0290/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0290/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:29:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft .Net. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0289 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0289/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0289/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0288 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0288/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0288/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:29:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0287 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0287/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0287/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T06:07:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0286 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Xen (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0286/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0286/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T05:52:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0285 : Vulnérabilité dans WordPress (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0285/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0285/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T05:48:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans WordPress. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0284 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (10 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0284/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0284/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T05:29:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Fixes 149 Flaws in Huge April Patch Release, Zero-Days Included]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/microsoft-fixes-149-flaws-in-huge-april.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/microsoft-fixes-149-flaws-in-huge-april.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T04:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates for the month of April 2024 to remediate a record 149 flaws, two of which have come under active exploitation in the wild.
Of the 149 flaws, three are rated Critical, 142 are rated Important, three are rated Moderate, and one is rated Low in severity. The update is aside from 21 vulnerabilities that the company addressed in its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical 'BatBadBut' Rust Vulnerability Exposes Windows Systems to Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-batbadbut-rust-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-batbadbut-rust-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-10T03:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw in the Rust standard library could be exploited to target Windows users and stage command injection attacks.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-24576, has a CVSS score of 10.0, indicating maximum severity. That said, it only impacts scenarios where batch files are invoked on Windows with untrusted arguments.
"The Rust standard library did not properly escape]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[10-Year-Old 'RUBYCARP' Romanian Hacker Group Surfaces with Botnet]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/10-year-old-rubycarp-romanian-hacker.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/10-year-old-rubycarp-romanian-hacker.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T14:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat group of suspected Romanian origin called RUBYCARP has been observed maintaining a long-running botnet for carrying out crypto mining, distributed denial-of-service (DDoS), and phishing attacks.
The group, believed to be active for at least 10 years, employs the botnet for financial gain, Sysdig said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
"Its primary method of operation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Targeting Human Rights Activists in Morocco and Western Sahara]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-targeting-human-rights.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/hackers-targeting-human-rights.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Human rights activists in Morocco and the Western Sahara region are the targets of a new threat actor that leverages phishing attacks to trick victims into installing bogus Android apps and serve credential harvesting pages for Windows users.
Cisco Talos is tracking the activity cluster under the name Starry Addax, describing it as primarily singling out activists associated with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Discover LG Smart TV Vulnerabilities Allowing Root Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-discover-lg-smart-tv.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/researchers-discover-lg-smart-tv.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in LG webOS running on its smart televisions that could be exploited to bypass authorization and gain root access on the devices.
The findings come from Romanian cybersecurity firm Bitdefender, which discovered and reported the flaws in November 2023. The issues were fixed by LG as part of updates released on March 22, 2024.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CL0P's Ransomware Rampage - Security Measures for 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/cl0ps-ransomware-rampage-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/cl0ps-ransomware-rampage-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T11:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 CL0P Growth 
Emerging in early 2019, CL0P was first introduced as a more advanced version of its predecessor the ‘CryptoMix’ ransomware, brought about by its owner CL0P ransomware, a cybercrime organisation. Over the years the group remained active with significant campaigns throughout 2020 to 2022. But in 2023 the CL0P ransomware gang took itself to new heights and became one of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0283 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (09 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0283/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0283/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T10:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0282 : [SCADA] Vulnérabilité dans les produits Schneider (09 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0282/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0282/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T09:57:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Schneider. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0281 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (09 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0281/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0281/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T09:57:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers Using Obfuscation Tools to Deliver Multi-Stage Malware via Invoice Phishing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/attackers-using-obfuscation-tools-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/attackers-using-obfuscation-tools-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an intricate multi-stage attack that leverages invoice-themed phishing decoys to deliver a wide range of malware such as Venom RAT, Remcos RAT, XWorm, NanoCore RAT, and a stealer that targets crypto wallets.
The email messages come with Scalable Vector Graphics (SVG) file attachments that, when clicked, activate the infection sequence, Fortinet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws Leave 92,000 D-Link NAS Devices Vulnerable to Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-flaws-leave-92000-d-link-nas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/04/critical-flaws-leave-92000-d-link-nas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T05:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively scanning and exploiting a pair of security flaws that are said to affect as many as 92,000 internet-exposed D-Link network-attached storage (NAS) devices.
Tracked as CVE-2024-3272 (CVSS score: 9.8) and CVE-2024-3273 (CVSS score: 7.3), the vulnerabilities impact legacy D-Link products that have reached end-of-life (EoL) status. D-Link, in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the Cloud: Revolutionizing Privileged Access Management with One Identity Cloud PAM Essentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/embracing-cloud-revolutionizing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/embracing-cloud-revolutionizing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cyber threats loom around every corner and privileged accounts become prime targets, the significance of implementing a robust Privileged Access Management (PAM) solution can't be overstated. With organizations increasingly migrating to cloud environments, the PAM Solution Market is experiencing a transformative shift toward cloud-based offerings. One Identity PAM Essentials stands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0280 : Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (09 avril 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0280/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0280/"/>
        <updated>2024-04-09T05:25:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>