<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-08-24T06:16:00.944Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PEAKLIGHT Dropper Deployed in Attacks Targeting Windows with Malicious Movie Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-peaklight-dropper-deployed-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-peaklight-dropper-deployed-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a never-before-seen dropper that serves as a conduit to launch next-stage malware with the ultimate goal of infecting Windows systems with information stealers and loaders.

"This memory-only dropper decrypts and executes a PowerShell-based downloader," Google-owned Mandiant said. "This PowerShell-based downloader is being tracked as PEAKLIGHT."

Some of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM QRadar SIEM (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0720/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0720/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans IBM QRadar SIEM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0719/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0719/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0718/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0718/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0717/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0717/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Experience the Power of a Must-Have All-in-One Cybersecurity Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-experience-power-of-must-have.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-experience-power-of-must-have.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's be honest. The world of cybersecurity feels like a constant war zone. You're bombarded by threats, scrambling to keep up with patches, and drowning in an endless flood of alerts. It's exhausting, isn’t it?
But what if there was a better way?
Imagine having every essential cybersecurity tool at your fingertips, all within a single, intuitive platform, backed by expert support 24/7. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0716/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0716/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Boot (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0715/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0715/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Boot. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus on What Matters Most: Exposure Management and Your Attack Surface]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/focus-on-what-matters-most-exposure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/focus-on-what-matters-most-exposure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the full article for key points from Intruder’s VP of Product, Andy Hornegold’s recent talk on exposure management. If you’d like to hear Andy’s insights first-hand, watch Intruder’s on-demand webinar. To learn more about reducing your attack surface, reach out to their team today. 
Attack surface management vs exposure management
Attack surface management (ASM) is the ongoing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Qilin Ransomware Attack Uses VPN Credentials, Steals Chrome Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qilin-ransomware-attack-uses-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qilin-ransomware-attack-uses-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind a recently observed Qilin ransomware attack have stolen credentials stored in Google Chrome browsers on a small set of compromised endpoints.
The use of credential harvesting in connection with a ransomware infection marks an unusual twist, and one that could have cascading consequences, cybersecurity firm Sophos said in a Thursday report.
The attack, detected in July]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0714/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0714/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T09:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0713/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0713/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T07:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Sonicwall (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0712/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0712/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T06:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Sonicwall. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0711/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0711/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T06:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New macOS Malware "Cthulhu Stealer" Targets Apple Users' Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-cthulhu-stealer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-cthulhu-stealer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new information stealer that's designed to target Apple macOS hosts and harvest a wide range of information, underscoring how threat actors are increasingly setting their sights on the operating system.
Dubbed Cthulhu Stealer, the malware has been available under a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) model for $500 a month from late 2023. It's capable of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latvian Hacker Extradited to U.S. for Role in Karakurt Cybercrime Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/latvian-hacker-extradited-to-us-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/latvian-hacker-extradited-to-us-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T04:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 33-year-old Latvian national living in Moscow, Russia, has been charged in the U.S. for allegedly stealing data, extorting victims, and laundering ransom payments since August 2021.
Deniss Zolotarjovs (aka Sforza_cesarini) has been charged with conspiring to commit money laundering, wire fraud and Hobbs Act extortion. He was arrested in Georgia in December 2023 and has since been extradited to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware Backdoor Discovered in RFID Cards Used in Hotels and Offices Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardware-backdoor-discovered-in-rfid.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardware-backdoor-discovered-in-rfid.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a hardware backdoor within a particular model of MIFARE Classic contactless cards that could allow authentication with an unknown key and open hotel rooms and office doors.
The attacks have been demonstrated against FM11RF08S, a new variant of MIFARE Classic that was released by Shanghai Fudan Microelectronics in 2020.
"The FM11RF08S backdoor enables any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardcoded Credential Vulnerability Found in SolarWinds Web Help Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardcoded-credential-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardcoded-credential-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has issued patches to address a new security flaw in its Web Help Desk (WHD) software that could allow remote unauthenticated users to gain unauthorized access to susceptible instances.
"The SolarWinds Web Help Desk (WHD) software is affected by a hardcoded credential vulnerability, allowing [a] remote unauthenticated user to access internal functionality and modify data," the company]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploit Zero-Day Cisco Switch Flaw to Gain System Control]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-hackers-exploit-zero-day-cisco.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-hackers-exploit-zero-day-cisco.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a China-nexus threat group's exploitation of a recently disclosed, now-patched security flaw in Cisco switches as a zero-day to seize control of the appliance and evade detection.
The activity, attributed to Velvet Ant, was observed early this year and involved the weaponization of CVE-2024-20399 (CVSS score: 6.0) to deliver bespoke malware and gain extensive control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'ALBeast' Vulnerability Exposes Weakness in AWS Application Load Balancer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-albeast-vulnerability-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-albeast-vulnerability-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 15,000 applications using Amazon Web Services' (AWS) Application Load Balancer (ALB) for authentication are potentially susceptible to a configuration-based issue that could expose them to sidestep access controls and compromise applications.
That's according to findings from Israeli cybersecurity company Miggo, which dubbed the problem ALBeast.
"This vulnerability allows attackers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Dovecot (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0710/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0710/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T12:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Dovecot. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Facts About Continuous Penetration Testing and Why It’s Important]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-facts-about-continuous-penetration.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-facts-about-continuous-penetration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Continuous Attack Surface Penetration Testing or CASPT?
Continuous Penetration Testing or Continuous Attack Surface Penetration Testing (CASPT) is an advanced security practice that involves the continuous, automated, and ongoing penetration testing services of an organization's digital assets to identify and mitigate security vulnerabilities. CASPT is designed for enterprises with an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0709/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0709/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0708/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0708/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mitel MiContact Center Business (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0707/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0707/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mitel MiContact Center Business. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0706/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0706/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T07:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-7971 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fixes High-Severity Chrome Flaw Actively Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T05:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has rolled out security fixes to address a high-severity security flaw in its Chrome browser that it said has come under active exploitation in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-7971, the vulnerability has been described as a type confusion bug in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine.
"Type confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.84 allowed a remote attacker to exploit heap]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in WordPress LiteSpeed Cache Plugin Allows Hackers Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-wordpress-litespeed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-wordpress-litespeed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T05:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a critical security flaw in the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress that could permit unauthenticated users to gain administrator privileges.
"The plugin suffers from an unauthenticated privilege escalation vulnerability which allows any unauthenticated visitor to gain Administrator level access after which malicious plugins could be uploaded and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Patches Critical Security Flaw in Enterprise Server Granting Admin Privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-patches-critical-security-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-patches-critical-security-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has released fixes to address a set of three security flaws impacting its Enterprise Server product, including one critical bug that could be abused to gain site administrator privileges.
The most severe of the shortcomings has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-6800, and carries a CVSS score of 9.5.
"On GitHub Enterprise Server instances that use SAML single sign-on (SSO)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware PG_MEM Targets PostgreSQL Databases for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-pgmem-targets-postgresql.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-pgmem-targets-postgresql.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unpacked a new malware strain dubbed PG_MEM that's designed to mine cryptocurrency after brute-forcing their way into PostgreSQL database instances.
"Brute-force attacks on Postgres involve repeatedly attempting to guess the database credentials until access is gained, exploiting weak passwords," Aqua security researcher Assaf Morag said in a technical report.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0705/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0705/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB Enterprise Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Patches Critical Copilot Studio Vulnerability Exposing Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-critical-copilot.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-critical-copilot.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a critical security flaw impacting Microsoft's Copilot Studio that could be exploited to access sensitive information.
Tracked as CVE-2024-38206 (CVSS score: 8.5), the vulnerability has been described as an information disclosure bug stemming from a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack.
"An authenticated attacker can bypass Server-Side Request]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Deploy New MoonPeak Trojan in Cyber Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new remote access trojan called MoonPeak has been discovered as being used by a state-sponsored North Korean threat activity cluster as part of a new campaign.
Cisco Talos attributed the malicious cyber campaign to a hacking group it tracks as UAT-5394, which it said exhibits some level of tactical overlaps with a known nation-state actor codenamed Kimsuky.
MoonPeak, under active development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0704/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0704/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time To Untangle the SaaS Ball of Yarn]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/its-time-to-untangle-saas-ball-of-yarn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/its-time-to-untangle-saas-ball-of-yarn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's no great revelation to say that SaaS applications have changed the way we operate, both in our personal and professional lives. We routinely rely on cloud-based and remote applications to conduct our basic functions, with the result that the only true perimeter of our networks has become the identities with which we log into these services.
Unfortunately – as is so often the case – our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styx Stealer Creator's OPSEC Fail Leaks Client List and Profit Details]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/styx-stealer-creators-opsec-fail-leaks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/styx-stealer-creators-opsec-fail-leaks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what's a case of an operational security (OPSEC) lapse, the operator behind a new information stealer called Styx Stealer leaked data from their own computer, including details related to the clients, profit information, nicknames, phone numbers, and email addresses.
Styx Stealer, a derivative of the Phemedrone Stealer, is capable of stealing browser data, instant messenger sessions from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New macOS Malware TodoSwift Linked to North Korean Hacking Groups]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-todoswift-linked-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-todoswift-linked-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new macOS malware strain dubbed TodoSwift that they say exhibits commonalities with known malicious software used by North Korean hacking groups.
"This application shares several behaviors with malware we've seen that originated in North Korea (DPRK) — specifically the threat actor known as BlueNoroff — such as KANDYKORN and RustBucket," Kandji security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0703/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0703/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0702/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0702/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Joomla! (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0701/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0701/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Joomla!. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERT-UA Warns of New Vermin-Linked Phishing Attacks with PoW Bait]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cert-ua-warns-of-new-vermin-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cert-ua-warns-of-new-vermin-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of new phishing attacks that aim to infect devices with malware.
The activity has been attributed to a threat cluster it tracks as UAC-0020, which is also known as Vermin. The exact scale and scope of the attacks are presently unknown.
The attack chains commence with phishing messages with photos of alleged prisoners of war (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GiveWP WordPress Plugin Vulnerability Puts 100,000+ Websites at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/givewp-wordpress-plugin-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/givewp-wordpress-plugin-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T04:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A maximum-severity security flaw has been disclosed in the WordPress GiveWP donation and fundraising plugin that exposes more than 100,000 websites to remote code execution attacks.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-5932 (CVSS score: 10.0), impacts all versions of the plugin prior to version 3.14.2, which was released on August 7, 2024. A security researcher, who goes by the online alias villu164,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting AWS Account Compromise: Key Indicators in CloudTrail Logs for Stolen API Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/detecting-aws-account-compromise-key.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/detecting-aws-account-compromise-key.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cloud infrastructure becomes the backbone of modern enterprises, ensuring the security of these environments is paramount. With AWS (Amazon Web Services) still being the dominant cloud it is important for any security professional to know where to look for signs of compromise. AWS CloudTrail stands out as an essential tool for tracking and logging API activity, providing a comprehensive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Czech Mobile Users Targeted in New Banking Credential Theft Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/czech-mobile-users-targeted-in-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/czech-mobile-users-targeted-in-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile users in the Czech Republic are the target of a novel phishing campaign that leverages a Progressive Web Application (PWA) in an attempt to steal their banking account credentials.
The attacks have targeted the Czech-based Československá obchodní banka (CSOB), as well as the Hungarian OTP Bank and the Georgian TBC Bank, according to Slovak cybersecurity company ESET.
"The phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit PHP Vulnerability to Deploy Stealthy Msupedge Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-php-vulnerability-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-php-vulnerability-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented backdoor named Msupedge has been put to use against a cyber attack targeting an unnamed university in Taiwan.
"The most notable feature of this backdoor is that it communicates with a command-and-control (C&C) server via DNS traffic," the Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
The origins of the backdoor are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of an Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/anatomy-of-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/anatomy-of-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly evolving cyber threat landscape, organizations face increasingly sophisticated attacks targeting their applications. Understanding these threats and the technologies designed to combat them is crucial. This article delves into the mechanics of a common application attack, using the infamous Log4Shell vulnerability as an example, and demonstrates how Application Detection and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover TLS Bootstrap Attack on Azure Kubernetes Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-tls-bootstrap.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-tls-bootstrap.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a security flaw impacting Microsoft Azure Kubernetes Services that, if successfully exploited, could allow an attacker to escalate their privileges and access credentials for services used by the cluster.
"An attacker with command execution in a Pod running within an affected Azure Kubernetes Services cluster could download the configuration used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Cyber Group TA453 Targets Jewish Leader with New AnvilEcho Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-cyber-group-ta453-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-cyber-group-ta453-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian state-sponsored threat actors have been observed orchestrating spear-phishing campaigns targeting a prominent Jewish figure starting in late July 2024 with the goal of delivering a new intelligence-gathering tool called AnvilEcho.
Enterprise security company Proofpoint is tracking the activity under the name TA453, which overlaps with activity tracked by the broader cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Security (20 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0700/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0700/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T06:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SpringSecurity. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blind Eagle Hackers Exploit Spear-Phishing to Deploy RATs in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blind-eagle-hackers-exploit-spear.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blind-eagle-hackers-exploit-spear.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T06:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a threat actor known as Blind Eagle that has persistently targeted entities and individuals in Colombia, Ecuador, Chile, Panama, and other Latin American nations.
Targets of these attacks span several sectors, including governmental institutions, financial companies, energy and oil and gas companies.
"Blind Eagle has demonstrated adaptability in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Oracle NetSuite Sites at Risk of Exposing Customer Information]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/thousands-of-oracle-netsuite-sites-at.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/thousands-of-oracle-netsuite-sites-at.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about the discovery of thousands of externally-facing Oracle NetSuite e-commerce sites that have been found susceptible to leaking sensitive customer information.
"A potential issue in NetSuite's SuiteCommerce platform could allow attackers to access sensitive data due to misconfigured access controls on custom record types (CRTs)," AppOmni's Aaron Costello]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Critical Jenkins Vulnerability Exploited in Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-critical-jenkins.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-critical-jenkins.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T04:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical security flaw impacting Jenkins to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, following its exploitation in ransomware attacks.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23897 (CVSS score: 9.8), is a path traversal flaw that could lead to code execution.
"Jenkins Command Line Interface (CLI) contains a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits F5 et Nginx (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0699/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0699/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T14:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits F5. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UULoader Malware Distributes Gh0st RAT and Mimikatz in East Asia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-uuloader-malware-distributes-gh0st.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-uuloader-malware-distributes-gh0st.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of malware called UULoader is being used by threat actors to deliver next-stage payloads like Gh0st RAT and Mimikatz.
The Cyberint Research Team, which discovered the malware, said it's distributed in the form of malicious installers for legitimate applications targeting Korean and Chinese speakers.
There is evidence pointing to UULoader being the work of a Chinese speaker due to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0698/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0698/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0697/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0697/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploit Popular Software Searches to Spread FakeBat Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-exploit-popular-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-exploit-popular-software.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a surge in malware infections stemming from malvertising campaigns distributing a loader called FakeBat.
"These attacks are opportunistic in nature, targeting users seeking popular business software," the Mandiant Managed Defense team said in a technical report. "The infection utilizes a trojanized MSIX installer, which executes a PowerShell script to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0696/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0696/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate the Hardest Parts of Employee Offboarding]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/11/how-to-automate-hardest-parts-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/11/how-to-automate-hardest-parts-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to recent research on employee offboarding, 70% of IT professionals say they’ve experienced the negative effects of incomplete IT offboarding, whether in the form of a security incident tied to an account that wasn't deprovisioned, a surprise bill for resources that aren’t in use anymore, or a missed handoff of a critical resource or account. This is despite an average of five]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xeon Sender Tool Exploits Cloud APIs for Large-Scale SMS Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/xeon-sender-tool-exploits-cloud-apis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/xeon-sender-tool-exploits-cloud-apis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors are using a cloud attack tool named Xeon Sender to conduct SMS phishing and spam campaigns on a large scale by abusing legitimate services.
"Attackers can use Xeon to send messages through multiple software-as-a-service (SaaS) providers using valid credentials for the service providers," SentinelOne security researcher Alex Delamotte said in a report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-037 (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-037/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-037/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Patches Zero-Day Flaw Exploited by North Korea’s Lazarus Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-zero-day-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-zero-day-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly patched security flaw in Microsoft Windows was exploited as a zero-day by Lazarus Group, a prolific state-sponsored actor affiliated with North Korea.
The security vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38193 (CVSS score: 7.8), has been described as a privilege escalation bug in the Windows Ancillary Function Driver (AFD.sys) for WinSock.
"An attacker who successfully exploited this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover New Infrastructure Tied to FIN7 Cybercrime Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-new-infrastructure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-new-infrastructure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered new infrastructure linked to a financially motivated threat actor known as FIN7.
The two clusters of potential FIN7 activity "indicate communications inbound to FIN7 infrastructure from IP addresses assigned to Post Ltd (Russia) and SmartApe (Estonia), respectively," Team Cymru said in a report published this week as part of a joint investigation with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Blocks Iranian Influence Operation Using ChatGPT for U.S. Election Propaganda]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/openai-blocks-iranian-influence.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/openai-blocks-iranian-influence.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T06:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI on Friday said it banned a set of accounts linked to what it said was an Iranian covert influence operation that leveraged ChatGPT to generate content that, among other things, focused on the upcoming U.S. presidential election.
"This week we identified and took down a cluster of ChatGPT accounts that were generating content for a covert Iranian influence operation identified as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers Exploit Public .env Files to Breach Cloud and Social Media Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/attackers-exploit-public-env-files-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/attackers-exploit-public-env-files-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large-scale extortion campaign has compromised various organizations by taking advantage of publicly accessible environment variable files (.env) that contain credentials associated with cloud and social media applications.
"Multiple security missteps were present in the course of this campaign, including the following: Exposing environment variables, using long-lived credentials, and absence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacker Jailed 3+ Years for Selling Stolen Credentials on Dark Web]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hacker-jailed-3-years-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hacker-jailed-3-years-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 27-year-old Russian national has been sentenced to over three years in prison for peddling financial information, login credentials, and other personally identifying information (PII) on a now-defunct dark web marketplace called Slilpp.
Georgy Kavzharadze, 27, of Moscow, Russia, pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit bank fraud and wire fraud earlier this February. In addition to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Using Fake Brand Sites to Spread DanaBot and StealC Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-using-fake-brand-sites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-using-fake-brand-sites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a sophisticated information stealer campaign that impersonates legitimate brands to distribute malware like DanaBot and StealC.
The activity cluster, orchestrated by Russian-speaking cybercriminals and collectively codenamed Tusk, is said to encompass several sub-campaigns, leveraging the reputation of the platforms to trick users into downloading the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0695/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0695/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0694/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0694/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0693/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0693/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Stage ValleyRAT Targets Chinese Users with Advanced Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/multi-stage-valleyrat-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/multi-stage-valleyrat-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking users are the target of an ongoing campaign that distributes malware known as ValleyRAT.
"ValleyRAT is a multi-stage malware that utilizes diverse techniques to monitor and control its victims and deploy arbitrary plugins to cause further damage," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researchers Eduardo Altares and Joie Salvio said.
"Another noteworthy characteristic of this malware is its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hidden Security Gaps in Your SaaS Apps: Are You Doing Due Diligence?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-hidden-security-gaps-in-your-saas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-hidden-security-gaps-in-your-saas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications have become indispensable for organizations aiming to enhance productivity and streamline operations. However, the convenience and efficiency these applications offer come with inherent security risks, often leaving hidden gaps that can be exploited. Conducting thorough due diligence on SaaS apps is essential to identify and mitigate these risks, ensuring the protection of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0692/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0692/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0691/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0691/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic APM Server (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0690/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0690/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic APM Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Spring Framework (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0689/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0689/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Spring Framework. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0688/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0688/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mitel Unify OpenScape Business Application (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0687/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0687/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mitel Unify OpenScape Business Application. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Xen (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0686/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0686/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0685/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0685/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Banshee Stealer Targets 100+ Browser Extensions on Apple macOS Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-banshee-stealer-targets-100-browser.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-banshee-stealer-targets-100-browser.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered new stealer malware that's designed to specifically target Apple macOS systems.
Dubbed Banshee Stealer, it's offered for sale in the cybercrime underground for a steep price of $3,000 a month and works across both x86_64 and ARM64 architectures. 
"Banshee Stealer targets a wide range of browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, and around 100 browser]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel Devices Shipped with Vulnerable App, Leaving Millions at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-pixel-devices-shipped-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-pixel-devices-shipped-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large percentage of Google's own Pixel devices shipped globally since September 2017 included dormant software that could be used to stage nefarious attacks and deliver various kinds of malware.
The issue manifests in the form of a pre-installed Android app called "Showcase.apk" that comes with excessive system privileges, including the ability to remotely execute code and install arbitrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Releases Patch for Critical Flaw in Web Help Desk Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/solarwinds-releases-patch-for-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/solarwinds-releases-patch-for-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has released patches to address a critical security vulnerability in its Web Help Desk software that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code on susceptible instances.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-28986 (CVSS score: 9.8), has been described as a deserialization bug.
"SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a Java deserialization remote code execution vulnerability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-Linked Hackers Target Eastern European NGOs and Media]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-linked-hackers-target-eastern.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-linked-hackers-target-eastern.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian and Belarusian non-profit organizations, Russian independent media, and international non-governmental organizations active in Eastern Europe have become the target of two separate spear-phishing campaigns orchestrated by threat actors whose interests align with that of the Russian government.
While one of the campaigns – dubbed River of Phish – has been attributed to COLDRIVER, an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identity Threat Detection and Response Solution Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/identity-threat-detection-and-response.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/identity-threat-detection-and-response.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emergence of Identity Threat Detection and Response
Identity Threat Detection and Response (ITDR) has emerged as a critical component to effectively detect and respond to identity-based attacks. Threat actors have shown their ability to compromise the identity infrastructure and move laterally into IaaS, Saas, PaaS and CI/CD environments. Identity Threat Detection and Response solutions help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RansomHub Group Deploys New EDR-Killing Tool in Latest Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ransomhub-group-deploys-new-edr-killing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ransomhub-group-deploys-new-edr-killing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cybercrime group with links to the RansomHub ransomware has been observed using a new tool designed to terminate endpoint detection and response (EDR) software on compromised hosts, joining the likes of other similar programs like AuKill (aka AvNeutralizer) and Terminator.
The EDR-killing utility has been dubbed EDRKillShifter by cybersecurity company Sophos, which discovered the tool in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Vulnerability 'ArtiPACKED' Exposes Repositories to Potential Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-vulnerability-artipacked-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-vulnerability-artipacked-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered attack vector in GitHub Actions artifacts dubbed ArtiPACKED could be exploited to take over repositories and gain access to organizations' cloud environments.
"A combination of misconfigurations and security flaws can make artifacts leak tokens, both of third party cloud services and GitHub tokens, making them available for anyone with read access to the repository to consume,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cyber Threat Targets Azerbaijan and Israel Diplomats, Stealing Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyber-threat-targets-azerbaijan-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyber-threat-targets-azerbaijan-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown threat actor has been attributed to a spate of attacks targeting Azerbaijan and Israel with an aim to steal sensitive data.
The attack campaign, detected by NSFOCUS on July 1, 2024, leveraged spear-phishing emails to single out Azerbaijani and Israeli diplomats. The activity is being tracked under the moniker Actor240524.
"Actor240524 possesses the ability to steal secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Gafgyt Botnet Variant Targets Weak SSH Passwords for GPU Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-gafgyt-botnet-variant-targets-weak.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-gafgyt-botnet-variant-targets-weak.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new variant of the Gafgyt botnet that's targeting machines with weak SSH passwords to ultimately mine cryptocurrency on compromised instances using their GPU computational power.
This indicates that the "IoT botnet is targeting more robust servers running on cloud native environments," Aqua Security researcher Assaf Morag said in a Wednesday analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta-Linked Attackers Target Users with SystemBC Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/black-basta-linked-attackers-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/black-basta-linked-attackers-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing social engineering campaign with alleged links to the Black Basta ransomware group has been linked to "multiple intrusion attempts" with the goal of conducting credential theft and deploying a malware dropper called SystemBC.
"The initial lure being utilized by the threat actors remains the same: an email bomb followed by an attempt to call impacted users and offer a fake solution,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0684/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0684/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0683/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0683/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0681/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0681/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que les...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0682/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0682/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0680/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0680/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-38189 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0679/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0679/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0678/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0678/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T12:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belarusian-Ukrainian Hacker Extradited to U.S. for Ransomware and Cybercrime Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/belarusian-ukrainian-hacker-extradited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/belarusian-ukrainian-hacker-extradited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of law enforcement agencies coordinated by the U.K. National Crime Agency (NCA) has led to the arrest and extradition of a Belarussian and Ukrainian dual-national believed to be associated with Russian-speaking cybercrime groups.
Maksim Silnikau (aka Maksym Silnikov), 38, went by the online monikers J.P. Morgan, xxx, and lansky. He was extradited to the U.S. from Poland on August 9,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0677/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0677/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Augment Your Password Security with EASM]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-augment-your-password-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-augment-your-password-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simply relying on traditional password security measures is no longer sufficient. When it comes to protecting your organization from credential-based attacks, it is essential to lock down the basics first. Securing your Active Directory should be a priority – it is like making sure a house has a locked front door before investing in a high-end alarm system. Once the fundamentals are covered,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Security Center (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0676/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0676/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T09:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Security Center. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nagios XI (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0675/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0675/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T09:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nagios XI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoS Attacks Surge 46% in First Half of 2024, Gcore Report Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ddos-attacks-surge-46-in-first-half-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ddos-attacks-surge-46-in-first-half-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring evolving DDoS trends is essential for anticipating threats and adapting defensive strategies. The comprehensive Gcore Radar Report for the first half of 2024 provides detailed insights into DDoS attack data, showcasing changes in attack patterns and the broader landscape of cyber threats. Here, we share a selection of findings from the full report.
Key Takeaways
The number of DDoS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues Patches for 90 Flaws, Including 10 Critical Zero-Day Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-issues-patches-for-90-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-issues-patches-for-90-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Tuesday shipped fixes to address a total of 90 security flaws, including 10 zero-days, of which six have come under active exploitation in the wild.
Of the 90 bugs, seven are rated Critical, 79 are rated Important, and one is rated Moderate in severity. This is also in addition to 36 vulnerabilities that the tech giant resolved in its Edge browser since last month.
The Patch Tuesday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Ivanti Virtual Traffic Manager Could Allow Rogue Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-ivanti-virtual-traffic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-ivanti-virtual-traffic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has rolled out security updates for a critical flaw in Virtual Traffic Manager (vTM) that could be exploited to achieve an authentication bypass and create rogue administrative users.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7593, has a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Backed Earth Baku Expands Cyber Attacks to Europe, Middle East, and Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-backed-earth-baku-expands-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-backed-earth-baku-expands-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-backed threat actor known as Earth Baku has diversified its targeting footprint beyond the Indo-Pacific region to include Europe, the Middle East, and Africa starting in late 2022.
Newly targeted countries as part of the activity include Italy, Germany, the U.A.E., and Qatar, with suspected attacks also detected in Georgia and Romania. Governments, media and communications, telecoms,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Zabbix (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0674/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0674/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Zabbix. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhostWrite: New T-Head CPU Bugs Expose Devices to Unrestricted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ghostwrite-new-t-head-cpu-bugs-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ghostwrite-new-t-head-cpu-bugs-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of researchers from the CISPA Helmholtz Center for Information Security in Germany has disclosed an architectural bug impacting Chinese chip company T-Head's XuanTie C910 and C920 RISC-V CPUs that could allow attackers to gain unrestricted access to susceptible devices.
The vulnerability has been codenamed GhostWrite. It has been described as a direct CPU bug embedded in the hardware, as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider Electric (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0673/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0673/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider Electric. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0672/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0672/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Vulnerabilities in AI-Powered Azure Health Bot Service]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in_0471960302.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in_0471960302.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered two security flaws in Microsoft's Azure Health Bot Service that, if exploited, could permit a malicious actor to achieve lateral movement within customer environments and access sensitive patient data.
The critical issues, now patched by Microsoft, could have allowed access to cross-tenant resources within the service, Tenable said in a new report shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0671/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0671/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T12:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Hardsec Matters: From Protecting Critical Services to Enhancing Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/why-hardsec-matters-from-protecting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/why-hardsec-matters-from-protecting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditionally, the focus has been on defending against digital threats such as malware, ransomware, and phishing attacks by detecting them and responding. However, as cyber threats become more sophisticated. There is a growing recognition of the importance of measures that stop new attacks before they are recognized. With high-value assets, it’s not good enough to have the protection, it’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Shuts Down Dispossessor Ransomware Group's Servers Across U.S., U.K., and Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-shuts-down-dispossessor-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-shuts-down-dispossessor-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) on Monday announced the disruption of online infrastructure associated with a nascent ransomware group called Dispossessor (aka Radar).
The effort saw the dismantling of three U.S. servers, three United Kingdom servers, 18 German servers, eight U.S.-based criminal domains, and one German-based criminal domain. Dispossessor is said to be led by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0670/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0670/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T08:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Warns of New Phishing Campaign Targeting Government Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ukraine-warns-of-new-phishing-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ukraine-warns-of-new-phishing-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of a new phishing campaign that masquerades as the Security Service of Ukraine to distribute malware capable of remote desktop access.
The agency is tracking the activity under the name UAC-0198. More than 100 computers are estimated to have been infected since July 2024, including those related to government bodies in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Phishing Attacks Adapt Quickly to Capitalize on Current Events]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-phishing-attacks-adapt-quickly-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-phishing-attacks-adapt-quickly-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, no fewer than 94 percent of businesses were impacted by phishing attacks, a 40 percent increase compared to the previous year, according to research from Egress.
What's behind the surge in phishing? One popular answer is AI – particularly generative AI, which has made it trivially easier for threat actors to craft content that they can use in phishing campaigns, like malicious emails]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Vulnerabilities in Solarman and Deye Solar Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified a number of security shortcomings in photovoltaic system management platforms operated by Chinese companies Solarman and Deye that could enable malicious actors to cause disruption and power blackouts.
"If exploited, these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to control inverter settings that could take parts of the grid down, potentially causing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hangover is Here – The End of the Beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-ai-hangover-is-here-end-of-beginning.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-ai-hangover-is-here-end-of-beginning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a good year of sustained exuberance, the hangover is finally here. It’s a gentle one (for now), as the market corrects the share price of the major players (like Nvidia, Microsoft, and Google), while other players reassess the market and adjust priorities. Gartner calls it the trough of disillusionment, when interest wanes and implementations fail to deliver the promised breakthroughs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD Releases Urgent Patch for High-Severity OpenSSH Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/freebsd-releases-urgent-patch-for-high.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/freebsd-releases-urgent-patch-for-high.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of the FreeBSD Project have released security updates to address a high-severity flaw in OpenSSH that attackers could potentially exploit to execute arbitrary code remotely with elevated privileges.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7589, carries a CVSS score of 7.4 out of a maximum of 10.0, indicating high severity.
"A signal handler in sshd(8) may call a logging function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-036 (12 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-036/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-036/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T06:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial Remote Access Tool Ewon Cosy+ Vulnerable to Root Access Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/industrial-remote-access-tool-ewon-cosy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/industrial-remote-access-tool-ewon-cosy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T06:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in the industrial remote access solution Ewon Cosy+ that could be abused to gain root privileges to the devices and stage follow-on attacks.
The elevated access could then be weaponized to decrypt encrypted firmware files and encrypted data such as passwords in configuration files, and even get correctly signed X.509 VPN certificates for foreign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EastWind Attack Deploys PlugY and GrewApacha Backdoors Using Booby-Trapped LNK Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-government-hit-by-eastwind.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-government-hit-by-eastwind.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T03:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian government and IT organizations are the target of a new campaign that delivers a number of backdoors and trojans as part of a spear-phishing campaign codenamed EastWind.
The attack chains are characterized by the use of RAR archive attachments containing a Windows shortcut (LNK) file that, upon opening, activates the infection sequence, culminating in the deployment of malware such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogue PyPI Library Solana Users, Steals Blockchain Wallet Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/rogue-pypi-library-solana-users-steals.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/rogue-pypi-library-solana-users-steals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new malicious package on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that masquerades as a library from the Solana blockchain platform but is actually designed to steal victims' secrets.
"The legitimate Solana Python API project is known as 'solana-py' on GitHub, but simply 'solana' on the Python software registry, PyPI," Sonatype researcher Ax Sharma]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover 10 Flaws in Google's File Transfer Tool Quick Share]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-10-flaws-in-googles.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-10-flaws-in-googles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 10 security flaws have been uncovered in Google's Quick Share data transfer utility for Android and Windows that could be assembled to trigger remote code execution (RCE) chain on systems that have the software installed.
"The Quick Share application implements its own specific application-layer communication protocol to support file transfers between nearby, compatible devices,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Hits 300,000 Users with Rogue Chrome and Edge Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-hits-300000-users-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-hits-300000-users-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing, widespread malware campaign has been observed installing rogue Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge extensions via a trojan distributed via fake websites masquerading as popular software.
"The trojan malware contains different deliverables ranging from simple adware extensions that hijack searches to more sophisticated malicious scripts that deliver local extensions to steal private data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Unpatched Office Vulnerability Leading to Data Breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-warns-of-unpatched-office.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-warns-of-unpatched-office.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T05:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has disclosed an unpatched zero-day in Office that, if successfully exploited, could result in unauthorized disclosure of sensitive information to malicious actors.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38200 (CVSS score: 7.5), has been described as a spoofing flaw that affects the following versions of Office -

Microsoft Office 2016 for 32-bit edition and 64-bit editions
Microsoft]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover Severe AWS Flaws Leading to RCE, Data Theft, and Full-Service Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/experts-uncover-severe-aws-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/experts-uncover-severe-aws-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered multiple critical flaws in Amazon Web Services (AWS) offerings that, if successfully exploited, could result in serious consequences.
"The impact of these vulnerabilities range between remote code execution (RCE), full-service user takeover (which might provide powerful administrative access), manipulation of AI modules, exposing sensitive data, data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Reveals Four OpenVPN Flaws Leading to Potential RCE and LPE]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-reveals-four-openvpn-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-reveals-four-openvpn-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Thursday disclosed four medium-severity security flaws in the open-source OpenVPN software that could be chained to achieve remote code execution (RCE) and local privilege escalation (LPE).
"This attack chain could enable attackers to gain full control over targeted endpoints, potentially resulting in data breaches, system compromise, and unauthorized access to sensitive information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Roundcube (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-010/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-010/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T14:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 4 août 2024, Roundcube a publié des correctifs concernant les vulnérabilités critiques CVE-2024-42008 et CVE-2024-42009 affectant son serveur de courriel. Ces vulnérabilités permettent des injections de code indirectes à distance (XSS) qui peuvent, par exemple, conduire à la récupération du...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Flaws in Sonos Smart Speakers Allow Hackers to Eavesdrop on Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-flaws-in-sonos-smart-speakers-allow.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-flaws-in-sonos-smart-speakers-allow.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered weaknesses in Sonos smart speakers that could be exploited by malicious actors to clandestinely eavesdrop on users.
The vulnerabilities "led to an entire break in the security of Sonos's secure boot process across a wide range of devices and remotely being able to compromise several devices over the air," NCC Group security researchers Alex Plaskett and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0669/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0669/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T11:46:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0668/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0668/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T11:36:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0667/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0667/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T11:31:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0666/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0666/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T11:24:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0665/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0665/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:19:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans PostgreSQL (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0664/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0664/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:13:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans PostgreSQL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ Charges Nashville Man for Helping North Koreans Get U.S. Tech Jobs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/doj-charges-nashville-man-for-helping.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/doj-charges-nashville-man-for-helping.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Thursday charged a 38-year-old individual from Nashville, Tennessee, for allegedly running a "laptop farm" to help get North Koreans remote jobs with American and British companies.
Matthew Isaac Knoot is charged with conspiracy to cause damage to protected computers, conspiracy to launder monetary instruments, conspiracy to commit wire fraud, intentional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Asterisk (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0663/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0663/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:06:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Asterisk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB (09 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0662/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0662/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T07:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Hackers Exploiting Legacy Cisco Smart Install Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-legacy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-hackers-exploiting-legacy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T05:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has disclosed that threat actors are abusing the legacy Cisco Smart Install (SMI) feature with the aim of accessing sensitive data.
The agency said it has seen adversaries "acquire system configuration files by leveraging available protocols or software on devices, such as abusing the legacy Cisco Smart Install feature."
It also]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[University Professors Targeted by North Korean Cyber Espionage Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/university-professors-targeted-by-north.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/university-professors-targeted-by-north.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T15:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Kimsuky has been linked to a new set of attacks targeting university staff, researchers, and professors for intelligence gathering purposes.
Cybersecurity firm Resilience said it identified the activity in late July 2024 after it observed an operation security (OPSEC) error made by the hackers.
Kimsuky, also known by the names APT43, ARCHIPELAGO,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[0.0.0.0 Day: 18-Year-Old Browser Vulnerability Impacts MacOS and Linux Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/0000-day-18-year-old-browser.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/0000-day-18-year-old-browser.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T13:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new "0.0.0.0 Day" impacting all major web browsers that malicious websites could take advantage of to breach local networks.
The critical vulnerability "exposes a fundamental flaw in how browsers handle network requests, potentially granting malicious actors access to sensitive services running on local devices," Oligo Security researcher Avi Lumelsky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Automated Security Validation: One (Very Important) Part of a Complete CTEM Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/automated-security-validation-one-very.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/automated-security-validation-one-very.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The last few years have seen more than a few new categories of security solutions arise in hopes of stemming a never-ending tidal wave of risks. One of these categories is Automated Security Validation (ASV), which provides the attacker’s perspective of exposures and equips security teams to continuously validate exposures, security measures, and remediation at scale. ASV is an important element]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows Downgrade Attack Risks Exposing Patched Systems to Old Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/windows-downgrade-attack-risks-exposing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/windows-downgrade-attack-risks-exposing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T10:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft said it is developing security updates to address two loopholes that it said could be abused to stage downgrade attacks against the Windows update architecture and replace current versions of the Windows files with older versions.
The vulnerabilities are listed below -

CVE-2024-38202 (CVSS score: 7.3) - Windows Update Stack Elevation of Privilege Vulnerability
CVE-2024-21302 (CVSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Scam Uses Google Drawings and WhatsApp Shortened Links]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-phishing-scam-uses-google-drawings.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-phishing-scam-uses-google-drawings.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T09:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a novel phishing campaign that leverages Google Drawings and shortened links generated via WhatsApp to evade detection and trick users into clicking on bogus links designed to steal sensitive information.
"The attackers chose a group of the best-known websites in computing to craft the threat, including Google and WhatsApp to host the attack elements,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (08 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0661/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0661/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T08:04:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (08 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0660/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0660/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unlock the Future of Cybersecurity: Exclusive, Next Era AI Insights and Cutting-Edge Training at SANS Network Security 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unlock-future-of-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unlock-future-of-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Immersive Experience Happening This September in Las Vegas!In an era of relentless cybersecurity threats and rapid technological advancement, staying ahead of the curve is not just a necessity, but critical. SANS Institute, the premier global authority in cybersecurity training, is thrilled to announce Network Security 2024, a landmark event designed to empower cybersecurity professionals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (08 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0659/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0659/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T07:07:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI and CISA Warn of BlackSuit Ransomware That Demands Up to $500 Million]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-and-cisa-warn-of-blacksuit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-and-cisa-warn-of-blacksuit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T06:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ransomware strain known as BlackSuit has demanded as much as $500 million in ransoms to date, with one individual ransom demand hitting $60 million.
That's according to an updated advisory from the U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) and the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI).
"BlackSuit actors have exhibited a willingness to negotiate payment amounts," the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Flaw in WhatsUp Gold Under Active Attack - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-security-flaw-in-whatsup-gold.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-security-flaw-in-whatsup-gold.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-08T05:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw impacting Progress Software WhatsUp Gold is seeing active exploitation attempts, making it essential that users move quickly to apply the latest.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-4885 (CVSS score: 9.8), an unauthenticated remote code execution bug impacting versions of the network monitoring application released before 2023.1.3.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Kernel Exploit Technique 'SLUBStick' Discovered by Researchers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-linux-kernel-exploit-technique.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-linux-kernel-exploit-technique.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a novel Linux kernel exploitation technique dubbed SLUBStick that could be exploited to elevate a limited heap vulnerability to an arbitrary memory read-and-write primitive.
"Initially, it exploits a timing side-channel of the allocator to perform a cross-cache attack reliably," a group of academics from the Graz University of Technology said [PDF]. "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Roundcube Webmail Flaws Allow Hackers to Steal Emails and Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/roundcube-webmail-flaws-allow-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/roundcube-webmail-flaws-allow-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of security flaws in the Roundcube webmail software that could be exploited to execute malicious JavaScript in a victim's web browser and steal sensitive information from their account under specific circumstances.
"When a victim views a malicious email in Roundcube sent by an attacker, the attacker can execute arbitrary JavaScript in the victim's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Go-based Backdoor GoGra Targets South Asian Media Organization]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-go-based-backdoor-gogra-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-go-based-backdoor-gogra-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unnamed media organization in South Asia was targeted in November 20233 using a previously undocumented Go-based backdoor called GoGra.
"GoGra is written in Go and uses the Microsoft Graph API to interact with a command-and-control (C&C) server hosted on Microsoft mail services," Symantec, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
It's currently not clear how it's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike Reveals Root Cause of Global System Outages]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/crowdstrike-reveals-root-cause-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/crowdstrike-reveals-root-cause-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity company CrowdStrike has published its root cause analysis detailing the Falcon Sensor software update crash that crippled millions of Windows devices globally.
The "Channel File 291" incident, as originally highlighted in its Preliminary Post Incident Review (PIR), has been traced back to a content validation issue that arose after it introduced a new Template Type to enable]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (07 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0658/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0658/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T09:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (07 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0657/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0657/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T08:50:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (07 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0656/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0656/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T08:37:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android (07 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0655/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0655/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T08:14:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. L'éditeur indique que la vulnérabilité...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chameleon Android Banking Trojan Targets Users Through Fake CRM App]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chameleon-android-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chameleon-android-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have lifted the lid on a new technique adopted by threat actors behind the Chameleon Android banking trojan targeting users in Canada by masquerading as a Customer Relationship Management (CRM) app.
"Chameleon was seen masquerading as a CRM app, targeting a Canadian restaurant chain operating internationally," Dutch security outfit ThreatFabric said in a technical]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple’s New macOS Sequoia Tightens Gatekeeper Controls to Block Unauthorized Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apples-new-macos-sequoia-tightens.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apples-new-macos-sequoia-tightens.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-07T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple on Tuesday announced an update to its next-generation macOS version that makes it a little more difficult for users to override Gatekeeper protections.
Gatekeeper is a crucial line of defense built into macOS designed to ensure that only trusted apps run on the operating system. When an app is downloaded from outside of the App Store and opened for the first time, it verifies that the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL Recovers $41 Million in Largest Ever BEC Scam in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/interpol-recovers-41-million-in-largest.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/interpol-recovers-41-million-in-largest.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL said it devised a "global stop-payment mechanism" that helped facilitate the largest-ever recovery of funds defrauded in a business email compromise (BEC) scam. 
The development comes after an unnamed commodity firm based in Singapore fell victim to a BEC scam in mid-July 2024. It refers to a type of cybercrime where a malicious actor poses as a trusted figure and uses email to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspicious Minds: Insider Threats in The SaaS World]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/suspicious-minds-insider-threats-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/suspicious-minds-insider-threats-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Everyone loves the double-agent plot twist in a spy movie, but it’s a different story when it comes to securing company data. Whether intentional or unintentional, insider threats are a legitimate concern. According to CSA research, 26% of companies who reported a SaaS security incident were struck by an insider. 
The challenge for many is detecting those threats before they lead to full]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Moonstone Sleet Push Malicious JS Packages to npm Registry]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-moonstone-sleet.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-moonstone-sleet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Moonstone Sleet has continued to push malicious npm packages to the JavaScript package registry with the aim of infecting Windows systems, underscoring the persistent nature of their campaigns.
The packages in question, harthat-api and harthat-hash, were published on July 7, 2024, according to Datadog Security Labs. Both the libraries did not attract]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Spyware LianSpy Evades Detection Using Yandex Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-spyware-lianspy-evades.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-spyware-lianspy-evades.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users in Russia have been the target of a previously undocumented Android post-compromise spyware called LianSpy since at least 2021.
Cybersecurity vendor Kaspersky, which discovered the malware in March 2024, noted its use of Yandex Cloud, a Russian cloud service, for command-and-control (C2) communications as a way to avoid having a dedicated infrastructure and evade detection.
"This threat is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Kibana (06 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0654/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0654/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T07:02:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Kibana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans LibreOffice (06 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0653/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0653/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T07:01:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans LibreOffice. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Patches New Android Kernel Vulnerability Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-patches-new-android-kernel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-patches-new-android-kernel.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has addressed a high-severity security flaw impacting the Android kernel that it has been actively exploited in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-36971, has been described as a case of remote code execution impacting the kernel.
"There are indications that CVE-2024-36971 may be under limited, targeted exploitation," the tech giant noted in its monthly Android security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Zero-Day Flaw in Apache OFBiz ERP Allows Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-zero-day-flaw-in-apache-ofbiz-erp.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-zero-day-flaw-in-apache-ofbiz-erp.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-06T04:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new zero-day pre-authentication remote code execution vulnerability has been disclosed in the Apache OFBiz open-source enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that could allow threat actors to achieve remote code execution on affected instances.
Tracked as CVE-2024-38856, the flaw has a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0. It affects Apache OFBiz versions prior to 18.12.15.
"The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Flaws in Windows Smart App Control and SmartScreen]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-flaws-in-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-flaws-in-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T13:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered design weaknesses in Microsoft's Windows Smart App Control and SmartScreen that could enable threat actors to gain initial access to target environments without raising any warnings.
Smart App Control (SAC) is a cloud-powered security feature introduced by Microsoft in Windows 11 to block malicious, untrusted, and potentially unwanted apps from being run]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kazakh Organizations Targeted by 'Bloody Wolf' Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/kazakh-organizations-targeted-by-bloody.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/kazakh-organizations-targeted-by-bloody.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T12:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Organizations in Kazakhstan are the target of a threat activity cluster dubbed Bloody Wolf that delivers a commodity malware called STRRAT (aka Strigoi Master).
"The program selling for as little as $80 on underground resources allows the adversaries to take control of corporate computers and hijack restricted data," cybersecurity vendor BI.ZONE said in a new analysis.
The cyber attacks employ]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-035 (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-035/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-035/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T12:32:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0652/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0652/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T12:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Trend Micro (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0651/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0651/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:59:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Trend Micro. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Stormshield Management Center  (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0650/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0650/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:55:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Stormshield Management Center. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Citrix (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0649/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0649/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:50:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Citrix. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SonicWall (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0648/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0648/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:43:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SonicWall. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Loper Bright Decision: How it Impacts Cybersecurity Law]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-loper-bright-decision-how-it.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-loper-bright-decision-how-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Loper Bright decision has yielded impactful results: the Supreme Court has overturned forty years of administrative law, leading to potential litigation over the interpretation of ambiguous laws previously decided by federal agencies. This article explores key questions for cybersecurity professionals and leaders as we enter a more contentious period of cybersecurity law.
Background
What is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Enhancing Incident Response Readiness with Wazuh]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/enhancing-incident-response-readiness.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/enhancing-incident-response-readiness.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T10:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incident response is a structured approach to managing and addressing security breaches or cyber-attacks. Security teams must overcome challenges such as timely detection, comprehensive data collection, and coordinated actions to enhance readiness. Improving these areas ensures a swift and effective response, minimizing damage and restoring normal operations quickly.
Challenges in incident]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Roundcube (05 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0647/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0647/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T07:38:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Roundcube. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Rockwell Automation Devices Allows Unauthorized Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-rockwell-automation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-rockwell-automation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T06:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A high-severity security bypass vulnerability has been disclosed in Rockwell Automation ControlLogix 1756 devices that could be exploited to execute common industrial protocol (CIP) programming and configuration commands.
The flaw, which is assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-6242, carries a CVSS v3.1 score of 8.4.
"A vulnerability exists in the affected products that allows a threat actor to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Trojan "BlankBot" Targets Turkish Users' Financial Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-trojan-blankbot-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-trojan-blankbot-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T04:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new Android banking trojan called BlankBot targeting Turkish users with an aim to steal financial information.
"BlankBot features a range of malicious capabilities, which include customer injections, keylogging, screen recording and it communicates with a control server over a WebSocket connection," Intel 471 said in an analysis published last week.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Compromise ISP to Deploy Malicious Software Updates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-linked-hackers-compromise-isp-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-linked-hackers-compromise-isp-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-05T04:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked threat actor known as Evasive Panda compromised an unnamed internet service provider (ISP) to push malicious software updates to target companies in mid-2023, highlighting a new level of sophistication associated with the group.
Evasive Panda, also known by the names Bronze Highland, Daggerfly, and StormBamboo, is a cyber espionage group that's been active since at least 2012,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DOJ and FTC Sue TikTok for Violating Children's Privacy Laws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/doj-and-ftc-sue-tiktok-for-violating.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/doj-and-ftc-sue-tiktok-for-violating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T09:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ), along with the Federal Trade Commission (FTC), filed a lawsuit against popular video-sharing platform TikTok for "flagrantly violating" children's privacy laws in the country.
The agencies claimed the company knowingly permitted children to create TikTok accounts and to view and share short-form videos and messages with adults and others on the service.
They]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Misconfigured Jupyter Notebooks with Repurposed Minecraft DDoS Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-jupyter.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-jupyter.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-03T03:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a new distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attack campaign targeting misconfigured Jupyter Notebooks.
The activity, codenamed Panamorfi by cloud security firm Aqua, utilizes a Java-based tool called mineping to launch a TCP flood DDoS attack. Mineping is a DDoS package designed for Minecraft game servers.
Attack chains entail the exploitation]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT41 Hackers Use ShadowPad, Cobalt Strike in Taiwanese Institute Cyber Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt41-hackers-use-shadowpad-cobalt.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt41-hackers-use-shadowpad-cobalt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Taiwanese government-affiliated research institute that specializes in computing and associated technologies was breached by nation-state threat actors with ties to China, according to new findings from Cisco Talos.
The unnamed organization was targeted as early as mid-July 2023 to deliver a variety of backdoors and post-compromise tools like ShadowPad and Cobalt Strike. It has been attributed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT28 Targets Diplomats with HeadLace Malware via Car Sale Phishing Lure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt28-targets-diplomats-with-headlace.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt28-targets-diplomats-with-headlace.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T16:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Russia-linked threat actor has been linked to a new campaign that employed a car for sale as a phishing lure to deliver a modular Windows backdoor called HeadLace.

"The campaign likely targeted diplomats and began as early as March 2024," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 said in a report published today, attributing it with medium to high level of confidence to APT28, which is also referred to as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (02 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0646/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0646/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T12:20:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (02 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0645/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0645/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T12:09:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (02 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0644/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0644/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T12:01:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Moxa (02 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0643/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0643/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T11:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Moxa. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Discover the All-in-One Cybersecurity Solution for SMBs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-discover-all-in-one.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-discover-all-in-one.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T11:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital battlefield, small and medium businesses (SMBs) face the same cyber threats as large corporations, but with fewer resources. Managed service providers (MSPs) are struggling to keep up with the demand for protection.
If your current cybersecurity strategy feels like a house of cards – a complex, costly mess of different vendors and tools – it's time for a change.
Introducing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mirai Botnet targeting OFBiz Servers Vulnerable to Directory Traversal]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/mirai-botnet-targeting-ofbiz-servers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/mirai-botnet-targeting-ofbiz-servers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T10:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Enterprise Resource Planning (ERP) Software is at the heart of many enterprising supporting human resources, accounting, shipping, and manufacturing. These systems can become very complex and difficult to maintain. They are often highly customized, which can make patching difficult. However, critical vulnerabilities keep affecting these systems and put critical business data at risk. 
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Windows Backdoor BITSLOTH Exploits BITS for Stealthy Communication]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-windows-backdoor-bitsloth-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-windows-backdoor-bitsloth-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T09:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a previously undocumented Windows backdoor that leverages a built-in feature called Background Intelligent Transfer Service (BITS) as a command-and-control (C2) mechanism.
The newly identified malware strain has been codenamed BITSLOTH by Elastic Security Labs, which made the discovery on June 25, 2024, in connection with a cyber attack targeting an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (02 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0642/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0642/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T08:36:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Releases High-Profile Russian Hackers in Diplomatic Prisoner Exchange]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-releases-high-profile-russian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-releases-high-profile-russian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T07:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a historic prisoner exchange between Belarus, Germany, Norway, Russia, Slovenia, and the U.S., two Russian nationals serving time for cybercrime activities have been freed and repatriated to their country.
This includes Roman Valerevich Seleznev and Vladislav Klyushin, who are part of a group of eight people who have been swapped back to Russia in exchange for the release of 16 people who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Abusing Cloudflare Tunnels to Evade Detection and Spread Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-abusing-cloudflare.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-abusing-cloudflare.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-02T07:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity companies are warning about an uptick in the abuse of Clouflare's TryCloudflare free service for malware delivery.
The activity, documented by both eSentire and Proofpoint, entails the use of TryCloudflare to create a one-time tunnel that acts as a conduit to relay traffic from an attacker-controlled server to a local machine through Cloudflare's infrastructure.
Attack chains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 1 Million Domains at Risk of 'Sitting Ducks' Domain Hijacking Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/over-1-million-domains-at-risk-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/over-1-million-domains-at-risk-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Over a million domains are susceptible to takeover by malicious actors by means of what has been called a Sitting Ducks attack.
The powerful attack vector, which exploits weaknesses in the domain name system (DNS), is being exploited by over a dozen Russian-nexus cybercriminal actors to stealthily hijack domains, a joint analysis published by Infoblox and Eclypsium has revealed.
"In a Sitting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Distributing Malicious Python Packages via Popular Developer Q&A Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-distributing-malicious-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-distributing-malicious-python.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In yet another sign that threat actors are always looking out for new ways to trick users into downloading malware, it has come to light that the question-and-answer (Q&A) platform known as Stack Exchange has been abused to direct unsuspecting developers to bogus Python packages capable of draining their cryptocurrency wallets.
"Upon installation, this code would execute automatically,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Banking Trojan BingoMod Steals Money, Wipes Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-banking-trojan-bingomod.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-banking-trojan-bingomod.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T12:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new Android remote access trojan (RAT) called BingoMod that not only performs fraudulent money transfers from the compromised devices but also wipes them in an attempt to erase traces of the malware.
Italian cybersecurity firm Cleafy, which discovered the RAT towards the end of May 2024, said the malware is under active development. It attributed the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Obfuscation: There Are Two Sides To Everything]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/obfuscation-there-are-two-sides-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/obfuscation-there-are-two-sides-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How to detect and prevent attackers from using these various techniques
Obfuscation is an important technique for protecting software that also carries risks, especially when used by malware authors. In this article, we examine obfuscation, its effects, and responses to it.
What Is Obfuscation?
Obfuscation is the technique of intentionally making information difficult to read, especially in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Adds App-Bound Encryption to Protect Cookies from Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-chrome-adds-app-bound-encryption.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-chrome-adds-app-bound-encryption.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's adding a new layer of protection to its Chrome browser through what's called app-bound encryption to prevent information-stealing malware from grabbing cookies on Windows systems.
"On Windows, Chrome uses the Data Protection API (DPAPI) which protects the data at rest from other users on the system or cold boot attacks," Will Harris from the Chrome security team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0641/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0641/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:24:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic Elasticsearch (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0640/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0640/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:18:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic Elasticsearch. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (01 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0639/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0639/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T07:16:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook Ads Lead to Fake Websites Stealing Credit Card Information]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/facebook-ads-lead-to-fake-websites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/facebook-ads-lead-to-fake-websites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-01T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook users are the target of a scam e-commerce network that uses hundreds of fake websites to steal personal and financial data using brand impersonation and malvertising tricks.
Recorded Future's Payment Fraud Intelligence team, which detected the campaign on April 17, 2024, has given it the name ERIAKOS owing to the use of the same content delivery network (CDN) oss.eriakos[.]com.
"These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DigiCert to Revoke 83,000+ SSL Certificates Due to Domain Validation Oversight]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/digicert-to-revoke-83000-ssl.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/digicert-to-revoke-83000-ssl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T14:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Certificate authority (CA) DigiCert has warned that it will be revoking a subset of SSL/TLS certificates within 24 hours due to an oversight with how it verified if a digital certificate is issued to the rightful owner of a domain.
The company said it will be taking the step of revoking certificates that do not have proper Domain Control Validation (DCV).
"Before issuing a certificate to a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korea-Linked Malware Targets Developers on Windows, Linux, and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korea-linked-malware-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/north-korea-linked-malware-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind an ongoing malware campaign targeting software developers have demonstrated new malware and tactics, expanding their focus to include Windows, Linux, and macOS systems.
The activity cluster, dubbed DEV#POPPER and linked to North Korea, has been found to have singled out victims across South Korea, North America, Europe, and the Middle East.
"This form of attack is an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Target Japanese Firms with LODEINFO and NOOPDOOR Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-japanese-firms.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/chinese-hackers-target-japanese-firms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese organizations are the target of a Chinese nation-state threat actor that leverages malware families like LODEINFO and NOOPDOOR to harvest sensitive information from compromised hosts while stealthily remaining under the radar in some cases for a time period ranging from two to three years.
Israeli cybersecurity company Cybereason is tracking the campaign under the name Cuckoo Spear,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How To Get the Most From Your Security Team’s Email Alert Budget]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-get-most-from-your-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-to-get-most-from-your-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[We’ll TL;DR the FUDdy introduction: we all know that phishing attacks are on the rise in scale and complexity, that AI is enabling more sophisticated attacks that evade traditional defenses, and the never-ending cybersecurity talent gap means we’re all struggling to keep security teams fully staffed. 
Given that reality, security teams need to be able to monitor and respond to threats]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Deploy 100K+ Malware Android Apps to Steal OTP Codes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-deploy-100k-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-deploy-100k-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malicious campaign has been observed making use of malicious Android apps to steal users' SMS messages since at least February 2022 as part of a large-scale campaign.
The malicious apps, spanning over 107,000 unique samples, are designed to intercept one-time passwords (OTPs) used for online account verification to commit identity fraud.
"Of those 107,000 malware samples, over 99,000 of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Espionage Group XDSpy Targets Companies in Russia and Moldova]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-espionage-group-xdspy-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-espionage-group-xdspy-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies in Russia and Moldova have been the target of a phishing campaign orchestrated by a little-known cyber espionage group known as XDSpy.
The findings come from cybersecurity firm F.A.C.C.T., which said the infection chains lead to the deployment of a malware called DSDownloader. The activity was observed this month, it added.
XDSpy is a threat actor of indeterminate origin that was first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic Kibana (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0638/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0638/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T08:37:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic Kibana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager  (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0637/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0637/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:49:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans HPE Aruba Networking ClearPass Policy Manager. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (31 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0636/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0636/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T07:38:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Settles for $1.4 Billion with Texas Over Illegal Biometric Data Collection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-settles-for-14-billion-with-texas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/meta-settles-for-14-billion-with-texas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-31T04:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta, the parent company of Facebook, Instagram, and WhatsApp, agreed to a record $1.4 billion settlement with the U.S. state of Texas over allegations that it illegally collected biometric data of millions of users without their permission, marking one of the largest penalties levied by regulators against the tech giant.
"This historic settlement demonstrates our commitment to standing up to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mandrake Spyware Found in Google Play Store Apps After Two Years]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-mandrake-spyware-found-in-google.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-mandrake-spyware-found-in-google.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new iteration of a sophisticated Android spyware called Mandrake has been discovered in five applications that were available for download from the Google Play Store and remained undetected for two years.
The applications attracted a total of more than 32,000 installations before being pulled from the app storefront, Kaspersky said in a Monday write-up. A majority of the downloads originated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans StormShield Management Center (30 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0635/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0635/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:44:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans StormShield Management Center. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Power and Peril of RMM Tools]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/the-power-and-peril-of-rmm-tools.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/the-power-and-peril-of-rmm-tools.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As more people work remotely, IT departments must manage devices distributed over different cities and countries relying on VPNs and remote monitoring and management (RMM) tools for system administration. 
However, like any new technology, RMM tools can also be used maliciously. Threat actors can establish connections to a victim's device and run commands, exfiltrate data, and stay]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Target Polish Businesses with Agent Tesla and Formbook Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-target-polish-businesses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cybercriminals-target-polish-businesses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T11:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detailed widespread phishing campaigns targeting small and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in Poland during May 2024 that led to the deployment of several malware families like Agent Tesla, Formbook, and Remcos RAT.
Some of the other regions targeted by the campaigns include Italy and Romania, according to cybersecurity firm ESET.
"Attackers used previously]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Threat Intelligence: Illuminating the Deep, Dark Cybercriminal Underground]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-threat-intelligence-illuminating.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/cyber-threat-intelligence-illuminating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
The deep and dark web, otherwise known as the cybercriminal underground, is where malicious actors gather to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (30 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0634/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0634/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T08:17:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance. Apple indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-23296 est...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SideWinder Cyber Attacks Target Maritime Facilities in Multiple Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-sidewinder-cyber-attacks-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-sidewinder-cyber-attacks-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T07:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nation-state threat actor known as SideWinder has been attributed to a new cyber espionage campaign targeting ports and maritime facilities in the Indian Ocean and Mediterranean Sea.
The BlackBerry Research and Intelligence Team, which discovered the activity, said targets of the spear-phishing campaign include countries like Pakistan, Egypt, Sri Lanka, Bangladesh, Myanmar, Nepal, and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OneDrive Phishing Scam Tricks Users into Running Malicious PowerShell Script]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/onedrive-phishing-scam-tricks-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/onedrive-phishing-scam-tricks-users.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about a new phishing campaign that targets Microsoft OneDrive users with the aim of executing a malicious PowerShell script.
"This campaign heavily relies on social engineering tactics to deceive users into executing a PowerShell script, thereby compromising their systems," Trellix security researcher Rafael Pena said in a Monday analysis.
The cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware ESXi Flaw Exploited by Ransomware Groups for Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vmware-esxi-flaw-exploited-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/vmware-esxi-flaw-exploited-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-30T04:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched security flaw impacting VMware ESXi hypervisors has been actively exploited by "several" ransomware groups to gain elevated permissions and deploy file-encrypting malware.
The attacks involve the exploitation of CVE-2024-37085 (CVSS score: 6.8), an Active Directory integration authentication bypass that allows an attacker to obtain administrative access to the host.
"A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Acronis Cyber Infrastructure Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-acronis-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-acronis-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T16:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity company Acronis is warning that a now-patched critical security flaw impacting its Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) product has been exploited in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-45249 (CVSS score: 9.8), concerns a case of remote code execution that stems from the use of default passwords.
The flaw impacts the following versions of Acronis Cyber Infrastructure (ACI) -

&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proofpoint Email Routing Flaw Exploited to Send Millions of Spoofed Phishing Emails]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/proofpoint-email-routing-flaw-exploited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/proofpoint-email-routing-flaw-exploited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor has been linked to a massive scam campaign that exploited an email routing misconfiguration in email security vendor Proofpoint's defenses to send millions of messages spoofing various legitimate companies.
"These emails echoed from official Proofpoint email relays with authenticated SPF and DKIM signatures, thus bypassing major security protections — all to deceive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Searchable Encryption Changes the Data Security Game]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-searchable-encryption-changes-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/how-searchable-encryption-changes-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Searchable Encryption has long been a mystery. An oxymoron. An unattainable dream of cybersecurity professionals everywhere.
Organizations know they must encrypt their most valuable, sensitive data to prevent data theft and breaches. They also understand that organizational data exists to be used. To be searched, viewed, and modified to keep businesses running. Unfortunately, our Network and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-034 (29 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-034/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-034/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T08:16:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA['Stargazer Goblin' Creates 3,000 Fake GitHub Accounts for Malware Spread]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/stargazer-goblin-creates-3000-fake.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/stargazer-goblin-creates-3000-fake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor known as Stargazer Goblin has set up a network of inauthentic GitHub accounts to fuel a Distribution-as-a-Service (DaaS) that propagates a variety of information-stealing malware and netting them $100,000 in illicit profits over the past year.
The network, which comprises over 3,000 accounts on the cloud-based code hosting platform, spans thousands of repositories that are used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Gh0st RAT Trojan Targets Chinese Windows Users via Fake Chrome Site]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gh0st-rat-trojan-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/gh0st-rat-trojan-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-29T04:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The remote access trojan known as Gh0st RAT has been observed being delivered by an "evasive dropper" called Gh0stGambit as part of a drive-by download scheme targeting Chinese-speaking Windows users.
These infections stem from a fake website ("chrome-web[.]com") serving malicious installer packages masquerading as Google's Chrome browser, indicating that users searching for the software on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Launch Operation to Remove PlugX Malware from Infected Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/french-authorities-launch-operation-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/french-authorities-launch-operation-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T06:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French judicial authorities, in collaboration with Europol, have launched a so-called "disinfection operation" to rid compromised hosts of a known malware called PlugX.
The Paris Prosecutor's Office, Parquet de Paris, said the initiative was launched on July 18 and that it's expected to continue for "several months."
It further said around a hundred victims located in France, Malta, Portugal,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious PyPI Package Targets macOS to Steal Google Cloud Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-pypi-package-targets-macos-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/malicious-pypi-package-targets-macos-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-27T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a malicious package on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that targets Apple macOS systems with the goal of stealing users' Google Cloud credentials from a narrow pool of victims.
The package, named "lr-utils-lib," attracted a total of 59 downloads before it was taken down. It was uploaded to the registry in early June 2024.
"The malware uses a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[This AI-Powered Cybercrime Service Bundles Phishing Kits with Malicious Android Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/spanish-hackers-bundle-phishing-kits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/spanish-hackers-bundle-phishing-kits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Spanish-speaking cybercrime group named GXC Team has been observed bundling phishing kits with malicious Android applications, taking malware-as-a-service (MaaS) offerings to the next level.
Singaporean cybersecurity company Group-IB, which has been tracking the e-crime actor since January 2023, described the crimeware solution as a "sophisticated AI-powered phishing-as-a-service platform"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0633/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0633/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T12:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0632/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0632/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:58:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0631/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0631/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:51:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM QRadar (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0630/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0630/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans IBM QRadar. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0629/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0629/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:27:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Offensive AI: The Sine Qua Non of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/offensive-ai-sine-qua-non-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/offensive-ai-sine-qua-non-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA["Peace is the virtue of civilization. War is its crime. Yet it is often in the furnace of war that the sharpest tools of peace are forged." - Victor Hugo.
In 1971, an unsettling message started appearing on several computers that comprised ARPANET, the precursor to what we now know as the Internet. The message, which read "I'm the Creeper: catch me if you can." was the output of a program named]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0628/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0628/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T10:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (26 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0627/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0627/"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T10:55:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DoJ Indicts North Korean Hacker for Ransomware Attacks on Hospitals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-doj-indicts-north-korean-hacker-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/us-doj-indicts-north-korean-hacker-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Thursday unsealed an indictment against a North Korean military intelligence operative for allegedly carrying out ransomware attacks against healthcare facilities in the country and funneling the payments to orchestrate additional intrusions into defense, technology, and government entities across the world.
"Rim Jong Hyok and his co-conspirators deployed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ongoing Cyberattack Targets Exposed Selenium Grid Services for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ongoing-cyberattack-targets-exposed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/ongoing-cyberattack-targets-exposed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T06:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are sounding the alarm over an ongoing campaign that's leveraging internet-exposed Selenium Grid services for illicit cryptocurrency mining.
Cloud security Wiz is tracking the activity under the name SeleniumGreed. The campaign, which is targeting older versions of Selenium (3.141.59 and prior), is believed to be underway since at least April 2023.
"Unbeknownst to most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike Warns of New Phishing Scam Targeting German Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-warns-of-new-phishing-scam.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/crowdstrike-warns-of-new-phishing-scam.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T05:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[CrowdStrike is alerting about an unfamiliar threat actor attempting to capitalize on the Falcon Sensor update fiasco to distribute dubious installers targeting German customers as part of a highly targeted campaign.
The cybersecurity company said it identified what it described as an unattributed spear-phishing attempt on July 24, 2024, distributing an inauthentic CrowdStrike Crash Reporter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Telerik Report Server Poses Remote Code Execution Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-telerik-report-server.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaw-in-telerik-report-server.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-26T04:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software is urging users to update their Telerik Report Server instances following the discovery of a critical security flaw that could result in remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-6327 (CVSS score: 9.9), impacts Report Server version 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.514) and earlier.
"In Progress Telerik Report Server versions prior to 2024 Q2 (10.1.24.709), a remote code]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>