<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-07-01T20:43:31.661Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws in CocoaPods Expose iOS and macOS Apps to Supply Chain Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaws-in-cocoapods-expose-ios.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/critical-flaws-in-cocoapods-expose-ios.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trio of security flaws has been uncovered in the CocoaPods dependency manager for Swift and Objective-C Cocoa projects that could be exploited to stage software supply chain attacks, putting downstream customers at severe risks.
The vulnerabilities allow "any malicious actor to claim ownership over thousands of unclaimed pods and insert malicious code into many of the most popular iOS and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CapraRAT Spyware Disguised as Popular Apps Threatens Android Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/caprarat-spyware-disguised-as-popular.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/caprarat-spyware-disguised-as-popular.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Transparent Tribe has continued to unleash malware-laced Android apps as part of a social engineering campaign to target individuals of interest.
"These APKs continue the group's trend of embedding spyware into curated video browsing applications, with a new expansion targeting mobile gamers, weapons enthusiasts, and TikTok fans," SentinelOne security researcher Alex]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSH (01 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-009</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-009"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T12:56:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 1 juillet 2024, OpenSSH a publié un avis de sécurité concernant la vulnérabilité critique CVE-2024-6387. Cette vulnérabilité permet à un attaquant non authentifié d'exécuter du code arbitraire à distance avec les privilèges *root*. L'éditeur précise que les versions 8.5p1 à 9.7p1 sont...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian Software Firm's Products Hacked to Spread Data-Stealing Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/indian-software-firms-products-hacked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/indian-software-firms-products-hacked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T12:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Installers for three different software products developed by an Indian company named Conceptworld have been trojanized to distribute information-stealing malware.
The installers correspond to Notezilla, RecentX, and Copywhiz, according to cybersecurity firm Rapid7, which discovered the supply chain compromise on June 18, 2024. The issue has since been remediated by Conceptworld as of June 24]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans OpenSSH (01 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0531</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0531"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T11:19:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans OpenSSH. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-End Secrets Security: Making a Plan to Secure Your Machine Identities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/end-to-end-secrets-security-making-plan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/end-to-end-secrets-security-making-plan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At the heart of every application are secrets. Credentials that allow human-to-machine and machine-to-machine communication. Machine identities outnumber human identities by a factor of 45-to-1 and represent the majority of secrets we need to worry about. According to CyberArk's recent research, 93% of organizations had two or more identity-related breaches in the past year. It is clear that we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New OpenSSH Vulnerability Could Lead to RCE as Root on Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-openssh-vulnerability-could-lead-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/new-openssh-vulnerability-could-lead-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenSSH maintainers have released security updates to contain a critical security flaw that could result in unauthenticated remote code execution with root privileges in glibc-based Linux systems.
The vulnerability has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-6387. It resides in the OpenSSH server component, also known as sshd, which is designed to listen for connections from any of the client]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (01 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0530</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0530"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T08:07:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-028 (01 juillet 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-028</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-028"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T07:47:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks Releases Critical Security Update for Routers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/juniper-networks-releases-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/07/juniper-networks-releases-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-07-01T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks has released out-of-band security updates to address a critical security flaw that could lead to an authentication bypass in some of its routers.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-2973, carries a CVSS score of 10.0, indicating maximum severity.
“An Authentication Bypass Using an Alternate Path or Channel vulnerability in Juniper Networks Session Smart Router or Conductor]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google to Block Entrust Certificates in Chrome Starting November 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-to-block-entrust-certificates-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-to-block-entrust-certificates-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-29T14:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's going to start blocking websites that use certificates from Entrust starting around November 1, 2024, in its Chrome browser, citing compliance failures and the certificate authority's inability to address security issues in a timely manner.
"Over the past several years, publicly disclosed incident reports highlighted a pattern of concerning behaviors by Entrust]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky Using TRANSLATEXT Chrome Extension to Steal Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/kimsuky-using-translatext-chrome.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/kimsuky-using-translatext-chrome.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T16:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Kimsuky has been linked to the use of a new malicious Google Chrome extension that's designed to steal sensitive information as part of an ongoing intelligence collection effort.
Zscaler ThreatLabz, which observed the activity in early March 2024, has codenamed the extension TRANSLATEXT, highlighting its ability to gather email addresses, usernames,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab Releases Patch for Critical CI/CD Pipeline Vulnerability and 13 Others]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/gitlab-releases-patch-for-critical-cicd.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/gitlab-releases-patch-for-critical-cicd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T14:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab has released security updates to address 14 security flaws, including one critical vulnerability that could be exploited to run continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) pipelines as any user.
The weaknesses, which affect GitLab Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE), have been addressed in versions 17.1.1, 17.0.3, and 16.11.5.
The most severe of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0529</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0529"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T12:39:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[8220 Gang Exploits Oracle WebLogic Server Flaws for Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/8220-gang-exploits-oracle-weblogic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/8220-gang-exploits-oracle-weblogic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have shed more light on the cryptocurrency mining operation conducted by the 8220 Gang by exploiting known security flaws in the Oracle WebLogic Server.
"The threat actor employs fileless execution techniques, using DLL reflective and process injection, allowing the malware code to run solely in memory and avoid disk-based detection mechanisms," Trend Micro researchers Ahmed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0528</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0528"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:56:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian LTS (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0527</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0527"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:49:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian LTS. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0526</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0526"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:37:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combatting the Evolving SaaS Kill Chain: How to Stay Ahead of Threat Actors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/combatting-evolving-saas-kill-chain-how.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/combatting-evolving-saas-kill-chain-how.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The modern kill chain is eluding enterprises because they aren’t protecting the infrastructure of modern business: SaaS. 
SaaS continues to dominate software adoption, and it accounts for the greatest share of public cloud spending. But enterprises and SMBs alike haven’t revised their security programs or adopted security tooling built for SaaS. 
Security teams keep jamming on-prem]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New SnailLoad Attack Exploits Network Latency to Spy on Users' Web Activities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-snailload-attack-exploits-network.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-snailload-attack-exploits-network.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of security researchers from the Graz University of Technology have demonstrated a new side-channel attack known as SnailLoad that could be used to remotely infer a user's web activity.
"SnailLoad exploits a bottleneck present on all Internet connections," the researchers said in a study released this week.
"This bottleneck influences the latency of network packets, allowing an attacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warn of Flaws in Widely Used Industrial Gas Analysis Equipment]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-warn-of-flaws-in-widely.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-warn-of-flaws-in-widely.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security flaws have been disclosed in Emerson Rosemount gas chromatographs that could be exploited by malicious actors to obtain sensitive information, induce a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, and even execute arbitrary commands.
The flaws impact GC370XA, GC700XA, and GC1500XA and reside in versions 4.1.5 and prior.
According to operational technology (OT) security firm Claroty, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Juniper Networks (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0525</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0525"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:34:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0524</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0524"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T07:08:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (28 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0523</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0523"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T06:58:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamViewer Detects Security Breach in Corporate IT Environment]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/teamviewer-detects-security-breach-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/teamviewer-detects-security-breach-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-28T05:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[TeamViewer on Thursday disclosed it detected an "irregularity" in its internal corporate IT environment on June 26, 2024.
"We immediately activated our response team and procedures, started investigations together with a team of globally renowned cyber security experts and implemented necessary remediation measures," the company said in a statement.
It further noted that its corporate IT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rust-Based P2PInfect Botnet Evolves with Miner and Ransomware Payloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rust-based-p2pinfect-botnet-evolves.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rust-based-p2pinfect-botnet-evolves.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T14:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The peer-to-peer malware botnet known as P2PInfect has been found targeting misconfigured Redis servers with ransomware and cryptocurrency miners.
The development marks the threat's transition from what appeared to be a dormant botnet with unclear motives to a financially motivated operation.
"With its latest updates to the crypto miner, ransomware payload, and rootkit elements, it demonstrates]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (27 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0522</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0522"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T11:53:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Secrets of Hidden AI Training on Your Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-secrets-of-hidden-ai-training-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-secrets-of-hidden-ai-training-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While some SaaS threats are clear and visible, others are hidden in plain sight, both posing significant risks to your organization. Wing's research indicates that an astounding 99.7% of organizations utilize applications embedded with AI functionalities. These AI-driven tools are indispensable, providing seamless experiences from collaboration and communication to work management and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Python to Build Secure Blockchain Applications]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-to-use-python-to-build-secure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-to-use-python-to-build-secure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know it’s now possible to build blockchain applications, known also as decentralized applications (or “dApps” for short) in native Python? Blockchain development has traditionally required learning specialized languages, creating a barrier for many developers… until now. AlgoKit, an all-in-one development toolkit for Algorand, enables developers to build blockchain applications in pure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prompt Injection Flaw in Vanna AI Exposes Databases to RCE Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prompt-injection-flaw-in-vanna-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prompt-injection-flaw-in-vanna-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a high-severity security flaw in the Vanna.AI library that could be exploited to achieve remote code execution vulnerability via prompt injection techniques.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-5565 (CVSS score: 8.1), relates to a case of prompt injection in the "ask" function that could be exploited to trick the library into executing arbitrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian National Indicted for Cyber Attacks on Ukraine Before 2022 Invasion]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-national-indicted-for-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-national-indicted-for-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T07:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 22-year-old Russian national has been indicted in the U.S. for his alleged role in staging destructive cyber attacks against Ukraine and its allies in the days leading to Russia's full-blown military invasion of Ukraine in early 2022.
Amin Timovich Stigal, the defendant in question, is assessed to be affiliated with the Main Directorate of the General Staff of the Armed Forces of the Russian]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (27 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0521</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0521"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T06:48:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical SQLi Vulnerability Found in Fortra FileCatalyst Workflow Application]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/critical-sqli-vulnerability-found-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/critical-sqli-vulnerability-found-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-27T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in Fortra FileCatalyst Workflow that, if left unpatched, could allow an attacker to tamper with the application database.
Tracked as CVE-2024-5276, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.8. It impacts FileCatalyst Workflow versions 5.1.6 Build 135 and earlier. It has been addressed in version 5.1.6 build 139.
"An SQL injection vulnerability in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New MOVEit Transfer Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation - Patch ASAP!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-moveit-transfer-vulnerability-under.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-moveit-transfer-vulnerability-under.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T14:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly disclosed critical security flaw impacting Progress Software MOVEit Transfer is already seeing exploitation attempts in the wild shortly after details of the bug were publicly disclosed.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-5806 (CVSS score: 9.1), concerns an authentication bypass that impacts the following versions -

From 2023.0.0 before 2023.0.11
From 2023.1.0 before 2023.1.6, and&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Progress (26 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0520</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0520"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T11:52:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Progress. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese and N. Korean Hackers Target Global Infrastructure with Ransomware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-and-n-korean-hackers-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-and-n-korean-hackers-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T10:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with suspected ties to China and North Korea have been linked to ransomware and data encryption attacks targeting government and critical infrastructure sectors across the world between 2021 and 2023.
While one cluster of activity has been associated with the ChamelGang (aka CamoFei), the second cluster overlaps with activity previously attributed to Chinese and North Korean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Practical Guidance For Securing Your Software Supply Chain]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/practical-guidance-for-securing-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/practical-guidance-for-securing-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The heightened regulatory and legal pressure on software-producing organizations to secure their supply chains and ensure the integrity of their software should come as no surprise. In the last several years, the software supply chain has become an increasingly attractive target for attackers who see opportunities to force-multiply their attacks by orders of magnitude. For example, look no]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Patches AirPods Bluetooth Vulnerability That Could Allow Eavesdropping]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/apple-patches-airpods-bluetooth.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/apple-patches-airpods-bluetooth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has released a firmware update for AirPods that could allow a malicious actor to gain access to the headphones in an unauthorized manner.
Tracked as CVE-2024-27867, the authentication issue affects AirPods (2nd generation and later), AirPods Pro (all models), AirPods Max, Powerbeats Pro, and Beats Fit Pro.
"When your headphones are seeking a connection request to one of your previously]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Credit Card Skimmer Targets WordPress, Magento, and OpenCart Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-credit-card-skimmer-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-credit-card-skimmer-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T08:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple content management system (CMS) platforms like WordPress, Magento, and OpenCart have been targeted by a new credit card web skimmer called Caesar Cipher Skimmer.
A web skimmer refers to malware that is injected into e-commerce sites with the goal of stealing financial and payment information. 
According to Sucuri, the latest campaign entails making malicious modifications to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (26 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0519</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0519"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:54:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Medusa Android Trojan Targets Banking Users Across 7 Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-medusa-android-trojan-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-medusa-android-trojan-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T07:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an updated version of an Android banking trojan called Medusa that has been used to target users in Canada, France, Italy, Spain, Turkey, the U.K., and the U.S.
The new fraud campaigns, observed in May 2024 and active since July 2023, manifested through five different botnets operated by various affiliates, cybersecurity firm Cleafy said in an analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 110,000 Websites Affected by Hijacked Polyfill Supply Chain Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/over-110000-websites-affected-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/over-110000-websites-affected-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-26T04:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has taken steps to block ads for e-commerce sites that use the Polyfill.io service after a Chinese company acquired the domain and modified the JavaScript library ("polyfill.js") to redirect users to malicious and scam sites.
More than 110,000 sites that embed the library are impacted by the supply chain attack, Sansec said in a Tuesday report.
Polyfill is a popular library that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans LibreOffice (25 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0518</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0518"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T11:34:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Libreoffice. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Attack Technique Exploits Microsoft Management Console Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-attack-technique-exploits-microsoft.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-attack-technique-exploits-microsoft.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T10:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are exploiting a novel attack technique in the wild that leverages specially crafted management saved console (MSC) files to gain full code execution using Microsoft Management Console (MMC) and evade security defenses.
Elastic Security Labs has codenamed the approach GrimResource after identifying an artifact ("sccm-updater.msc") that was uploaded to the VirusTotal malware]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Cut Costs with a Browser Security Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-to-cut-costs-with-browser-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-to-cut-costs-with-browser-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T09:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Browser security is becoming increasingly popular, as organizations understand the need to protect at the point of risk - the browser. Network and endpoint solutions are limited in their ability to protect from web-borne threats like phishing websites or malicious browser extensions. They also do not protect from internal data exfiltration, like employees pasting sensitive data to ChatGPT. As it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cyberthreat 'Boolka' Deploying BMANAGER Trojan via SQLi Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-cyberthreat-boolka-deploying.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-cyberthreat-boolka-deploying.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T09:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat actor dubbed Boolka has been observed compromising websites with malicious scripts to deliver a modular trojan codenamed BMANAGER.
"The threat actor behind this campaign has been carrying out opportunistic SQL injection attacks against websites in various countries since at least 2022," Group-IB researchers Rustam Mirkasymov and Martijn van den Berk said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Citrix Secure Access client (25 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0517</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0517"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:04:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Citrix Secure Access client. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans WordPress (25 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0516</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0516"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T07:03:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans WordPress. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (25 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0515</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0515"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T06:58:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wikileaks' Julian Assange Released from U.K. Prison, Heads to Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/wikileaks-julian-assange-released-from.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/wikileaks-julian-assange-released-from.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T05:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WikiLeaks founder Julian Assange has been freed in the U.K. and has departed the country after serving more than five years in a maximum security prison at Belmarsh for what was described by the U.S. government as the "largest compromises of classified information in the history" of the country.
Capping off a 14-year legal saga, Assange, 52, pleaded guilty to one criminal count of conspiring to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 FIN9-linked Vietnamese Hackers Indicted in $71M U.S. Cybercrime Spree]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/4-fin9-linked-vietnamese-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/4-fin9-linked-vietnamese-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T03:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Four Vietnamese nationals with ties to the FIN9 cybercrime group have been indicted in the U.S. for their involvement in a series of computer intrusions that caused over $71 million in losses to companies.
The defendants, Ta Van Tai (aka Quynh Hoa and Bich Thuy), Nguyen Viet Quoc (aka Tien Nguyen), Nguyen Trang Xuyen, and Nguyen Van Truong (aka Chung Nguyen), have been accused of conducting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple WordPress Plugins Compromised: Hackers Create Rogue Admin Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/multiple-wordpress-plugins-compromised.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/multiple-wordpress-plugins-compromised.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-25T03:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple WordPress plugins have been backdoored to inject malicious code that makes it possible to create rogue administrator accounts with the aim of performing arbitrary actions.
"The injected malware attempts to create a new administrative user account and then sends those details back to the attacker-controlled server," Wordfence security researcher Chloe Chamberland said in a Monday alert.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Introduces Project Naptime for AI-Powered Vulnerability Research]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-introduces-project-naptime-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-introduces-project-naptime-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has developed a new framework called Project Naptime that it says enables a large language model (LLM) to carry out vulnerability research with an aim to improve automated discovery approaches.
"The Naptime architecture is centered around the interaction between an AI agent and a target codebase," Google Project Zero researchers Sergei Glazunov and Mark Brand said. "The agent is provided]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical RCE Vulnerability Discovered in Ollama AI Infrastructure Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/critical-rce-vulnerability-discovered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/critical-rce-vulnerability-discovered.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T13:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detailed a now-patch security flaw affecting the Ollama open-source artificial intelligence (AI) infrastructure platform that could be exploited to achieve remote code execution.
Tracked as CVE-2024-37032, the vulnerability has been codenamed Probllama by cloud security firm Wiz. Following responsible disclosure on May 5, 2024, the issue was addressed in version]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ease the Burden with AI-Driven Threat Intelligence Reporting]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ease-burden-with-ai-driven-threat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ease-burden-with-ai-driven-threat.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T11:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
Cybersecurity professionals are facing unprecedented challenges as they strive to manage increasing workloads]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-027 (24 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-027</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-027"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T08:13:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RedJuliett Cyber Espionage Campaign Hits 75 Taiwanese Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/redjuliett-cyber-espionage-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/redjuliett-cyber-espionage-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A likely China-linked state-sponsored threat actor has been linked to a cyber espionage campaign targeting government, academic, technology, and diplomatic organizations in Taiwan between November 2023 and April 2024.
Recorded Future's Insikt Group is tracking the activity under the name RedJuliett, describing it as a cluster that operates Fuzhou, China, to support Beijing's intelligence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple Threat Actors Deploying Open-Source Rafel RAT to Target Android Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/iranian-hackers-deploy-rafel-rat-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/iranian-hackers-deploy-rafel-rat-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-24T05:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple threat actors, including cyber espionage groups, are employing an open-source Android remote administration tool called Rafel RAT to meet their operational objectives by masquerading it as Instagram, WhatsApp, and various e-commerce and antivirus apps.
"It provides malicious actors with a powerful toolkit for remote administration and control, enabling a range of malicious activities]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ExCobalt Cyber Gang Targets Russian Sectors with New GoRed Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/excobalt-cyber-gang-targets-russian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/excobalt-cyber-gang-targets-russian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian organizations have been targeted by a cybercrime gang called ExCobalt using a previously unknown Golang-based backdoor known as GoRed.
"ExCobalt focuses on cyber espionage and includes several members active since at least 2016 and presumably once part of the notorious Cobalt Gang," Positive Technologies researchers Vladislav Lunin and Alexander Badayev said in a technical report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: New Adware Campaign Targets Meta Quest App Seekers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/warning-new-adware-campaign-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/warning-new-adware-campaign-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new campaign is tricking users searching for the Meta Quest (formerly Oculus) application for Windows into downloading a new adware family called AdsExhaust.
"The adware is capable of exfiltrating screenshots from infected devices and interacting with browsers using simulated keystrokes," cybersecurity firm eSentire said in an analysis, adding it identified the activity earlier this month.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Sanctions 12 Kaspersky Executives Amid Software Ban]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/us-treasury-sanctions-12-kaspersky.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/us-treasury-sanctions-12-kaspersky.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-22T06:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) imposed sanctions against a dozen individuals serving executive and senior leadership roles at Kaspersky Lab, a day after the Russian company was banned by the Commerce Department.
The move "underscores our commitment to ensure the integrity of our cyber domain and to protect our citizens against malicious cyber]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Deploy SpiceRAT and SugarGh0st in Global Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-hackers-deploy-spicerat-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-hackers-deploy-spicerat-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented Chinese-speaking threat actor codenamed SneakyChef has been linked to an espionage campaign primarily targeting government entities across Asia and EMEA (Europe, Middle East, and Africa) with SugarGh0st malware since at least August 2023.
"SneakyChef uses lures that are scanned documents of government agencies, most of which are related to various countries' Ministries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Military-themed Email Scam Spreads Malware to Infect Pakistani Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/military-themed-emails-used-to-spread.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/military-themed-emails-used-to-spread.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T13:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a new phishing campaign that has been identified as targeting people in Pakistan using a custom backdoor.
Dubbed PHANTOM#SPIKE by Securonix, the unknown threat actors behind the activity have leveraged military-related phishing documents to activate the infection sequence.
"While there are many methods used today to deploy malware, the threat actors]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (21 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0514</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0514"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T12:19:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (21 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0513</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0513"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T12:06:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (21 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0512</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0512"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:59:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Tines's SOC Automation Capability Matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-to-use-tiness-soc-automation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-to-use-tiness-soc-automation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created by John Tuckner and the team at automation and AI-powered workflow platform Tines, the SOC Automation Capability Matrix (SOC ACM) is a set of techniques designed to help security operations teams understand their automation capabilities and respond more effectively to incidents. 
A customizable, vendor-agnostic tool featuring lists of automation opportunities, it's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oyster Backdoor Spreading via Trojanized Popular Software Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oyster-backdoor-spreading-via.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oyster-backdoor-spreading-via.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malvertising campaign is leveraging trojanized installers for popular software such as Google Chrome and Microsoft Teams to drop a backdoor called Oyster (aka Broomstick and CleanUpLoader).
That's according to findings from Rapid7, which identified lookalike websites hosting the malicious payloads that users are redirected to after searching for them on search engines like Google and Bing.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Serv-U Vulnerability Under Active Attack - Patch Immediately]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/solarwinds-serv-u-vulnerability-under.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/solarwinds-serv-u-vulnerability-under.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T08:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched high-severity flaw impacting SolarWinds Serv-U file transfer software is being actively exploited by malicious actors in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-28995 (CVSS score: 8.6), concerns a directory transversal bug that could allow attackers to read sensitive files on the host machine.
Affecting all versions of the software prior to and including Serv-U 15.4.2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits ESET (21 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0511</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0511"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T08:53:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits ESET. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (21 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0510</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0510"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T08:46:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Bans Kaspersky Software, Citing National Security Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/us-bans-kaspersky-software-citing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/us-bans-kaspersky-software-citing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-21T04:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Commerce's Bureau of Industry and Security (BIS) on Thursday announced a "first of its kind" ban that prohibits Kaspersky Lab's U.S. subsidiary from directly or indirectly offering its security software in the country.
The blockade also extends to the cybersecurity company's affiliates, subsidiaries and parent companies, the department said, adding the action is based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover UEFI Vulnerability Affecting Multiple Intel CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-uefi-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-uefi-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a now-patched security flaw in Phoenix SecureCore UEFI firmware that affects multiple families of Intel Core desktop and mobile processors.
Tracked as CVE-2024-0762 (CVSS score: 7.5), the "UEFIcanhazbufferoverflow" vulnerability has been described as a case of a buffer overflow stemming from the use of an unsafe variable in the Trusted Platform]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Diplomatic Entities Targeted in Russian-Linked Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/french-diplomatic-entities-targeted-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/french-diplomatic-entities-targeted-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State-sponsored actors with ties to Russia have been linked to targeted cyber attacks aimed at French diplomatic entities, the country's information security agency ANSSI said in an advisory.
The attacks have been attributed to a cluster tracked by Microsoft under the name Midnight Blizzard (formerly Nobelium), which overlaps with activity tracked as APT29, BlueBravo, Cloaked Ursa, Cozy Bear,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans SonicWall SonicOS (20 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0509</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0509"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:34:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Sonicwall. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (20 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0508</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0508"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T12:29:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Tool Overload: Why MSPs Are Still Drowning with Countless Cybersecurity Tools in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/tool-overload-why-msps-are-still.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/tool-overload-why-msps-are-still.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Highlights
Complex Tool Landscape: Explore the wide array of cybersecurity tools used by MSPs, highlighting the common challenge of managing multiple systems that may overlap in functionality but lack integration.Top Cybersecurity Challenges: Discuss the main challenges MSPs face, including integration issues, limited visibility across systems, and the high cost and complexity of maintaining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Cyber Espionage Targets Telecom Operators in Asia Since 2021]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-cyber-espionage-targets-telecom.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-cyber-espionage-targets-telecom.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T10:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber espionage groups associated with China have been linked to a long-running campaign that has infiltrated several telecom operators located in a single Asian country at least since 2021.
"The attackers placed backdoors on the networks of targeted companies and also attempted to steal credentials," the Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Rust-based Fickle Malware Uses PowerShell for UAC Bypass and Data Exfiltration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-rust-based-fickle-malware-uses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-rust-based-fickle-malware-uses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new Rust-based information stealer malware called Fickle Stealer has been observed being delivered via multiple attack chains with the goal of harvesting sensitive information from compromised hosts.
Fortinet FortiGuard Labs said it's aware of four different distribution methods -- namely VBA dropper, VBA downloader, link downloader, and executable downloader -- with some of them using a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Cloud Function (20 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0507</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0507"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T07:19:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilités a été découverte dans Spring Cloud Function. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover New Evasive SquidLoader Malware Targeting Chinese Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/experts-uncover-new-evasive-squidloader.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/experts-uncover-new-evasive-squidloader.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-20T06:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new evasive malware loader named SquidLoader that spreads via phishing campaigns targeting Chinese organizations.
AT&T LevelBlue Labs, which first observed the malware in late April 2024, said it incorporates features that are designed to thwart static and dynamic analysis and ultimately evade detection.
Attack chains leverage phishing emails that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kraken Crypto Exchange Hit by $3 Million Theft Exploiting Zero-Day Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/kraken-crypto-exchange-hit-by-3-million.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/kraken-crypto-exchange-hit-by-3-million.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T16:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Kraken revealed that an unnamed security researcher exploited an "extremely critical" zero-day flaw in its platform to steal $3 million in digital assets and refused to return them.
Details of the incident were shared by Kraken's Chief Security Officer, Nick Percoco, on X (formerly Twitter), stating it received a Bug Bounty program alert about a bug that "allowed them to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Cyber Espionage Group Exploits Fortinet, Ivanti and VMware Zero-Days]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-cyber-espionage-group-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-cyber-espionage-group-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T15:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-nexus cyber espionage actor linked to the zero-day exploitation of security flaws in Fortinet, Ivanti, and VMware devices has been observed utilizing multiple persistence mechanisms in order to maintain unfettered access to compromised environments.
"Persistence mechanisms encompassed network devices, hypervisors, and virtual machines, ensuring alternative channels remain available]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🇬🇧 Malicious activities linked to the Nobelium intrusion set (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-001</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/ioc/CERTFR-2024-IOC-001"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T12:52:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[🇬🇧 The following indicators of compromise are associated with the phishing campaigns by the Nobelium intrusion set described in the CERTFR-2024-CTI-006 report. These technical elements are provided to help detecting malicious activities in logs or inside live network trafic. DOWNLOAD IOCs (JSON...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0506</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0506"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T11:30:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Case Study: Unmanaged GTM Tags Become a Security Nightmare]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-case-study-unmanaged-gtm-tags.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-case-study-unmanaged-gtm-tags.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Are your tags really safe with Google Tag Manager? If you've been thinking that using GTM means that your tracking tags and pixels are safely managed, then it might be time to think again. In this article we look at how a big-ticket seller that does business on every continent came unstuck when it forgot that you can’t afford to allow tags to go unmanaged or become misconfigured. 
Read the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Void Arachne Uses Deepfakes and AI to Deliver Malicious VPNs to Chinese Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/void-arachne-uses-deepfakes-and-ai-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/void-arachne-uses-deepfakes-and-ai-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking users are the target of a never-before-seen threat activity cluster codenamed Void Arachne that employs malicious Windows Installer (MSI) files for virtual private networks (VPNs) to deliver a command-and-control (C&C) framework called Winos 4.0.
"The campaign also promotes compromised MSI files embedded with nudifiers and deepfake pornography-generating software, as well as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: Markopolo's Scam Targeting Crypto Users via Fake Meeting Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/warning-markopolos-scam-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/warning-markopolos-scam-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T10:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A threat actor who goes by alias markopolo has been identified as behind a large-scale cross-platform scam that targets digital currency users on social media with information stealer malware and carries out cryptocurrency theft.
The attack chains involve the use of a purported virtual meeting software named Vortax (and 23 other apps) that are used as a conduit to deliver Rhadamanthys, StealC,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[🇬🇧 Malicious activities linked to the Nobelium intrusion set (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-006</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-006"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T09:20:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several cyberattacks against French diplomatic entities can be linked to the Nobelium intrusion set. Nobelium is an intrusion set active since at least October 2020, used against high-value targets, most likely for espionage purposes. Western diplomatic entities, such as embassies and Ministries...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0505</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0505"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:41:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moodle. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0504</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0504"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T08:32:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (19 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0503</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0503"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T07:58:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mailcow Mail Server Flaws Expose Servers to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/mailcow-mail-server-flaws-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/mailcow-mail-server-flaws-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-19T07:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in the Mailcow open-source mail server suite that could be exploited by malicious actors to achieve arbitrary code execution on susceptible instances.
Both shortcomings impact all versions of the software prior to version 2024-04, which was released on April 4, 2024. The issues were responsibly disclosed by SonarSource on March 22, 2024.
The flaws]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal Foundation Warns Against EU's Plan to Scan Private Messages for CSAM]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/signal-foundation-warns-against-eus.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/signal-foundation-warns-against-eus.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T16:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A controversial proposal put forth by the European Union to scan users' private messages for detection child sexual abuse material (CSAM) poses severe risks to end-to-end encryption (E2EE), warned Meredith Whittaker, president of the Signal Foundation, which maintains the privacy-focused messaging service of the same name.
"Mandating mass scanning of private communications fundamentally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploit Free Software Lures to Deploy Hijack Loader and Vidar Stealer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybercriminals-exploit-free-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybercriminals-exploit-free-software.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T13:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are luring unsuspecting users with free or pirated versions of commercial software to deliver a malware loader called Hijack Loader, which then deploys an information stealer known as Vidar Stealer.
"Adversaries had managed to trick users into downloading password-protected archive files containing trojanized copies of a Cisco Webex Meetings App (ptService.exe)," Trellix security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (18 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0502</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0502"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T12:23:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Annual SaaS Security Report: 2025 CISO Plans and Priorities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-annual-saas-security-report-2025.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-annual-saas-security-report-2025.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T11:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Seventy percent of enterprises are prioritizing investment in SaaS security by establishing dedicated teams to secure SaaS applications, as part of a growing trend of maturity in this field of cybersecurity, according to a new survey released this month by the Cloud Security Alliance (CSA).
Despite economic instability and major job cuts in 2023, organizations drastically increased investment in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Targets Exposed Docker APIs for Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-malware-targets-exposed-docker-apis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-malware-targets-exposed-docker-apis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T09:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new malware campaign that targets publicly exposed Docket API endpoints with the aim of delivering cryptocurrency miners and other payloads.
Included among the tools deployed is a remote access tool that's capable of downloading and executing more malicious programs as well as a utility to propagate the malware via SSH, cloud analytics platform Datadog]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Issues Patches for Cloud Foundation, vCenter Server, and vSphere ESXi]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/vmware-issues-patches-for-cloud.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/vmware-issues-patches-for-cloud.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T08:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released updates to address critical flaws impacting Cloud Foundation, vCenter Server, and vSphere ESXi that could be exploited to achieve privilege escalation and remote code execution.
The list of vulnerabilities is as follows -

CVE-2024-37079 & CVE-2024-37080 (CVSS scores: 9.8) - Multiple heap-overflow vulnerabilities in the implementation of the DCE/RPC protocol that could]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Police Extradites Malaysians Linked to Android Malware Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/singapore-police-extradites-malaysians.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/singapore-police-extradites-malaysians.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-18T07:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore Police Force (SPF) has announced the extradition of two men from Malaysia for their alleged involvement in a mobile malware campaign targeting citizens in the country since June 2023.
The unnamed individuals, aged 26 and 47, engaged in scams that tricked unsuspecting users into downloading malicious apps onto their Android devices via phishing campaigns with the aim of stealing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-026 (17 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-026</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-026"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS Patches Critical Authentication Bypass Flaw in Multiple Router Models]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/asus-patches-critical-authentication.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/asus-patches-critical-authentication.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ASUS has shipped software updates to address a critical security flaw impacting its routers that could be exploited by malicious actors to bypass authentication.
Tracked as CVE-2024-3080, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"Certain ASUS router models have authentication bypass vulnerability, allowing unauthenticated remote attackers to log in the device,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Infiltrate East Asian Firm for 3 Years Using F5 Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-linked-hackers-infiltrate-east.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-linked-hackers-infiltrate-east.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected China-nexus cyber espionage actor has been attributed as behind a prolonged attack against an unnamed organization located in East Asia for a period of about three years, with the adversary establishing persistence using legacy F5 BIG-IP appliances and using it as an internal command-and-control (C&C) for defense evasion purposes.
Cybersecurity company Sygnia, which responded to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is DevSecOps and Why is it Essential for Secure Software Delivery?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/what-is-devsecops-and-why-is-it.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/what-is-devsecops-and-why-is-it.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional application security practices are not effective in the modern DevOps world. When security scans are run only at the end of the software delivery lifecycle (either right before or after a service is deployed), the ensuing process of compiling and fixing vulnerabilities creates massive overhead for developers. The overhead that degrades velocity and puts production deadlines at risk.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Nextcloud (17 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0501</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0501"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T08:43:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Nextcloud. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Elastic Kibana (17 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0500</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0500"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:25:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Elastic Kibana. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans NetApp StorageGRID (17 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0499</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0499"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T07:15:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits NetApp. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Legitimate Websites to Deliver BadSpace Windows Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-websites-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-websites-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T06:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Legitimate-but-compromised websites are being used as a conduit to deliver a Windows backdoor dubbed BadSpace under the guise of fake browser updates.
"The threat actor employs a multi-stage attack chain involving an infected website, a command-and-control (C2) server, in some cases a fake browser update, and a JScript downloader to deploy a backdoor into the victim's system," German]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NiceRAT Malware Targets South Korean Users via Cracked Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/nicerat-malware-targets-south-korean.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/nicerat-malware-targets-south-korean.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-17T05:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed deploying a malware called NiceRAT to co-opt infected devices into a botnet.
The attacks, which target South Korean users, are designed to propagate the malware under the guise of cracked software, such as Microsoft Windows, or tools that purport to offer license verification for Microsoft Office.
"Due to the nature of crack programs, information sharing amongst]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.K. Hacker Linked to Notorious Scattered Spider Group Arrested in Spain]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/uk-hacker-linked-to-notorious-scattered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/uk-hacker-linked-to-notorious-scattered.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-16T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement authorities have allegedly arrested a key member of the notorious cybercrime group called Scattered Spider.
The individual, a 22-year-old man from the United Kingdom, was arrested this week in the Spanish city of Palma de Mallorca as he attempted to board a flight to Italy. The move is said to be a joint effort between the U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) and the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grandoreiro Banking Trojan Hits Brazil as Smishing Scams Surge in Pakistan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/grandoreiro-banking-trojan-hits-brazil.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/grandoreiro-banking-trojan-hits-brazil.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T09:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan has become the latest target of a threat actor called the Smishing Triad, marking the first expansion of its footprint beyond the E.U., Saudi Arabia, the U.A.E., and the U.S.
"The group's latest tactic involves sending malicious messages on behalf of Pakistan Post to customers of mobile carriers via iMessage and SMS," Resecurity said in a report published earlier this week. "The goal is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistani Hackers Use DISGOMOJI Malware in Indian Government Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/pakistani-hackers-use-disgomoji-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/pakistani-hackers-use-disgomoji-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T08:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected Pakistan-based threat actor has been linked to a cyber espionage campaign targeting Indian government entities in 2024.
Cybersecurity company Volexity is tracking the activity under the moniker UTA0137, noting the adversary's exclusive use of a malware called DISGOMOJI that's written in Golang and is designed to infect Linux systems.
"It is a modified version of the public project]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Halts AI Training on EU User Data Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/meta-halts-ai-training-on-eu-user-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/meta-halts-ai-training-on-eu-user-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-15T07:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta on Friday said it's delaying its efforts to train the company's large language models (LLMs) using public content shared by adult users on Facebook and Instagram in the European Union following a request from the Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC).
The company expressed disappointment at having to put its AI plans on pause, stating it had taken into account feedback from regulators and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Privacy Sandbox Accused of User Tracking by Austrian Non-Profit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/googles-privacy-sandbox-accused-of-user.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/googles-privacy-sandbox-accused-of-user.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's plans to deprecate third-party tracking cookies in its Chrome web browser with Privacy Sandbox has run into fresh trouble after Austrian privacy non-profit noyb (none of your business) said the feature can still be used to track users.
"While the so-called 'Privacy Sandbox' is advertised as an improvement over extremely invasive third-party tracking, the tracking is now simply done]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0498</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0498"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T12:48:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0497</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0497"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T12:42:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn to Secure Petabyte-Scale Data in a Webinar with Industry Titans]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/learn-to-secure-petabyte-scale-data-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/learn-to-secure-petabyte-scale-data-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T12:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Data is growing faster than ever. Remember when petabytes (that's 1,000,000 gigabytes!) were only for tech giants? Well, that's so last decade! Today, businesses of all sizes are swimming in petabytes.
But this isn't just about storage anymore. This data is ALIVE—it's constantly accessed, analyzed, shared, and even used to train the next wave of AI.
This creates a huge challenge: how do you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0496</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0496"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T12:23:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0495</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0495"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T12:14:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Regulated Industries are Turning to Military-Grade Cyber Defenses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/why-regulated-industries-are-turning-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/why-regulated-industries-are-turning-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T11:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cyber threats loom large and data breaches continue to pose increasingly significant risks. Organizations and industries that handle sensitive information and valuable assets make prime targets for cybercriminals seeking financial gain or strategic advantage. 
Which is why many highly regulated sectors, from finance to utilities, are turning to military-grade cyber defenses to safeguard]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans FreeRADIUS (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0494</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0494"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T09:35:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans FreeRADIUS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ZKTeco Biometric System Found Vulnerable to 24 Critical Security Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zkteco-biometric-system-found.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zkteco-biometric-system-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of a hybrid biometric access system from Chinese manufacturer ZKTeco has uncovered two dozen security flaws that could be used by attackers to defeat authentication, steal biometric data, and even deploy malicious backdoors.
"By adding random user data to the database or using a fake QR code, a nefarious actor can easily bypass the verification process and gain unauthorized access,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (14 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0493</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0493"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T08:01:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Brazilian Fintech with Sophisticated Phishing Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/north-korean-hackers-target-brazilian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/north-korean-hackers-target-brazilian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors linked to North Korea have accounted for one-third of all the phishing activity targeting Brazil since 2020, as the country's emergence as an influential power has drawn the attention of cyber espionage groups.
"North Korean government-backed actors have targeted the Brazilian government and Brazil's aerospace, technology, and financial services sectors," Google's Mandiant and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Delays AI-Powered Recall Feature for Copilot+ PCs Amid Security Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-delays-ai-powered-recall.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-delays-ai-powered-recall.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-14T04:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Thursday revealed that it's delaying the rollout of the controversial artificial intelligence (AI)-powered Recall feature for Copilot+ PCs.
To that end, the company said it intends to shift from general availability preview available first in the Windows Insider Program (WIP) in the coming weeks.
"We are adjusting the release model for Recall to leverage the expertise of the Windows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Attack Technique 'Sleepy Pickle' Targets Machine Learning Models]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-attack-technique-sleepy-pickle.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-attack-technique-sleepy-pickle.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The security risks posed by the Pickle format have once again come to the fore with the discovery of a new "hybrid machine learning (ML) model exploitation technique" dubbed Sleepy Pickle.
The attack method, per Trail of Bits, weaponizes the ubiquitous format used to package and distribute machine learning (ML) models to corrupt the model itself, posing a severe supply chain risk to an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arid Viper Launches Mobile Espionage Campaign with AridSpy Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/arid-viper-launches-mobile-espionage.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/arid-viper-launches-mobile-espionage.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Arid Viper has been attributed to a mobile espionage campaign that leverages trojanized Android apps to deliver a spyware strain dubbed AridSpy.
"The malware is distributed through dedicated websites impersonating various messaging apps, a job opportunity app, and a Palestinian Civil Registry app," ESET researcher Lukáš Štefanko said in a report published today. "Often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android et Pixel (13 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0492</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0492"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T12:12:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android et Pixel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-32896...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why SaaS Security is Suddenly Hot: Racing to Defend and Comply]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/why-saas-security-is-suddenly-hot.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/why-saas-security-is-suddenly-hot.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Recent supply chain cyber-attacks are prompting cyber security regulations in the financial sector to tighten compliance requirements, and other industries are expected to follow. Many companies still don’t have efficient methods to manage related time-sensitive SaaS security and compliance tasks. Free SaaS risk assessment tools are an easy and practical way to bring visibility and initial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan-linked Malware Campaign Evolves to Target Windows, Android, and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/pakistan-linked-malware-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/pakistan-linked-malware-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T10:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to Pakistan have been linked to a long-running malware campaign dubbed Operation Celestial Force since at least 2018.
The activity, still ongoing, entails the use of an Android malware called GravityRAT and a Windows-based malware loader codenamed HeavyLift, according to Cisco Talos, which are administered using another standalone tool referred to as GravityAdmin.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Employ PhantomLoader to Distribute SSLoad Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybercriminals-employ-phantomloader-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybercriminals-employ-phantomloader-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The nascent malware known as SSLoad is being delivered by means of a previously undocumented loader called PhantomLoader, according to findings from cybersecurity firm Intezer.
"The loader is added to a legitimate DLL, usually EDR or AV products, by binary patching the file and employing self-modifying techniques to evade detection," security researchers Nicole Fishbein and Ryan Robinson said in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (13 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0491</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0491"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T09:22:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (13 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0490</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0490"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T09:14:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Police Arrest Suspect Linked to LockBit and Conti Ransomware Groups]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ukraine-police-arrest-suspect-linked-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ukraine-police-arrest-suspect-linked-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cyber Police of Ukraine has announced the arrest of a local man who is suspected to have offered their services to LockBit and Conti ransomware groups.
The unnamed 28-year-old native of the Kharkiv region allegedly specialized in the development of crypters to encrypt and obfuscate malicious payloads in order to evade detection by security programs.
The product is believed to have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Warns of Pixel Firmware Security Flaw Exploited as Zero-Day]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-warns-of-pixel-firmware-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-warns-of-pixel-firmware-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T07:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has warned that a security flaw impacting Pixel Firmware has been exploited in the wild as a zero-day.
The high-severity vulnerability, tagged as CVE-2024-32896, has been described as an elevation of privilege issue in Pixel Firmware.
The company did not share any additional details related to the nature of attacks exploiting it, but noted "there are indications that CVE-2024-32896 may be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cross-Platform Malware 'Noodle RAT' Targets Windows and Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-cross-platform-malware-noodle-rat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-cross-platform-malware-noodle-rat.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-13T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented cross-platform malware codenamed Noodle RAT has been put to use by Chinese-speaking threat actors either for espionage or cybercrime for years.
While this backdoor was previously categorized as a variant of Gh0st RAT and Rekoobe, Trend Micro security researcher Hara Hiroaki said "this backdoor is not merely a variant of existing malware, but is a new type altogether."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptojacking Campaign Targets Misconfigured Kubernetes Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cryptojacking-campaign-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cryptojacking-campaign-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have warned of an ongoing cryptojacking campaign targeting misconfigured Kubernetes clusters to mine Dero cryptocurrency.
Cloud security firm Wiz, which shed light on the activity, said it's an updated variant of a financially motivated operation that was first documented by CrowdStrike in March 2023.
"In this incident, the threat actor abused anonymous access to an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0489</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0489"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:51:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0488</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0488"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:51:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0486</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0486"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0487</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0487"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:51:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0485</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0485"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T12:51:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0484</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0484"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:43:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lessons from the Ticketmaster-Snowflake Breach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lessons-from-ticketmaster-snowflake.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lessons-from-ticketmaster-snowflake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Last week, the notorious hacker gang, ShinyHunters, sent shockwaves across the globe by allegedly plundering 1.3 terabytes of data from 560 million Ticketmaster users. This colossal breach, with a price tag of $500,000, could expose the personal information of a massive swath of the live event company's clientele, igniting a firestorm of concern and outrage. 
A massive data breach 
Let’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta Ransomware May Have Exploited MS Windows Zero-Day Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/black-basta-ransomware-may-have.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/black-basta-ransomware-may-have.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors linked to the Black Basta ransomware may have exploited a recently disclosed privilege escalation flaw in the Microsoft Windows Error Reporting Service as zero-day, according to new findings from Symantec.
The security flaw in question is CVE-2024-26169 (CVSS score: 7.8), an elevation of privilege bug in the Windows Error Reporting Service that could be exploited to achieve SYSTEM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Failles sur les équipements de sécurité - Retour d'expérience du CERT-FR (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-005</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-005"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T10:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L'année 2023 et le début de l'année 2024 ont été marqués par de nombreux incidents concernant des équipements de sécurité présents notamment en bordure de réseau. Ces incidents ont pour origine l'exploitation d'une ou plusieurs vulnérabilités critiques dans des pare-feux, passerelles VPN ou...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0483</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0483"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:42:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mozilla Firefox (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0482</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0482"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:33:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mozilla Firefox. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0481</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0481"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:31:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Citrix (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0480</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0480"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:19:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Citrix. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans HPE Aruba Networking AirWave Management Platform (12 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0479</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0479"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T09:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans HPE Aruba Networking AirWave Management Platform. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Campaign Deploys WARMCOOKIE Backdoor Targeting Job Seekers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-phishing-campaign-deploys.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-phishing-campaign-deploys.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of an ongoing phishing campaign that leverages recruiting- and job-themed lures to deliver a Windows-based backdoor named WARMCOOKIE.
"WARMCOOKIE appears to be an initial backdoor tool used to scout out victim networks and deploy additional payloads," Elastic Security Labs researcher Daniel Stepanic said in a new analysis. "Each sample is compiled]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Backed Hackers Exploit Fortinet Flaw, Infecting 20,000 Systems Globally]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-backed-hackers-exploit-fortinet.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-backed-hackers-exploit-fortinet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T08:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[State-sponsored threat actors backed by China gained access to 20,000 Fortinet FortiGate systems worldwide by exploiting a known critical security flaw between 2022 and 2023, indicating that the operation had a broader impact than previously known.
"The state actor behind this campaign was already aware of this vulnerability in FortiGate systems at least two months before Fortinet disclosed the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues Patches for 51 Flaws, Including Critical MSMQ Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-issues-patches-for-51-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-issues-patches-for-51-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-12T04:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released security updates to address 51 flaws as part of its Patch Tuesday updates for June 2024.
Of the 51 vulnerabilities, one is rated Critical and 50 are rated Important. This is in addition to 17 vulnerabilities resolved in the Chromium-based Edge browser over the past month.
None of the security flaws have been actively exploited in the wild, with one of them listed as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cynet Makes MSPs Rich & Their Clients Secure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-cynet-makes-msps-rich-their-clients.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/how-cynet-makes-msps-rich-their-clients.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T16:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Managed service providers (MSPs) are on the front lines of soaring demand for cybersecurity services as cyberattacks increase in volume and sophistication. Cynet has emerged as the security vendor of choice for MSPs to capitalize on existing relationships with SMB clients and profitably expand their client base. By unifying a full suite of cybersecurity capabilities in a simple, cost-effective]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Actor SecShow Conducts Massive DNS Probing on Global Scale]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-actor-secshow-conducts-massive.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-actor-secshow-conducts-massive.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T14:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed more light on a Chinese actor codenamed SecShow that has been observed conducting Domain Name System (DNS) on a global scale since at least June 2023.
The adversary, according to Infoblox security researchers Dr. Renée Burton and Dave Mitchell, operates from the China Education and Research Network (CERNET), a project funded by the Chinese government.
"These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (11 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0478</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0478"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:33:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (11 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0477</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0477"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider Electric (11 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0476</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0476"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider Electric. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 10 Critical Pentest Findings 2024: What You Need to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/top-10-critical-pentest-findings-2024.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/top-10-critical-pentest-findings-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most effective ways for information technology (IT) professionals to uncover a company’s weaknesses before the bad guys do is penetration testing. By simulating real-world cyberattacks, penetration testing, sometimes called pentests, provides invaluable insights into an organization’s security posture, revealing weaknesses that could potentially lead to data breaches or other security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Integrates OpenAI's ChatGPT into Siri for iOS, iPadOS, and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/apple-integrates-openais-chatgpt-into.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/apple-integrates-openais-chatgpt-into.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has announced the launch of a "groundbreaking cloud intelligence system" called Private Cloud Compute (PCC) that's designed for processing artificial intelligence (AI) tasks in a privacy-preserving manner in the cloud.
The tech giant described PCC as the "most advanced security architecture ever deployed for cloud AI compute at scale."
PCC coincides with the arrival of new generative AI (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked ValleyRAT Malware Resurfaces with Advanced Data Theft Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-linked-valleyrat-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/china-linked-valleyrat-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered an updated version of malware called ValleyRAT that's being distributed as part of a new campaign.
"In the latest version, ValleyRAT introduced new commands, such as capturing screenshots, process filtering, forced shutdown, and clearing Windows event logs," Zscaler ThreatLabz researchers Muhammed Irfan V A and Manisha Ramcharan Prajapati said.
ValleyRAT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Security Center (11 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0475</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0475"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T08:06:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Security Center. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Veeam Recovery Orchestrator (11 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0474</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0474"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T07:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Veeam Recovery Orchestrator. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowflake Breach Exposes 165 Customers' Data in Ongoing Extortion Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-breach-exposes-165-customers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-breach-exposes-165-customers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T06:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 165 customers of Snowflake are said to have had their information potentially exposed as part of an ongoing campaign designed to facilitate data theft and extortion, indicating the operation has broader implications than previously thought.
Google-owned Mandiant, which is assisting the cloud data warehousing platform in its incident response efforts, is tracking the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Arm Warns of Actively Exploited Zero-Day Vulnerability in Mali GPU Drivers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/arm-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/arm-warns-of-actively-exploited-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-11T06:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Arm is warning of a security vulnerability impacting Mali GPU Kernel Driver that it said has been actively exploited in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-4610, the use-after-free issue impacts the following products -

Bifrost GPU Kernel Driver (all versions from r34p0 to r40p0)
Valhall GPU Kernel Driver (all versions from r34p0 to r40p0)

"A local non-privileged user can make improper GPU memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[More_eggs Malware Disguised as Resumes Targets Recruiters in Phishing Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/moreeggs-malware-disguised-as-resumes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/moreeggs-malware-disguised-as-resumes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have spotted a phishing attack distributing the More_eggs malware by masquerading it as a resume, a technique originally detected more than two years ago.
The attack, which was unsuccessful, targeted an unnamed company in the industrial services industry in May 2024, Canadian cybersecurity firm eSentire disclosed last week.
"Specifically, the targeted individual was a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity CPEs: Unraveling the What, Why & How]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybersecurity-cpes-unraveling-what-why.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cybersecurity-cpes-unraveling-what-why.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T11:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Staying Sharp: Cybersecurity CPEs Explained
Perhaps even more so than in other professional domains, cybersecurity professionals constantly face new threats. To ensure you stay on top of your game, many certification programs require earning Continuing Professional Education (CPE) credits. CPEs are essentially units of measurement used to quantify the time and effort professionals spend on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Azure Service Tags Vulnerability: Microsoft Warns of Potential Abuse by Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/azure-service-tags-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/azure-service-tags-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is warning about the potential abuse of Azure Service Tags by malicious actors to forge requests from a trusted service and get around firewall rules, thereby allowing them to gain unauthorized access to cloud resources.
"This case does highlight an inherent risk in using service tags as a single mechanism for vetting incoming network traffic," the Microsoft Security Response Center (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Takes Down Influence Campaigns Tied to China, Indonesia, and Russia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-takes-down-influence-campaigns.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-takes-down-influence-campaigns.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has revealed that it took down 1,320 YouTube channels and 1,177 Blogger blogs as part of a coordinated influence operation connected to the People’s Republic of China (PRC).
"The coordinated inauthentic network uploaded content in Chinese and English about China and U.S. foreign affairs," Google Threat Analysis Group (TAG) researcher Billy Leonard said in the company's quarterly bulletin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans VMware Tanzu (10 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0473</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0473"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T08:13:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Tanzu. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-025 (10 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-025</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-025"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T06:57:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sticky Werewolf Expands Cyber Attack Targets in Russia and Belarus]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sticky-werewolf-expands-cyber-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sticky-werewolf-expands-cyber-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-10T05:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a threat actor known as Sticky Werewolf that has been linked to cyber attacks targeting entities in Russia and Belarus.
The phishing attacks were aimed at a pharmaceutical company, a Russian research institute dealing with microbiology and vaccine development, and the aviation sector, expanding beyond their initial focus of government]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PHP Vulnerability Exposes Windows Servers to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-php-vulnerability-exposes-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-php-vulnerability-exposes-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a new critical security flaw impacting PHP that could be exploited to achieve remote code execution under certain circumstances.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-4577, has been described as a CGI argument injection vulnerability affecting all versions of PHP installed on the Windows operating system.
According to DEVCORE security researcher, the shortcoming makes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Revamps Controversial AI-Powered Recall Feature Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-revamps-controversial-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-revamps-controversial-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T06:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Friday said it will disable its much-criticized artificial intelligence (AI)-powered Recall feature by default and make it an opt-in.
Recall, currently in preview and coming exclusively to Copilot+ PCs on June 18, 2024, functions as an "explorable visual timeline" by capturing screenshots of what appears on users' screens every five seconds, which are subsequently analyzed and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Cyber Hygiene Guide: Learn How to Simplify Your Security Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ultimate-cyber-hygiene-guide-learn-how.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ultimate-cyber-hygiene-guide-learn-how.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was a year of unprecedented cyberattacks. Ransomware crippled businesses, DDoS attacks disrupted critical services, and data breaches exposed millions of sensitive records. The cost of these attacks? Astronomical. The damage to reputations? Irreparable.
But here's the shocking truth: many of these attacks could have been prevented with basic cyber hygiene.
Are you ready to transform your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LightSpy Spyware's macOS Variant Found with Advanced Surveillance Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lightspy-spywares-macos-variant-found.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lightspy-spywares-macos-variant-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed that the LightSpy spyware allegedly targeting Apple iOS users is in fact a previously undocumented macOS variant of the implant.
The findings come from both Huntress Labs and ThreatFabric, which separately analyzed the artifacts associated with the cross-platform malware framework that likely possesses capabilities to infect Android, iOS, Windows, macOS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Serv-U (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0467</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0467"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Serv-U. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0472</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0472"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0471</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0471"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0470</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0470"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Elastic (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0469</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0469"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Elastic. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Landscape is Evolving - So Should Your SCA]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cyber-landscape-is-evolving-so-should.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cyber-landscape-is-evolving-so-should.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional SCAs Are Broken: Did You Know You Are Missing Critical Pieces?
Application Security professionals face enormous challenges securing their software supply chains, racing against time to beat the attacker to the mark. 
Software Composition Analysis (SCA) tools have become a basic instrument in the application security arsenal in the last 7 years. Although essential, many platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Debate: Google's Guidelines, Meta's GDPR Dispute, Microsoft's Recall Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-ai-debate-googles-guidelines-metas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-ai-debate-googles-guidelines-metas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is urging third-party Android app developers to incorporate generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) features in a responsible manner.
The new guidance from the search and advertising giant is an effort to combat problematic content, including sexual content and hate speech, created through such tools.
To that end, apps that generate content using AI must ensure they don't create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans PHP (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0468</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0468"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PHP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Distributes 7,000 LockBit Ransomware Decryption Keys to Help Victims]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/fbi-distributes-7000-lockbit-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/fbi-distributes-7000-lockbit-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has disclosed that it's in possession of more than 7,000 decryption keys associated with the LockBit ransomware operation to help victims get their data back at no cost.
"We are reaching out to known LockBit victims and encouraging anyone who suspects they were a victim to visit our Internet Crime Complaint Center at ic3.gov," FBI Cyber Division]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPECTR Malware Targets Ukraine Defense Forces in SickSync Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/spectr-malware-targets-ukraine-defense.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/spectr-malware-targets-ukraine-defense.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of cyber attacks targeting defense forces in the country with a malware called SPECTR as part of an espionage campaign dubbed SickSync.
The agency attributed the attacks to a threat actor it tracks under the moniker UAC-0020, which is also called Vermin and is assessed to be associated with security agencies of the Luhansk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commando Cat Cryptojacking Attacks Target Misconfigured Docker Instances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/commando-cat-cryptojacking-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/commando-cat-cryptojacking-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Commando Cat has been linked to an ongoing cryptojacking attack campaign that leverages poorly secured Docker instances to deploy cryptocurrency miners for financial gain.
"The attackers used the cmd.cat/chattr docker image container that retrieves the payload from their own command-and-control (C&C) infrastructure," Trend Micro researchers Sunil Bharti and Shubham]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muhstik Botnet Exploiting Apache RocketMQ Flaw to Expand DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/muhstik-botnet-exploiting-apache.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/muhstik-botnet-exploiting-apache.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T13:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) botnet known as Muhstik has been observed leveraging a now-patched security flaw impacting Apache RocketMQ to co-opt susceptible servers and expand its scale.
"Muhstik is a well-known threat targeting IoT devices and Linux-based servers, notorious for its ability to infect devices and utilize them for cryptocurrency mining and launching Distributed Denial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third-Party Cyber Attacks: The Threat No One Sees Coming – Here's How to Stop Them]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/third-party-cyber-attacks-threat-no-one.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/third-party-cyber-attacks-threat-no-one.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
In an increasingly interconnected world, supply chain attacks have emerged as a formidable threat, compromising]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevent Account Takeover with Better Password Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prevent-account-takeover-with-better.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prevent-account-takeover-with-better.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom works for a reputable financial institution. He has a long, complex password that would be near-impossible to guess. He’s memorized it by heart, so he started using it for his social media accounts and on his personal devices too. Unbeknownst to Tom, one of these sites has had its password database compromised by hackers and put it up for sale on the dark web. Now threat actors are working]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Legitimate Packer Software to Spread Malware Undetected]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-packer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-packer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are increasingly abusing legitimate and commercially available packer software such as BoxedApp to evade detection and distribute malware such as remote access trojans and information stealers.
"The majority of the attributed malicious samples targeted financial institutions and government industries," Check Point security researcher Jiri Vinopal said in an analysis.
The volume of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Elastic (06 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0466</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0466"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Elastic. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps Timeline Data to be Stored Locally on Your Device for Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-maps-timeline-data-to-be-stored.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-maps-timeline-data-to-be-stored.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced plans to store Maps Timeline data locally on users' devices instead of their Google account effective December 1, 2024.
The changes were originally announced by the tech giant in December 2023, alongside changes to the auto-delete control when enabling Location History by setting it to three months by default, down from the previous limit of 18 months.
Google Maps Timeline,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB PyMongo (06 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0465</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0465"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB PyMongo. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target Python Developers with Fake "Crytic-Compilers" Package on PyPI]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-target-python-developers-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-target-python-developers-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a malicious Python package uploaded to the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that's designed to deliver an information stealer called Lumma (aka LummaC2).
The package in question is crytic-compilers, a typosquatted version of a legitimate library named crytic-compile. The rogue package was downloaded 441 times before it was taken down by PyPI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese State-Backed Cyber Espionage Targets Southeast Asian Government]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-state-backed-cyber-espionage.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-state-backed-cyber-espionage.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unnamed high-profile government organization in Southeast Asia emerged as the target of a "complex, long-running" Chinese state-sponsored cyber espionage operation codenamed Crimson Palace.
"The overall goal behind the campaign was to maintain access to the target network for cyberespionage in support of Chinese state interests," Sophos researchers Paul Jaramillo, Morgan Demboski, Sean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking 2024's SaaS Threat Predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/unpacking-2024s-saas-threat-predictions.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/unpacking-2024s-saas-threat-predictions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early in 2024, Wing Security released its State of SaaS Security report, offering surprising insights into emerging threats and best practices in the SaaS domain. Now, halfway through the year, several SaaS threat predictions from the report have already proven accurate. Fortunately, SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM) solutions have prioritized mitigation capabilities to address many of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebranded Knight Ransomware Targeting Healthcare and Businesses Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rebranded-knight-ransomware-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rebranded-knight-ransomware-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of a nascent ransomware strain called RansomHub has revealed it to be an updated and rebranded version of Knight ransomware, itself an evolution of another ransomware known as Cyclops.
Knight (aka Cyclops 2.0) ransomware first arrived in May 2023, employing double extortion tactics to steal and encrypt victims' data for financial gain. It's operational across multiple platforms,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel Releases Patches for Firmware Vulnerabilities in EoL NAS Models]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zyxel-releases-patches-for-firmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zyxel-releases-patches-for-firmware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel has released security updates to address critical flaws impacting two of its network-attached storage (NAS) devices that have currently reached end-of-life (EoL) status.
Successful exploitation of three of the five vulnerabilities could permit an unauthenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands and arbitrary code on affected installations.
Impacted models include NAS326]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans SolarWinds Platform (05 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0464</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0464"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SolarWinds Platform. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrity TikTok Accounts Compromised Using Zero-Click Attack via DMs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/celebrity-tiktok-accounts-compromised.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/celebrity-tiktok-accounts-compromised.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular video-sharing platform TikTok has acknowledged a security issue that has been exploited by threat actors to take control of high-profile accounts on the platform.
The development was first reported by Semafor and Forbes, which detailed a zero-click account takeover campaign that allows malware propagated via direct messages to compromise brand and celebrity accounts without having to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ruby on Rails (05 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0463</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0463"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ruby on Rails. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Power Companies, IT Firms, and Govt Agencies Hit by Decoy Dog Trojan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-power-companies-it-firms-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-power-companies-it-firms-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian organizations are at the receiving end of cyber attacks that have been found to deliver a Windows version of a malware called Decoy Dog.
Cybersecurity company Positive Technologies is tracking the activity cluster under the name Operation Lahat, attributing it to an advanced persistent threat (APT) group called HellHounds.
"The Hellhounds group compromises organizations they select and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik Report Server Flaw Could Let Attackers Create Rogue Admin Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/telerik-report-server-flaw-could-let.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/telerik-report-server-flaw-could-let.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has rolled out updates to address a critical security flaw impacting the Telerik Report Server that could be potentially exploited by a remote attacker to bypass authentication and create rogue administrator users.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2024-4358, carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"In Progress Telerik Report Server, version 2024 Q1 (10.0.24.305) or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Platform (04 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0462</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0462"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Platform. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Generation of RBI (Remote Browser Isolation)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-next-generation-of-rbi-remote.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-next-generation-of-rbi-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of browser security has undergone significant changes over the past decade. While Browser Isolation was once considered the gold standard for protecting against browser exploits and malware downloads, it has become increasingly inadequate and insecure in today's SaaS-centric world.
The limitations of Browser Isolation, such as degraded browser performance and inability to tackle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Use MS Excel Macro to Launch Multi-Stage Malware Attack in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-use-ms-excel-macro-to-launch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-use-ms-excel-macro-to-launch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new sophisticated cyber attack has been observed targeting endpoints geolocated to Ukraine with an aim to deploy Cobalt Strike and seize control of the compromised hosts.
The attack chain, per Fortinet FortiGuard Labs, involves a Microsoft Excel file that carries an embedded VBA macro to initiate the infection,
"The attacker uses a multi-stage malware strategy to deliver the notorious 'Cobalt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowflake Warns: Targeted Credential Theft Campaign Hits Cloud Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-warns-targeted-credential.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-warns-targeted-credential.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing and analytics company Snowflake said a "limited number" of its customers have been singled out as part of a targeted campaign.
"We have not identified evidence suggesting this activity was caused by a vulnerability, misconfiguration, or breach of Snowflake’s platform," the company said in a joint statement along with CrowdStrike and Google-owned Mandiant.
"We have not identified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (04 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0461</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0461"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkGate Malware Replaces AutoIt with AutoHotkey in Latest Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/darkgate-malware-replaces-autoit-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/darkgate-malware-replaces-autoit-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attacks involving the DarkGate malware-as-a-service (MaaS) operation have shifted away from AutoIt scripts to an AutoHotkey mechanism to deliver the last stages, underscoring continued efforts on the part of the threat actors to continuously stay ahead of the detection curve.
The updates have been observed in version 6 of DarkGate released in March 2024 by its developer RastaFarEye, who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle WebLogic Server OS Command Injection Flaw Under Active Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oracle-weblogic-server-os-command.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oracle-weblogic-server-os-command.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a security flaw impacting the Oracle WebLogic Server to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2017-3506 (CVSS score: 7.4), the issue concerns an operating system (OS) command injection vulnerability that could be exploited to obtain unauthorized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover RAT-Dropping npm Package Targeting Gulp Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-rat-dropping-npm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-rat-dropping-npm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new suspicious package uploaded to the npm package registry that's designed to drop a remote access trojan (RAT) on compromised systems.
The package in question is glup-debugger-log, which targets users of the gulp toolkit by masquerading as a "logger for gulp and gulp plugins." It has been downloaded 175 times to date.
Software supply chain security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities Ramp Up Efforts to Capture the Mastermind Behind Emotet]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/authorities-ramp-up-efforts-to-capture.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/authorities-ramp-up-efforts-to-capture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement authorities behind Operation Endgame are seeking information related to an individual who goes by the name Odd and is allegedly the mastermind behind the Emotet malware. 
Odd is also said to go by the nicknames Aron, C700, Cbd748, Ivanov Odd, Mors, Morse, Veron over the past few years, according to a video released by the agencies.
"Who is he working with? What is his]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-024 (03 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-024</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T12:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SASE Threat Report: 8 Key Findings for Enterprise Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sase-threat-report-8-key-findings-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sase-threat-report-8-key-findings-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are evolving, yet Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) remains confined to each isolated point solution. Organizations require a holistic analysis across external data, inbound and outbound threats and network activity. This will enable evaluating the true state of cybersecurity in the enterprise.
Cato’s Cyber Threat Research Lab (Cato CTRL, see more details below) has recently released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researcher Uncovers Flaws in Cox Modems, Potentially Impacting Millions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researcher-uncovers-flaws-in-cox-modems.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researcher-uncovers-flaws-in-cox-modems.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now-patched authorization bypass issues impacting Cox modems that could have been abused as a starting point to gain unauthorized access to the devices and run malicious commands.
"This series of vulnerabilities demonstrated a way in which a fully external attacker with no prerequisites could've executed commands and modified the settings of millions of modems, accessed any business customer's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les caméras Synology (03 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0460</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0460"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les caméras Synology. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andariel Hackers Target South Korean Institutes with New Dora RAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/andariel-hackers-target-south-korean.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/andariel-hackers-target-south-korean.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Andariel has been observed using a new Golang-based backdoor called Dora RAT in its attacks targeting educational institutes, manufacturing firms, and construction businesses in South Korea.
"Keylogger, Infostealer, and proxy tools on top of the backdoor were utilized for the attacks," the AhnLab Security Intelligence Center (ASEC) said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Fake Browser Updates Deliver BitRAT and Lumma Stealer Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/beware-fake-browser-updates-deliver.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/beware-fake-browser-updates-deliver.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T03:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fake web browser updates are being used to deliver remote access trojans (RATs) and information stealer malware such as BitRAT and Lumma Stealer (aka LummaC2).
"Fake browser updates have been responsible for numerous malware infections, including those of the well-known SocGholish malware," cybersecurity firm eSentire said in a new report. "In April 2024, we observed FakeBat being distributed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>