<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-09-08T05:43:39.215Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Threat Actors Deploy COVERTCATCH Malware via LinkedIn Job Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-threat-actors-deploy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-threat-actors-deploy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T07:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors affiliated with North Korea have been observed leveraging LinkedIn as a way to target developers as part of a fake job recruiting operation.

These attacks employ coding tests as a common initial infection vector, Google-owned Mandiant said in a new report about threats faced by the Web3 sector.

"After an initial chat conversation, the attacker sent a ZIP file that contained]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Cracks Down on Dark Web Marketplace Managed by Russian and Kazakh Nationals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/fbi-cracks-down-on-dark-web-marketplace.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/fbi-cracks-down-on-dark-web-marketplace.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two men have been indicted in the U.S. for their alleged involvement in managing a dark web marketplace called WWH Club that specializes in the sale of sensitive personal and financial information.
Alex Khodyrev, a 35-year-old Kazakhstan national, and Pavel Kublitskii, a 37-year-old Russian national, have been charged with conspiracy to commit access device fraud and conspiracy to commit wire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall Urges Users to Patch Critical Firewall Flaw Amid Possible Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/sonicwall-urges-users-to-patch-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/sonicwall-urges-users-to-patch-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall has revealed that a recently patched critical security flaw impacting SonicOS may have come under active exploitation, making it essential that users apply the patches as soon as possible.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-40766, carries a CVSS score of 9.3 out of a maximum of 10.
"An improper access control vulnerability has been identified in the SonicWall SonicOS management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GeoServer Vulnerability Targeted by Hackers to Deliver Backdoors and Botnet Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/geoserver-vulnerability-targeted-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/geoserver-vulnerability-targeted-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently disclosed security flaw in OSGeo GeoServer GeoTools has been exploited as part of multiple campaigns to deliver cryptocurrency miners, botnet malware such as Condi and JenX, and a known backdoor called SideWalk.
The security vulnerability is a critical remote code execution bug (CVE-2024-36401, CVSS score: 9.8) that could allow malicious actors to take over susceptible instances.
In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions Vulnerable to Typosquatting, Exposing Developers to Hidden Malicious Code]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/github-actions-vulnerable-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/github-actions-vulnerable-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have long leveraged typosquatting as a means to trick unsuspecting users into visiting malicious websites or downloading booby-trapped software and packages.

These attacks typically involve registering domains or packages with names slightly altered from their legitimate counterparts (e.g., goog1e.com vs. google.com).

Adversaries targeting open-source repositories across]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0750/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0750/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0749/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0749/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0748/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0748/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0747/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0747/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of the Virtual CISO Report: MSP/MSSP Security Strategies for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 State of the vCISO Report continues Cynomi’s tradition of examining the growing popularity of virtual Chief Information Security Officer (vCISO) services. According to the independent survey, the demand for these services is increasing, with both providers and clients reaping the rewards. The upward trend is set to continue, with even faster growth expected in the future. However,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Flaw Found in LiteSpeed Cache Plugin for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-security-flaw-found-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-security-flaw-found-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered yet another critical security flaw in the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress that could allow unauthenticated users to take control of arbitrary accounts.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-44000 (CVSS score: 7.5), impacts versions before and including 6.4.1. It has been addressed in version 6.5.0.1. 
"The plugin suffers from an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Elastic Kibana (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0746/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0746/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Elastic Kibana. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Asterisk (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0745/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0745/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Asterisk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache OFBiz Update Fixes High-Severity Flaw Leading to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apache-ofbiz-update-fixes-high-severity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apache-ofbiz-update-fixes-high-severity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new security flaw has been addressed in the Apache OFBiz open-source enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that, if successfully exploited, could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution on Linux and Windows.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-45195 (CVSS score: 7.5), affects all versions of the software before 18.12.16.


"An attacker with no valid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov Criticizes Outdated Laws After Arrest Over Telegram Criminal Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/paul-durov-criticizes-outdated-laws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/paul-durov-criticizes-outdated-laws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T04:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram CEO Pavel Durov has broken his silence nearly two weeks after his arrest in France, stating the charges are misguided.
"If a country is unhappy with an internet service, the established practice is to start a legal action against the service itself," Durov said in a 600-word statement on his Telegram account.
"Using laws from the pre-smartphone era to charge a CEO with crimes committed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-Speaking Hacker Group Targets Human Rights Studies in Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-speaking-hacker-group-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-speaking-hacker-group-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unnamed government entities in the Middle East and Malaysia are the target of a persistent cyber campaign orchestrated by a threat actor known as Tropic Trooper since June 2023.
"Sighting this group's [Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures] in critical governmental entities in the Middle East, particularly those related to human rights studies, marks a new strategic move for them," Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Releases Security Updates to Fix 18 Flaws, Including 5 Critical Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/veeam-releases-security-updates-to-fix.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/veeam-releases-security-updates-to-fix.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam has shipped security updates to address a total of 18 security flaws impacting its software products, including five critical vulnerabilities that could result in remote code execution.
The list of shortcomings is below -

CVE-2024-40711 (CVSS score: 9.8) - A vulnerability in Veeam Backup & Replication that allows unauthenticated remote code execution.


CVE-2024-42024 (CVSS score: 9.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans ClamAV (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0744/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0744/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T12:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans ClamAV. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Seizes 32 Pro-Russian Propaganda Domains in Major Disinformation Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-seizes-32-pro-russian-propaganda.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-seizes-32-pro-russian-propaganda.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Wednesday announced the seizure of 32 internet domains used by a pro-Russian propaganda operation called Doppelganger as part of a sweeping set of actions.
Accusing the Russian government-directed foreign malign influence campaign of violating U.S. money laundering and criminal trademark laws, the agency called out companies Social Design Agency (SDA),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Centreon Web (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0743/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0743/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Centreon web. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) and CTEM – Better Together]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/nist-cybersecurity-framework-csf-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/nist-cybersecurity-framework-csf-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a decade since the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) introduced its Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) 1.0. Created following a 2013 Executive Order, NIST was tasked with designing a voluntary cybersecurity framework that would help organizations manage cyber risk, providing guidance based on established standards and best practices. While this version was originally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware Attackers Using MacroPack to Deliver Havoc, Brute Ratel, and PhantomCore]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malware-attackers-using-macropack-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malware-attackers-using-macropack-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are likely employing a tool designated for red teaming exercises to serve malware, according to new findings from Cisco Talos.

The program in question is a payload generation framework called MacroPack, which is used to generate Office documents, Visual Basic scripts, Windows shortcuts, and other formats for penetration testing and social engineering assessments. It was developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0742/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0742/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0741/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0741/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Secure Analytics. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Veeam (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0740/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0740/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T06:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Veeam. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0739/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0739/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T06:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cross-Platform Malware KTLVdoor Discovered in Attack on Chinese Trading Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-cross-platform-malware-ktlvdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-cross-platform-malware-ktlvdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T05:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese-speaking threat actor known as Earth Lusca has been observed using a new backdoor dubbed KTLVdoor as part of a cyber attack targeting an unnamed trading company based in China.

The previously unreported malware is written in Golang, and thus is a cross-platform weapon capable of targeting both Microsoft Windows and Linux systems.

"KTLVdoor is a highly obfuscated malware that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Fixes Two Critical Flaws in Smart Licensing Utility to Prevent Remote Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisco-fixes-two-critical-flaws-in-smart.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisco-fixes-two-critical-flaws-in-smart.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T04:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released security updates for two critical security flaws impacting its Smart Licensing Utility that could allow unauthenticated, remote attackers to elevate their privileges or access sensitive information.
A brief description of the two vulnerabilities is below -

CVE-2024-20439 (CVSS score: 9.8) - The presence of an undocumented static user credential for an administrative account]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Targets Job Seekers with Fake FreeConference App]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-targets-job.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-targets-job.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors have leveraged a fake Windows video conferencing application impersonating FreeConference.com to backdoor developer systems as part of an ongoing financially-driven campaign dubbed Contagious Interview.
The new attack wave, spotted by Singaporean company Group-IB in mid-August 2024, is yet another indication that the activity is also leveraging native installers for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Confirms CVE-2024-32896 Exploited in the Wild, Releases Android Security Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-confirms-cve-2024-32896.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-confirms-cve-2024-32896.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released its monthly security updates for the Android operating system to address a known security flaw that it said has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-32896 (CVSS score: 7.8), relates to a case of privilege escalation in the Android Framework component.
According to the description of the bug in the NIST National]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Hijack 22,000 Removed PyPI Packages, Spreading Malicious Code to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-hijack-22000-removed-pypi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-hijack-22000-removed-pypi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new supply chain attack technique targeting the Python Package Index (PyPI) registry has been exploited in the wild in an attempt to infiltrate downstream organizations.
It has been codenamed Revival Hijack by software supply chain security firm JFrog, which said the attack method could be used to hijack 22,000 existing PyPI packages and result in "hundreds of thousands" of malicious package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0738/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0738/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T12:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moxa OnCell 3120-LTE-1 Series (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0737/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0737/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T12:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moxa OnCell 3120-LTE-1 Series. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel Patches Critical OS Command Injection Flaw in Access Points and Routers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/zyxel-patches-critical-os-command.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/zyxel-patches-critical-os-command.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel has released software updates to address a critical security flaw impacting certain access point (AP) and security router versions that could result in the execution of unauthorized commands.

Tracked as CVE-2024-7261 (CVSS score: 9.8), the vulnerability has been described as a case of operating system (OS) command injection.

"The improper neutralization of special elements in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Effective Way to Prevent Account Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-new-effective-way-to-prevent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-new-effective-way-to-prevent.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account takeover attacks have emerged as one of the most persistent and damaging threats to cloud-based SaaS environments. Yet despite significant investments in traditional security measures, many organizations continue to struggle with preventing these attacks. A new report, "Why Account Takeover Attacks Still Succeed, and Why the Browser is Your Secret Weapon in Stopping Them" argues that the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clearview AI Faces €30.5M Fine for Building Illegal Facial Recognition Database]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/clearview-ai-faces-305m-fine-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/clearview-ai-faces-305m-fine-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dutch Data Protection Authority (Dutch DPA) has imposed a fine of €30.5 million ($33.7 million) against facial recognition firm Clearview AI for violating the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Union (E.U.) by building an "illegal database with billions of photos of faces," including those of Dutch citizens.
"Facial recognition is a highly intrusive technology that you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0736/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0736/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T07:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0735/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0735/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T07:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans CPython (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0734/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0734/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T06:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans CPython. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Google (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0733/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0733/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T06:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Google. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Use Fake GlobalProtect VPN Software in New WikiLoader Malware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-use-fake-globalprotect-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-use-fake-globalprotect-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T05:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware campaign is spoofing Palo Alto Networks' GlobalProtect VPN software to deliver a variant of the WikiLoader (aka WailingCrab) loader by means of a search engine optimization (SEO) campaign.

The malvertising activity, observed in June 2024, is a departure from previously observed tactics wherein the malware has been propagated via traditional phishing emails, Unit 42 researchers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivists Exploits WinRAR Vulnerability in Attacks Against Russia and Belarus]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivists-exploits-winrar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivists-exploits-winrar.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacktivist group known as Head Mare has been linked to cyber attacks that exclusively target organizations located in Russia and Belarus.
"Head Mare uses more up-to-date methods for obtaining initial access," Kaspersky said in a Monday analysis of the group's tactics and tools.
"For instance, the attackers took advantage of the relatively recent CVE-2023-38831 vulnerability in WinRAR, which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Rust-Based Ransomware Cicada3301 Targets Windows and Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rust-based-ransomware-cicada3301.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rust-based-ransomware-cicada3301.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unpacked the inner workings of a new ransomware variant called Cicada3301 that shares similarities with the now-defunct BlackCat (aka ALPHV) operation.
"It appears that Cicada3301 ransomware primarily targets small to medium-sized businesses (SMBs), likely through opportunistic attacks that exploit vulnerabilities as the initial access vector," cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits VMware (03 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0732/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0732/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T11:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Fusion. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocinante Trojan Poses as Banking Apps to Steal Sensitive Data from Brazilian Android Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/rocinante-trojan-poses-as-banking-apps.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/rocinante-trojan-poses-as-banking-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile users in Brazil are the target of a new malware campaign that delivers a new Android banking trojan named Rocinante.

"This malware family is capable of performing keylogging using the Accessibility Service, and is also able to steal PII from its victims using phishing screens posing as different banks," Dutch security company ThreatFabric said.

"Finally, it can use all this exfiltrated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets Exposed: Why Your CISO Should Worry About Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/secrets-exposed-why-your-ciso-should.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/secrets-exposed-why-your-ciso-should.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the digital realm, secrets (API keys, private keys, username and password combos, etc.) are the keys to the kingdom. But what if those keys were accidentally left out in the open in the very tools we use to collaborate every day?
A Single Secret Can Wreak Havoc
Imagine this: It's a typical Tuesday in June 2024. Your dev team is knee-deep in sprints, Jira tickets are flying, and Slack is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (03 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0731/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0731/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T06:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Flaws in Microsoft macOS Apps Could Allow Hackers to Gain Unrestricted Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-flaws-in-microsoft-macos-apps-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-flaws-in-microsoft-macos-apps-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight vulnerabilities have been uncovered in Microsoft applications for macOS that an adversary could exploit to gain elevated privileges or access sensitive data by circumventing the operating system's permissions-based model, which revolves around the Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) framework.
"If successful, the adversary could gain any privileges already granted to the affected]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Engineer Charged in Missouri for Failed $750,000 Bitcoin Extortion Attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ex-engineer-charged-in-missouri-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ex-engineer-charged-in-missouri-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T01:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 57-year-old man from the U.S. state of Missouri has been arrested in connection with a failed data extortion campaign that targeted his former employer.
Daniel Rhyne of Kansas City, Missouri, has been charged with one count of extortion in relation to a threat to cause damage to a protected computer, one count of intentional damage to a protected computer, and one count of wire fraud.
He was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RansomHub Ransomware Group Targets 210 Victims Across Critical Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ransomhub-ransomware-group-targets-210.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ransomhub-ransomware-group-targets-210.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors linked to the RansomHub ransomware group encrypted and exfiltrated data from at least 210 victims since its inception in February 2024, the U.S. government said.
The victims span various sectors, including water and wastewater, information technology, government services and facilities, healthcare and public health, emergency services, food and agriculture, financial services,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-039 (02 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-039/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-039/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T12:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans MISP (02 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0730/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0730/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T11:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MISP. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Learn to Boost Cybersecurity with AI-Powered Vulnerability Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-learn-to-boost-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-learn-to-boost-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of cybersecurity is in a constant state of flux. New vulnerabilities emerge daily, and attackers are becoming more sophisticated.
In this high-stakes game, security leaders need every advantage they can get. That's where Artificial Intelligence (AI) comes in. AI isn't just a buzzword; it's a game-changer for vulnerability management.
AI is poised to revolutionize vulnerability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Generation Attacks, Same Targets - How to Protect Your Users' Identities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/next-generation-attacks-same-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/next-generation-attacks-same-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI and CISA Issue Joint Advisory on New Threats and How to Stop Ransomware
Note: on August 29, the FBI and CISA issued a joint advisory as part of their ongoing #StopRansomware effort to help organizations protect against ransomware. The latest advisory, AA24-242A, describes a new cybercriminal group and its attack methods. It also details three important actions to take today to mitigate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Mimicking 'noblox.js' Compromise Roblox Developers’ Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malicious-npm-packages-mimicking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malicious-npm-packages-mimicking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T03:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox developers are the target of a persistent campaign that seeks to compromise systems through bogus npm packages, once again underscoring how threat actors continue to exploit the trust in the open-source ecosystem to deliver malware.
"By mimicking the popular 'noblox.js' library, attackers have published dozens of packages designed to steal sensitive data and compromise systems," Checkmarx]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Deploy FudModule Rootkit via Chrome Zero-Day Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-fudmodule.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-fudmodule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched security flaw in Google Chrome and other Chromium web browsers was exploited as a zero-day by North Korean actors in a campaign designed to deliver the FudModule rootkit.
The development is indicative of the persistent efforts made by the nation-state adversary, which had made a habit of incorporating rafts of Windows zero-day exploits into its arsenal in recent months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers Exploit Google Sheets for Malware Control in Global Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cyberattackers-exploit-google-sheets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cyberattackers-exploit-google-sheets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a novel malware campaign that leverages Google Sheets as a command-and-control (C2) mechanism.
The activity, detected by Proofpoint starting August 5, 2024, impersonates tax authorities from governments in Europe, Asia, and the U.S., with the goal of targeting over 70 organizations worldwide by means of a bespoke tool called Voldemort that's equipped to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0729/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0729/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0728/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0728/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0727/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0727/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0726/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0726/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Set Up New Network to Target U.S. Political Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-hackers-set-up-new-network-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-hackers-set-up-new-network-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unearthed new network infrastructure set up by Iranian threat actors to support activities linked to the recent targeting of U.S. political campaigns.
Recorded Future's Insikt Group has linked the infrastructure to a threat it tracks as GreenCharlie, an Iran-nexus cyber threat group that overlaps with APT42, Charming Kitten, Damselfly, Mint Sandstorm (formerly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Masquerades as Palo Alto VPN Targeting Middle East Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-masquerades-as-palo-alto.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-masquerades-as-palo-alto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a new campaign that potentially targets users in the Middle East through malware that disguises itself as Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect virtual private network (VPN) tool.

"The malware can execute remote PowerShell commands, download and exfiltrate files, encrypt communications, and bypass sandbox solutions, representing a significant threat to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down AD CS Vulnerabilities: Insights for InfoSec Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/breaking-down-ad-cs-vulnerabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/breaking-down-ad-cs-vulnerabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T09:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most dangerous vulnerability you’ve never heard of.
In the world of cybersecurity, vulnerabilities are discovered so often, and at such a high rate, that it can be very difficult to keep up with. Some vulnerabilities will start ringing alarm bells within your security tooling, while others are far more nuanced, but still pose an equally dangerous threat. Today, we want to discuss one of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Developers with Malicious npm Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-target-developers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-target-developers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed publishing a set of malicious packages to the npm registry, indicating "coordinated and relentless" efforts to target developers with malware and steal cryptocurrency assets.
The latest wave, which was observed between August 12 and 27, 2024, involved packages named temp-etherscan-api, ethersscan-api, telegram-con, helmet-validate, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute Unveils Critical Infrastructure Strategy Guide for 2024: A Call to Action for Securing ICS/OT Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sans-institute-unveils-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sans-institute-unveils-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive guide authored by Dean Parsons emphasizes the growing need for specialized ICS security measures in the face of rising cyber threats.
With a staggering 50% increase in ransomware attacks targeting industrial control systems (ICS) in 2023, the SANS Institute is taking decisive action by announcing the release of its essential new strategy guide, "ICS Is the Business: Why Securing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cyberattack Targets Chinese-Speaking Businesses with Cobalt Strike Payloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyberattack-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyberattack-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking users are the target of a "highly organized and sophisticated attack" campaign that is likely leveraging phishing emails to infect Windows systems with Cobalt Strike payloads.
"The attackers managed to move laterally, establish persistence and remain undetected within the systems for more than two weeks," Securonix researchers Den Iuzvyk and Tim Peck said in a new report.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Confluence Vulnerability Exploited in Crypto Mining Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/atlassian-confluence-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/atlassian-confluence-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively exploiting a now-patched, critical security flaw impacting the Atlassian Confluence Data Center and Confluence Server to conduct illicit cryptocurrency mining on susceptible instances.
"The attacks involve threat actors that employ methods such as the deployment of shell scripts and XMRig miners, targeting of SSH endpoints, killing competing crypto mining processes,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Human Rights Group Targeted in Multi-Year Cyberattack by APT32]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/vietnamese-human-rights-group-targeted.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/vietnamese-human-rights-group-targeted.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A non-profit supporting Vietnamese human rights has been the target of a multi-year campaign designed to deliver a variety of malware on compromised hosts.
Cybersecurity company Huntress attributed the activity to a threat cluster known as APT32, a Vietnamese-aligned hacking crew that's also known as APT-C-00, Canvas Cyclone (formerly Bismuth), Cobalt Kitty, and OceanLotus. The intrusion is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Exploit Safari and Chrome Flaws in High-Profile Cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-exploit-safari-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-exploit-safari-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have flagged multiple in-the-wild exploit campaigns that leveraged now-patched flaws in Apple Safari and Google Chrome browsers to infect mobile users with information-stealing malware.
"These campaigns delivered n-day exploits for which patches were available, but would still be effective against unpatched devices," Google Threat Analysis Group (TAG) researcher Clement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Agencies Warn of Iranian Hacking Group's Ongoing Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-agencies-warn-of-iranian-hacking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-agencies-warn-of-iranian-hacking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. cybersecurity and intelligence agencies have called out an Iranian hacking group for breaching multiple organizations across the country and coordinating with affiliates to deliver ransomware.
The activity has been linked to a threat actor dubbed Pioneer Kitten, which is also known as Fox Kitten, Lemon Sandstorm (formerly Rubidium), Parisite, and UNC757, which it described as connected to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AitM Phishing Attacks Bypass MFA and EDR—and How to Fight Back]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-stop-aitm-phishing-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-stop-aitm-phishing-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are increasingly using new phishing toolkits (open-source, commercial, and criminal) to execute adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) attacks.
AitM enables attackers to not just harvest credentials but steal live sessions, allowing them to bypass traditional phishing prevention controls such as MFA, EDR, and email content filtering.
In this article, we’re going to look at what AitM phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched AVTECH IP Camera Flaw Exploited by Hackers for Botnet Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpatched-avtech-ip-camera-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpatched-avtech-ip-camera-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A years-old high-severity flaw impacting AVTECH IP cameras has been weaponized by malicious actors as a zero-day to rope them into a botnet.
CVE-2024-7029 (CVSS score: 8.7), the vulnerability in question, is a "command injection vulnerability found in the brightness function of AVTECH closed-circuit television (CCTV) cameras that allows for remote code execution (RCE)," Akamai researchers Kyle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Wireshark (29 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0725/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0725/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:34:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Wireshark. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (29 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0724/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0724/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:32:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco Nexus (29 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0723/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0723/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T08:28:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco Nexus. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[French Authorities Charge Telegram CEO with Facilitating Criminal Activities on Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/french-authorities-charge-telegram-ceo.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/french-authorities-charge-telegram-ceo.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T04:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[French prosecutors on Wednesday formally charged CEO Pavel Durov with facilitating a litany of criminal activity on the popular messaging platform and placed him under formal investigation following his arrest Saturday.
Russian-born Durov, who is also a French citizen, has been charged with being complicit in the spread of child sexual abuse material (CSAM) as well as enabling organized crime,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortra Issues Patch for High-Risk FileCatalyst Workflow Security Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fortra-issues-patch-for-high-risk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fortra-issues-patch-for-high-risk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T16:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortra has addressed a critical security flaw impacting FileCatalyst Workflow that could be abused by a remote attacker to gain administrative access.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-6633, carries a CVSS score of 9.8, and stems from the use of a static password to connect to a HSQL database.
"The default credentials for the setup HSQL database (HSQLDB) for FileCatalyst Workflow are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT-C-60 Group Exploit WPS Office Flaw to Deploy SpyGlace Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt-c-60-group-exploit-wps-office-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/apt-c-60-group-exploit-wps-office-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A South Korea-aligned cyber espionage has been linked to the zero-day exploitation of a now-patched critical remote code execution flaw in Kingsoft WPS Office to deploy a bespoke backdoor dubbed SpyGlace.
The activity has been attributed to a threat actor dubbed APT-C-60, according to cybersecurity firms ESET and DBAPPSecurity. The attacks have been found to infect Chinese and East Asian users]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB Server (28 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0722/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0722/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T11:30:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BlackByte Ransomware Exploits VMware ESXi Flaw in Latest Attack Wave]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blackbyte-ransomware-exploits-vmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blackbyte-ransomware-exploits-vmware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the BlackByte ransomware group have been observed likely exploiting a recently patched security flaw impacting VMware ESXi hypervisors, while also leveraging various vulnerable drivers to disarm security protections.
"The BlackByte ransomware group continues to leverage tactics, techniques, and procedures (TTPs) that have formed the foundation of its tradecraft since its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New QR Code Phishing Campaign Exploits Microsoft Sway to Steal Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qr-code-phishing-campaign-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qr-code-phishing-campaign-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T06:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are calling attention to a new QR code phishing (aka quishing) campaign that leverages Microsoft Sway infrastructure to host fake pages, once again highlighting the abuse of legitimate cloud offerings for malicious purposes.
"By using legitimate cloud applications, attackers provide credibility to victims, helping them to trust the content it serves," Netskope Threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Flags Critical Apache OFBiz Flaw Amid Active Exploitation Reports]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-flags-critical-apache-ofbiz-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-flags-critical-apache-ofbiz-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T05:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Tuesday added a critical security flaw affecting the Apache OFBiz open-source enterprise resource planning (ERP) system to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation in the wild.
The vulnerability, known as CVE-2024-38856, carries a CVSS score of 9.8, indicating critical severity.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical WPML Plugin Flaw Exposes WordPress Sites to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-wpml-plugin-flaw-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-wpml-plugin-flaw-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-28T04:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the WPML WordPress multilingual plugin that could allow authenticated users to execute arbitrary code remotely under certain circumstances.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-6386 (CVSS score: 9.9), impacts all versions of the plugin before 4.6.13, which was released on August 20, 2024.
Arising due to missing input validation and sanitization,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[macOS Version of HZ RAT Backdoor Targets Chinese Messaging App Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/macos-version-of-hz-rat-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/macos-version-of-hz-rat-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T16:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of Chinese instant messaging apps like DingTalk and WeChat are the target of an Apple macOS version of a backdoor named HZ RAT.
The artifacts "almost exactly replicate the functionality of the Windows version of the backdoor and differ only in the payload, which is received in the form of shell scripts from the attackers' server," Kaspersky researcher Sergey Puzan said.
HZ RAT was first]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Volt Typhoon Exploits Versa Director Flaw, Targets U.S. and Global IT Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-volt-typhoon-exploits-versa.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-volt-typhoon-exploits-versa.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-nexus cyber espionage group tracked as Volt Typhoon has been attributed with moderate confidence to the zero-day exploitation of a recently disclosed high-severity security flaw impacting Versa Director.
The attacks targeted four U.S. victims and one non-U.S. victim in the Internet service provider (ISP), managed service provider (MSP) and information technology (IT) sectors as early]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTEM in the Spotlight: How Gartner's New Categories Help to Manage Exposures]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ctem-in-spotlight-how-gartners-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ctem-in-spotlight-how-gartners-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T13:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Want to know what’s the latest and greatest in SecOps for 2024? Gartner’s recently released Hype Cycle for Security Operations report takes important steps to organize and mature the domain of Continuous Threat Exposure Management, aka CTEM. Three categories within this domain are included in this year’s report: Threat Exposure Management, Exposure Assessment Platforms (EAP), and Adversarial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Fixes ASCII Smuggling Flaw That Enabled Data Theft from Microsoft 365 Copilot]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-fixes-ascii-smuggling-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-fixes-ascii-smuggling-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T06:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a now-patched vulnerability in Microsoft 365 Copilot that could enable the theft of sensitive user information using a technique called ASCII smuggling.
"ASCII Smuggling is a novel technique that uses special Unicode characters that mirror ASCII but are actually not visible in the user interface," security researcher Johann Rehberger said.
"This means that an attacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Warns of CVE-2024-7965 Chrome Security Flaw Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-warns-of-cve-2024-7965-chrome.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-warns-of-cve-2024-7965-chrome.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-27T04:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has revealed that a security flaw that was patched as part of a security update rolled out last week to its Chrome browser has come under active exploitation in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-7965, the vulnerability has been described as an inappropriate implementation bug in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine.
"Inappropriate implementation in V8 in Google Chrome prior to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall Issues Critical Patch for Firewall Vulnerability Allowing Unauthorized Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sonicwall-issues-critical-patch-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sonicwall-issues-critical-patch-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall has released security updates to address a critical flaw impacting its firewalls that, if successfully exploited, could grant malicious actors unauthorized access to the devices.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-40766 (CVSS score: 9.3), has been described as an improper access control bug.
"An improper access control vulnerability has been identified in the SonicWall SonicOS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Regulator Fines Uber €290 Million for GDPR Violations in Data Transfers to U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/dutch-regulators-fines-uber-290-million.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/dutch-regulators-fines-uber-290-million.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T14:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dutch Data Protection Authority (DPA) has fined Uber a record €290 million ($324 million) for allegedly failing to comply with European Union (E.U.) data protection standards when sending sensitive driver data to the U.S.
"The Dutch DPA found that Uber transferred personal data of European taxi drivers to the United States (U.S.) and failed to appropriately safeguard the data with regard to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (26 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0721/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0721/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T11:33:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking Slack Hacks: 6 Ways to Protect Sensitive Data with Secure Collaboration]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpacking-slack-hacks-6-ways-to-protect.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpacking-slack-hacks-6-ways-to-protect.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nowadays, sensitive and critical data is traveling in everyday business channels that offer only the basic level of security and encryption, and companies are often oblivious to the risk. A case in point: Disney suffered a devastating data leak by a hacktivist group known as NullBulge that got hold of over 1.2 terabytes of data from Disney's internal Slack messaging channels. The breach exposed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Identify Over 20 Supply Chain Vulnerabilities in MLOps Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-identify-over-20-supply.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-identify-over-20-supply.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T10:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about the security risks in the machine learning (ML) software supply chain following the discovery of more than 20 vulnerabilities that could be exploited to target MLOps platforms.
These vulnerabilities, which are described as inherent- and implementation-based flaws, could have severe consequences, ranging from arbitrary code execution to loading]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws in Traccar GPS System Expose Users to Remote Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaws-in-traccar-gps-system.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaws-in-traccar-gps-system.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in the open-source Traccar GPS tracking system that could be potentially exploited by unauthenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution under certain circumstances.
Both the vulnerabilities are path traversal flaws and could be weaponized if guest registration is enabled, which is the default configuration for Traccar 5, Horizon3.ai]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-038 (26 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-038/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-038/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T07:33:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Malware NGate Steals NFC Data to Clone Contactless Payment Cards]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-malware-ngate-steals-nfc.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-android-malware-ngate-steals-nfc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-26T04:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered new Android malware that can relay victims' contactless payment data from physical credit and debit cards to an attacker-controlled device with the goal of conducting fraudulent operations.
The Slovak cybersecurity company is tracking the novel malware as NGate, stating it observed the crimeware campaign targeting three banks in Czechia.
The malware "has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Founder Pavel Durov Arrested in France for Content Moderation Failures]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/telegram-founder-pavel-durov-arrested.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/telegram-founder-pavel-durov-arrested.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov, founder and chief executive of the popular messaging app Telegram, was arrested in France on Saturday, according to French television network TF1.
Durov is believed to have been apprehended pursuant to a warrant issued in connection with a preliminary police investigation.
TF1 said the probe was focused on a lack of content moderation on the instant messaging service, which the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Malware 'sedexp' Hides Credit Card Skimmers Using Udev Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-linux-malware-sedexp-hides-credit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-linux-malware-sedexp-hides-credit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-25T05:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new stealthy piece of Linux malware that leverages an unconventional technique to achieve persistence on infected systems and hide credit card skimmer code.
The malware, attributed to a financially motivated threat actor, has been codenamed sedexp by Aon's Stroz Friedberg incident response services team.
"This advanced threat, active since 2022, hides]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Urges Federal Agencies to Patch Versa Director Vulnerability by September]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-urges-federal-agencies-to-patch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-urges-federal-agencies-to-patch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has placed a security flaw impacting Versa Director to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog based on evidence of active exploitation.
The medium-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-39717 (CVSS score: 6.6), is case of file upload bug impacting the "Change Favicon" feature that could allow a threat actor to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Exposes Iranian Hacker Group Targeting Global Political Figures on WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/meta-exposes-iranian-hacker-group.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/meta-exposes-iranian-hacker-group.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-24T06:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Platforms on Friday became the latest company after Microsoft, Google, and OpenAI to expose the activities of an Iranian state-sponsored threat actor, who it said used a set of WhatsApp accounts that attempted to target individuals in Israel, Palestine, Iran, the U.K., and the U.S.
The activity cluster, which originated from Iran, "appeared to have focused on political and diplomatic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PEAKLIGHT Dropper Deployed in Attacks Targeting Windows with Malicious Movie Downloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-peaklight-dropper-deployed-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-peaklight-dropper-deployed-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T15:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a never-before-seen dropper that serves as a conduit to launch next-stage malware with the ultimate goal of infecting Windows systems with information stealers and loaders.

"This memory-only dropper decrypts and executes a PowerShell-based downloader," Google-owned Mandiant said. "This PowerShell-based downloader is being tracked as PEAKLIGHT."

Some of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM QRadar SIEM (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0720/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0720/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:53:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans IBM QRadar SIEM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0719/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0719/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:46:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0718/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0718/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0717/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0717/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:26:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Experience the Power of a Must-Have All-in-One Cybersecurity Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-experience-power-of-must-have.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/webinar-experience-power-of-must-have.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Let's be honest. The world of cybersecurity feels like a constant war zone. You're bombarded by threats, scrambling to keep up with patches, and drowning in an endless flood of alerts. It's exhausting, isn’t it?
But what if there was a better way?
Imagine having every essential cybersecurity tool at your fingertips, all within a single, intuitive platform, backed by expert support 24/7. This is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0716/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0716/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:14:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Boot (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0715/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0715/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T11:11:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Boot. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Focus on What Matters Most: Exposure Management and Your Attack Surface]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/focus-on-what-matters-most-exposure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/focus-on-what-matters-most-exposure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Read the full article for key points from Intruder’s VP of Product, Andy Hornegold’s recent talk on exposure management. If you’d like to hear Andy’s insights first-hand, watch Intruder’s on-demand webinar. To learn more about reducing your attack surface, reach out to their team today. 
Attack surface management vs exposure management
Attack surface management (ASM) is the ongoing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Qilin Ransomware Attack Uses VPN Credentials, Steals Chrome Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qilin-ransomware-attack-uses-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-qilin-ransomware-attack-uses-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind a recently observed Qilin ransomware attack have stolen credentials stored in Google Chrome browsers on a small set of compromised endpoints.
The use of credential harvesting in connection with a ransomware infection marks an unusual twist, and one that could have cascading consequences, cybersecurity firm Sophos said in a Thursday report.
The attack, detected in July]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0714/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0714/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T09:23:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0713/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0713/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T07:09:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Sonicwall (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0712/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0712/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T06:59:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Sonicwall. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (23 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0711/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0711/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T06:25:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New macOS Malware "Cthulhu Stealer" Targets Apple Users' Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-cthulhu-stealer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-cthulhu-stealer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new information stealer that's designed to target Apple macOS hosts and harvest a wide range of information, underscoring how threat actors are increasingly setting their sights on the operating system.
Dubbed Cthulhu Stealer, the malware has been available under a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) model for $500 a month from late 2023. It's capable of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latvian Hacker Extradited to U.S. for Role in Karakurt Cybercrime Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/latvian-hacker-extradited-to-us-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/latvian-hacker-extradited-to-us-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-23T04:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 33-year-old Latvian national living in Moscow, Russia, has been charged in the U.S. for allegedly stealing data, extorting victims, and laundering ransom payments since August 2021.
Deniss Zolotarjovs (aka Sforza_cesarini) has been charged with conspiring to commit money laundering, wire fraud and Hobbs Act extortion. He was arrested in Georgia in December 2023 and has since been extradited to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardware Backdoor Discovered in RFID Cards Used in Hotels and Offices Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardware-backdoor-discovered-in-rfid.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardware-backdoor-discovered-in-rfid.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a hardware backdoor within a particular model of MIFARE Classic contactless cards that could allow authentication with an unknown key and open hotel rooms and office doors.
The attacks have been demonstrated against FM11RF08S, a new variant of MIFARE Classic that was released by Shanghai Fudan Microelectronics in 2020.
"The FM11RF08S backdoor enables any]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hardcoded Credential Vulnerability Found in SolarWinds Web Help Desk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardcoded-credential-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hardcoded-credential-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has issued patches to address a new security flaw in its Web Help Desk (WHD) software that could allow remote unauthenticated users to gain unauthorized access to susceptible instances.
"The SolarWinds Web Help Desk (WHD) software is affected by a hardcoded credential vulnerability, allowing [a] remote unauthenticated user to access internal functionality and modify data," the company]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploit Zero-Day Cisco Switch Flaw to Gain System Control]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-hackers-exploit-zero-day-cisco.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/chinese-hackers-exploit-zero-day-cisco.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a China-nexus threat group's exploitation of a recently disclosed, now-patched security flaw in Cisco switches as a zero-day to seize control of the appliance and evade detection.
The activity, attributed to Velvet Ant, was observed early this year and involved the weaponization of CVE-2024-20399 (CVSS score: 6.0) to deliver bespoke malware and gain extensive control]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'ALBeast' Vulnerability Exposes Weakness in AWS Application Load Balancer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-albeast-vulnerability-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-albeast-vulnerability-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 15,000 applications using Amazon Web Services' (AWS) Application Load Balancer (ALB) for authentication are potentially susceptible to a configuration-based issue that could expose them to sidestep access controls and compromise applications.
That's according to findings from Israeli cybersecurity company Miggo, which dubbed the problem ALBeast.
"This vulnerability allows attackers to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Dovecot (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0710/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0710/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T12:23:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Dovecot. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Facts About Continuous Penetration Testing and Why It’s Important]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-facts-about-continuous-penetration.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-facts-about-continuous-penetration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T10:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[What is Continuous Attack Surface Penetration Testing or CASPT?
Continuous Penetration Testing or Continuous Attack Surface Penetration Testing (CASPT) is an advanced security practice that involves the continuous, automated, and ongoing penetration testing services of an organization's digital assets to identify and mitigate security vulnerabilities. CASPT is designed for enterprises with an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0709/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0709/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:07:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Cisco (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0708/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0708/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Cisco. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mitel MiContact Center Business (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0707/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0707/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T08:00:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mitel MiContact Center Business. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (22 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0706/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0706/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T07:57:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-7971 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fixes High-Severity Chrome Flaw Actively Exploited in the Wild]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-fixes-high-severity-chrome-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T05:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has rolled out security fixes to address a high-severity security flaw in its Chrome browser that it said has come under active exploitation in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-7971, the vulnerability has been described as a type confusion bug in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine.
"Type confusion in V8 in Google Chrome prior to 128.0.6613.84 allowed a remote attacker to exploit heap]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in WordPress LiteSpeed Cache Plugin Allows Hackers Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-wordpress-litespeed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-wordpress-litespeed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T05:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a critical security flaw in the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress that could permit unauthenticated users to gain administrator privileges.
"The plugin suffers from an unauthenticated privilege escalation vulnerability which allows any unauthenticated visitor to gain Administrator level access after which malicious plugins could be uploaded and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Patches Critical Security Flaw in Enterprise Server Granting Admin Privileges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-patches-critical-security-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-patches-critical-security-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T04:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has released fixes to address a set of three security flaws impacting its Enterprise Server product, including one critical bug that could be abused to gain site administrator privileges.
The most severe of the shortcomings has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-6800, and carries a CVSS score of 9.5.
"On GitHub Enterprise Server instances that use SAML single sign-on (SSO)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware PG_MEM Targets PostgreSQL Databases for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-pgmem-targets-postgresql.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-pgmem-targets-postgresql.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-22T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unpacked a new malware strain dubbed PG_MEM that's designed to mine cryptocurrency after brute-forcing their way into PostgreSQL database instances.
"Brute-force attacks on Postgres involve repeatedly attempting to guess the database credentials until access is gained, exploiting weak passwords," Aqua security researcher Assaf Morag said in a technical report.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0705/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0705/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:29:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB Enterprise Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Patches Critical Copilot Studio Vulnerability Exposing Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-critical-copilot.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-critical-copilot.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a critical security flaw impacting Microsoft's Copilot Studio that could be exploited to access sensitive information.
Tracked as CVE-2024-38206 (CVSS score: 8.5), the vulnerability has been described as an information disclosure bug stemming from a server-side request forgery (SSRF) attack.
"An authenticated attacker can bypass Server-Side Request]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Deploy New MoonPeak Trojan in Cyber Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T15:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new remote access trojan called MoonPeak has been discovered as being used by a state-sponsored North Korean threat activity cluster as part of a new campaign.
Cisco Talos attributed the malicious cyber campaign to a hacking group it tracks as UAT-5394, which it said exhibits some level of tactical overlaps with a known nation-state actor codenamed Kimsuky.
MoonPeak, under active development]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0704/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0704/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:13:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time To Untangle the SaaS Ball of Yarn]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/its-time-to-untangle-saas-ball-of-yarn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/its-time-to-untangle-saas-ball-of-yarn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It's no great revelation to say that SaaS applications have changed the way we operate, both in our personal and professional lives. We routinely rely on cloud-based and remote applications to conduct our basic functions, with the result that the only true perimeter of our networks has become the identities with which we log into these services.
Unfortunately – as is so often the case – our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Styx Stealer Creator's OPSEC Fail Leaks Client List and Profit Details]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/styx-stealer-creators-opsec-fail-leaks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/styx-stealer-creators-opsec-fail-leaks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In what's a case of an operational security (OPSEC) lapse, the operator behind a new information stealer called Styx Stealer leaked data from their own computer, including details related to the clients, profit information, nicknames, phone numbers, and email addresses.
Styx Stealer, a derivative of the Phemedrone Stealer, is capable of stealing browser data, instant messenger sessions from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New macOS Malware TodoSwift Linked to North Korean Hacking Groups]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-todoswift-linked-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-macos-malware-todoswift-linked-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new macOS malware strain dubbed TodoSwift that they say exhibits commonalities with known malicious software used by North Korean hacking groups.
"This application shares several behaviors with malware we've seen that originated in North Korea (DPRK) — specifically the threat actor known as BlueNoroff — such as KANDYKORN and RustBucket," Kandji security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0703/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0703/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:48:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0702/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0702/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:32:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Joomla! (21 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0701/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0701/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Joomla!. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERT-UA Warns of New Vermin-Linked Phishing Attacks with PoW Bait]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cert-ua-warns-of-new-vermin-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cert-ua-warns-of-new-vermin-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T05:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of new phishing attacks that aim to infect devices with malware.
The activity has been attributed to a threat cluster it tracks as UAC-0020, which is also known as Vermin. The exact scale and scope of the attacks are presently unknown.
The attack chains commence with phishing messages with photos of alleged prisoners of war (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GiveWP WordPress Plugin Vulnerability Puts 100,000+ Websites at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/givewp-wordpress-plugin-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/givewp-wordpress-plugin-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-21T04:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A maximum-severity security flaw has been disclosed in the WordPress GiveWP donation and fundraising plugin that exposes more than 100,000 websites to remote code execution attacks.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-5932 (CVSS score: 10.0), impacts all versions of the plugin prior to version 3.14.2, which was released on August 7, 2024. A security researcher, who goes by the online alias villu164,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Detecting AWS Account Compromise: Key Indicators in CloudTrail Logs for Stolen API Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/detecting-aws-account-compromise-key.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/detecting-aws-account-compromise-key.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T20:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cloud infrastructure becomes the backbone of modern enterprises, ensuring the security of these environments is paramount. With AWS (Amazon Web Services) still being the dominant cloud it is important for any security professional to know where to look for signs of compromise. AWS CloudTrail stands out as an essential tool for tracking and logging API activity, providing a comprehensive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Czech Mobile Users Targeted in New Banking Credential Theft Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/czech-mobile-users-targeted-in-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/czech-mobile-users-targeted-in-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T19:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile users in the Czech Republic are the target of a novel phishing campaign that leverages a Progressive Web Application (PWA) in an attempt to steal their banking account credentials.
The attacks have targeted the Czech-based Československá obchodní banka (CSOB), as well as the Hungarian OTP Bank and the Georgian TBC Bank, according to Slovak cybersecurity company ESET.
"The phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit PHP Vulnerability to Deploy Stealthy Msupedge Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-php-vulnerability-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/hackers-exploit-php-vulnerability-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented backdoor named Msupedge has been put to use against a cyber attack targeting an unnamed university in Taiwan.
"The most notable feature of this backdoor is that it communicates with a command-and-control (C&C) server via DNS traffic," the Symantec Threat Hunter Team, part of Broadcom, said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
The origins of the backdoor are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatomy of an Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/anatomy-of-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/anatomy-of-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T10:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly evolving cyber threat landscape, organizations face increasingly sophisticated attacks targeting their applications. Understanding these threats and the technologies designed to combat them is crucial. This article delves into the mechanics of a common application attack, using the infamous Log4Shell vulnerability as an example, and demonstrates how Application Detection and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover TLS Bootstrap Attack on Azure Kubernetes Clusters]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-tls-bootstrap.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-tls-bootstrap.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a security flaw impacting Microsoft Azure Kubernetes Services that, if successfully exploited, could allow an attacker to escalate their privileges and access credentials for services used by the cluster.
"An attacker with command execution in a Pod running within an affected Azure Kubernetes Services cluster could download the configuration used to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Cyber Group TA453 Targets Jewish Leader with New AnvilEcho Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-cyber-group-ta453-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-cyber-group-ta453-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T09:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian state-sponsored threat actors have been observed orchestrating spear-phishing campaigns targeting a prominent Jewish figure starting in late July 2024 with the goal of delivering a new intelligence-gathering tool called AnvilEcho.
Enterprise security company Proofpoint is tracking the activity under the name TA453, which overlaps with activity tracked by the broader cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Security (20 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0700/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0700/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T06:35:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SpringSecurity. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blind Eagle Hackers Exploit Spear-Phishing to Deploy RATs in Latin America]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blind-eagle-hackers-exploit-spear.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/blind-eagle-hackers-exploit-spear.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T06:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a threat actor known as Blind Eagle that has persistently targeted entities and individuals in Colombia, Ecuador, Chile, Panama, and other Latin American nations.
Targets of these attacks span several sectors, including governmental institutions, financial companies, energy and oil and gas companies.
"Blind Eagle has demonstrated adaptability in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Thousands of Oracle NetSuite Sites at Risk of Exposing Customer Information]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/thousands-of-oracle-netsuite-sites-at.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/thousands-of-oracle-netsuite-sites-at.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T05:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning about the discovery of thousands of externally-facing Oracle NetSuite e-commerce sites that have been found susceptible to leaking sensitive customer information.
"A potential issue in NetSuite's SuiteCommerce platform could allow attackers to access sensitive data due to misconfigured access controls on custom record types (CRTs)," AppOmni's Aaron Costello]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Critical Jenkins Vulnerability Exploited in Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-critical-jenkins.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cisa-warns-of-critical-jenkins.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-20T04:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a critical security flaw impacting Jenkins to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, following its exploitation in ransomware attacks.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23897 (CVSS score: 9.8), is a path traversal flaw that could lead to code execution.
"Jenkins Command Line Interface (CLI) contains a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits F5 et Nginx (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0699/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0699/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T14:49:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits F5. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New UULoader Malware Distributes Gh0st RAT and Mimikatz in East Asia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-uuloader-malware-distributes-gh0st.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-uuloader-malware-distributes-gh0st.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new type of malware called UULoader is being used by threat actors to deliver next-stage payloads like Gh0st RAT and Mimikatz.
The Cyberint Research Team, which discovered the malware, said it's distributed in the form of malicious installers for legitimate applications targeting Korean and Chinese speakers.
There is evidence pointing to UULoader being the work of a Chinese speaker due to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0698/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0698/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:44:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0697/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0697/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:44:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploit Popular Software Searches to Spread FakeBat Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-exploit-popular-software.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cybercriminals-exploit-popular-software.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a surge in malware infections stemming from malvertising campaigns distributing a loader called FakeBat.
"These attacks are opportunistic in nature, targeting users seeking popular business software," the Mandiant Managed Defense team said in a technical report. "The infection utilizes a trojanized MSIX installer, which executes a PowerShell script to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0696/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0696/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T12:03:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Automate the Hardest Parts of Employee Offboarding]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2023/11/how-to-automate-hardest-parts-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2023/11/how-to-automate-hardest-parts-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[According to recent research on employee offboarding, 70% of IT professionals say they’ve experienced the negative effects of incomplete IT offboarding, whether in the form of a security incident tied to an account that wasn't deprovisioned, a surprise bill for resources that aren’t in use anymore, or a missed handoff of a critical resource or account. This is despite an average of five]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Xeon Sender Tool Exploits Cloud APIs for Large-Scale SMS Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/xeon-sender-tool-exploits-cloud-apis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/xeon-sender-tool-exploits-cloud-apis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T10:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors are using a cloud attack tool named Xeon Sender to conduct SMS phishing and spam campaigns on a large scale by abusing legitimate services.
"Attackers can use Xeon to send messages through multiple software-as-a-service (SaaS) providers using valid credentials for the service providers," SentinelOne security researcher Alex Delamotte said in a report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-037 (19 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-037/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-037/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:40:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Patches Zero-Day Flaw Exploited by North Korea’s Lazarus Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-zero-day-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-patches-zero-day-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T07:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly patched security flaw in Microsoft Windows was exploited as a zero-day by Lazarus Group, a prolific state-sponsored actor affiliated with North Korea.
The security vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38193 (CVSS score: 7.8), has been described as a privilege escalation bug in the Windows Ancillary Function Driver (AFD.sys) for WinSock.
"An attacker who successfully exploited this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover New Infrastructure Tied to FIN7 Cybercrime Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-new-infrastructure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-new-infrastructure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-19T05:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered new infrastructure linked to a financially motivated threat actor known as FIN7.
The two clusters of potential FIN7 activity "indicate communications inbound to FIN7 infrastructure from IP addresses assigned to Post Ltd (Russia) and SmartApe (Estonia), respectively," Team Cymru said in a report published this week as part of a joint investigation with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI Blocks Iranian Influence Operation Using ChatGPT for U.S. Election Propaganda]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/openai-blocks-iranian-influence.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/openai-blocks-iranian-influence.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-17T06:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI on Friday said it banned a set of accounts linked to what it said was an Iranian covert influence operation that leveraged ChatGPT to generate content that, among other things, focused on the upcoming U.S. presidential election.
"This week we identified and took down a cluster of ChatGPT accounts that were generating content for a covert Iranian influence operation identified as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers Exploit Public .env Files to Breach Cloud and Social Media Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/attackers-exploit-public-env-files-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/attackers-exploit-public-env-files-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large-scale extortion campaign has compromised various organizations by taking advantage of publicly accessible environment variable files (.env) that contain credentials associated with cloud and social media applications.
"Multiple security missteps were present in the course of this campaign, including the following: Exposing environment variables, using long-lived credentials, and absence]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hacker Jailed 3+ Years for Selling Stolen Credentials on Dark Web]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hacker-jailed-3-years-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hacker-jailed-3-years-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T14:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 27-year-old Russian national has been sentenced to over three years in prison for peddling financial information, login credentials, and other personally identifying information (PII) on a now-defunct dark web marketplace called Slilpp.
Georgy Kavzharadze, 27, of Moscow, Russia, pleaded guilty to one count of conspiracy to commit bank fraud and wire fraud earlier this February. In addition to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Using Fake Brand Sites to Spread DanaBot and StealC Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-using-fake-brand-sites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-using-fake-brand-sites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T13:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a sophisticated information stealer campaign that impersonates legitimate brands to distribute malware like DanaBot and StealC.
The activity cluster, orchestrated by Russian-speaking cybercriminals and collectively codenamed Tusk, is said to encompass several sub-campaigns, leveraging the reputation of the platforms to trick users into downloading the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0695/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0695/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:47:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0694/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0694/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0693/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0693/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:44:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multi-Stage ValleyRAT Targets Chinese Users with Advanced Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/multi-stage-valleyrat-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/multi-stage-valleyrat-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking users are the target of an ongoing campaign that distributes malware known as ValleyRAT.
"ValleyRAT is a multi-stage malware that utilizes diverse techniques to monitor and control its victims and deploy arbitrary plugins to cause further damage," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researchers Eduardo Altares and Joie Salvio said.
"Another noteworthy characteristic of this malware is its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Hidden Security Gaps in Your SaaS Apps: Are You Doing Due Diligence?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-hidden-security-gaps-in-your-saas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-hidden-security-gaps-in-your-saas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications have become indispensable for organizations aiming to enhance productivity and streamline operations. However, the convenience and efficiency these applications offer come with inherent security risks, often leaving hidden gaps that can be exploited. Conducting thorough due diligence on SaaS apps is essential to identify and mitigate these risks, ensuring the protection of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0692/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0692/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T11:25:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0691/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0691/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Elastic APM Server (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0690/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0690/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:08:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic APM Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Spring Framework (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0689/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0689/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:04:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Spring Framework. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0688/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0688/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T09:01:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mitel Unify OpenScape Business Application (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0687/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0687/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:49:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mitel Unify OpenScape Business Application. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Xen (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0686/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0686/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:46:34.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk (16 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0685/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0685/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:37:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Web Help Desk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Banshee Stealer Targets 100+ Browser Extensions on Apple macOS Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-banshee-stealer-targets-100-browser.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-banshee-stealer-targets-100-browser.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered new stealer malware that's designed to specifically target Apple macOS systems.
Dubbed Banshee Stealer, it's offered for sale in the cybercrime underground for a steep price of $3,000 a month and works across both x86_64 and ARM64 architectures. 
"Banshee Stealer targets a wide range of browsers, cryptocurrency wallets, and around 100 browser]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Pixel Devices Shipped with Vulnerable App, Leaving Millions at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-pixel-devices-shipped-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/google-pixel-devices-shipped-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-16T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A large percentage of Google's own Pixel devices shipped globally since September 2017 included dormant software that could be used to stage nefarious attacks and deliver various kinds of malware.
The issue manifests in the form of a pre-installed Android app called "Showcase.apk" that comes with excessive system privileges, including the ability to remotely execute code and install arbitrary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Releases Patch for Critical Flaw in Web Help Desk Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/solarwinds-releases-patch-for-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/solarwinds-releases-patch-for-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T13:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has released patches to address a critical security vulnerability in its Web Help Desk software that could be exploited to execute arbitrary code on susceptible instances.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-28986 (CVSS score: 9.8), has been described as a deserialization bug.
"SolarWinds Web Help Desk was found to be susceptible to a Java deserialization remote code execution vulnerability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-Linked Hackers Target Eastern European NGOs and Media]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-linked-hackers-target-eastern.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-linked-hackers-target-eastern.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian and Belarusian non-profit organizations, Russian independent media, and international non-governmental organizations active in Eastern Europe have become the target of two separate spear-phishing campaigns orchestrated by threat actors whose interests align with that of the Russian government.
While one of the campaigns – dubbed River of Phish – has been attributed to COLDRIVER, an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Identity Threat Detection and Response Solution Guide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/identity-threat-detection-and-response.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/identity-threat-detection-and-response.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Emergence of Identity Threat Detection and Response
Identity Threat Detection and Response (ITDR) has emerged as a critical component to effectively detect and respond to identity-based attacks. Threat actors have shown their ability to compromise the identity infrastructure and move laterally into IaaS, Saas, PaaS and CI/CD environments. Identity Threat Detection and Response solutions help]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RansomHub Group Deploys New EDR-Killing Tool in Latest Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ransomhub-group-deploys-new-edr-killing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ransomhub-group-deploys-new-edr-killing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T10:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A cybercrime group with links to the RansomHub ransomware has been observed using a new tool designed to terminate endpoint detection and response (EDR) software on compromised hosts, joining the likes of other similar programs like AuKill (aka AvNeutralizer) and Terminator.
The EDR-killing utility has been dubbed EDRKillShifter by cybersecurity company Sophos, which discovered the tool in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Vulnerability 'ArtiPACKED' Exposes Repositories to Potential Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-vulnerability-artipacked-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/github-vulnerability-artipacked-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly discovered attack vector in GitHub Actions artifacts dubbed ArtiPACKED could be exploited to take over repositories and gain access to organizations' cloud environments.
"A combination of misconfigurations and security flaws can make artifacts leak tokens, both of third party cloud services and GitHub tokens, making them available for anyone with read access to the repository to consume,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cyber Threat Targets Azerbaijan and Israel Diplomats, Stealing Sensitive Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyber-threat-targets-azerbaijan-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyber-threat-targets-azerbaijan-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T06:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously unknown threat actor has been attributed to a spate of attacks targeting Azerbaijan and Israel with an aim to steal sensitive data.
The attack campaign, detected by NSFOCUS on July 1, 2024, leveraged spear-phishing emails to single out Azerbaijani and Israeli diplomats. The activity is being tracked under the moniker Actor240524.
"Actor240524 possesses the ability to steal secrets]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Gafgyt Botnet Variant Targets Weak SSH Passwords for GPU Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-gafgyt-botnet-variant-targets-weak.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-gafgyt-botnet-variant-targets-weak.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-15T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new variant of the Gafgyt botnet that's targeting machines with weak SSH passwords to ultimately mine cryptocurrency on compromised instances using their GPU computational power.
This indicates that the "IoT botnet is targeting more robust servers running on cloud native environments," Aqua Security researcher Assaf Morag said in a Wednesday analysis.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta-Linked Attackers Target Users with SystemBC Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/black-basta-linked-attackers-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/black-basta-linked-attackers-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T17:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing social engineering campaign with alleged links to the Black Basta ransomware group has been linked to "multiple intrusion attempts" with the goal of conducting credential theft and deploying a malware dropper called SystemBC.
"The initial lure being utilized by the threat actors remains the same: an email bomb followed by an attempt to call impacted users and offer a fake solution,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0684/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0684/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0683/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0683/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0681/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0681/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que les...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0682/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0682/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0680/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0680/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-38189 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0679/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0679/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T13:32:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0678/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0678/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T12:53:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belarusian-Ukrainian Hacker Extradited to U.S. for Ransomware and Cybercrime Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/belarusian-ukrainian-hacker-extradited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/belarusian-ukrainian-hacker-extradited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of law enforcement agencies coordinated by the U.K. National Crime Agency (NCA) has led to the arrest and extradition of a Belarussian and Ukrainian dual-national believed to be associated with Russian-speaking cybercrime groups.
Maksim Silnikau (aka Maksym Silnikov), 38, went by the online monikers J.P. Morgan, xxx, and lansky. He was extradited to the U.S. from Poland on August 9,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0677/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0677/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:30:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Augment Your Password Security with EASM]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-augment-your-password-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-augment-your-password-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Simply relying on traditional password security measures is no longer sufficient. When it comes to protecting your organization from credential-based attacks, it is essential to lock down the basics first. Securing your Active Directory should be a priority – it is like making sure a house has a locked front door before investing in a high-end alarm system. Once the fundamentals are covered,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Security Center (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0676/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0676/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T09:16:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Security Center. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nagios XI (14 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0675/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0675/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T09:12:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nagios XI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DDoS Attacks Surge 46% in First Half of 2024, Gcore Report Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ddos-attacks-surge-46-in-first-half-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ddos-attacks-surge-46-in-first-half-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T06:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Monitoring evolving DDoS trends is essential for anticipating threats and adapting defensive strategies. The comprehensive Gcore Radar Report for the first half of 2024 provides detailed insights into DDoS attack data, showcasing changes in attack patterns and the broader landscape of cyber threats. Here, we share a selection of findings from the full report.
Key Takeaways
The number of DDoS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues Patches for 90 Flaws, Including 10 Critical Zero-Day Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-issues-patches-for-90-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-issues-patches-for-90-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Tuesday shipped fixes to address a total of 90 security flaws, including 10 zero-days, of which six have come under active exploitation in the wild.
Of the 90 bugs, seven are rated Critical, 79 are rated Important, and one is rated Moderate in severity. This is also in addition to 36 vulnerabilities that the tech giant resolved in its Edge browser since last month.
The Patch Tuesday]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Ivanti Virtual Traffic Manager Could Allow Rogue Admin Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-ivanti-virtual-traffic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/critical-flaw-in-ivanti-virtual-traffic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has rolled out security updates for a critical flaw in Virtual Traffic Manager (vTM) that could be exploited to achieve an authentication bypass and create rogue administrative users.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7593, has a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"Incorrect implementation of an authentication algorithm in Ivanti vTM other than versions 22.2R1 or 22.7R2]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Backed Earth Baku Expands Cyber Attacks to Europe, Middle East, and Africa]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-backed-earth-baku-expands-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/china-backed-earth-baku-expands-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-14T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-backed threat actor known as Earth Baku has diversified its targeting footprint beyond the Indo-Pacific region to include Europe, the Middle East, and Africa starting in late 2022.
Newly targeted countries as part of the activity include Italy, Germany, the U.A.E., and Qatar, with suspected attacks also detected in Georgia and Romania. Governments, media and communications, telecoms,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Zabbix (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0674/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0674/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:08:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Zabbix. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhostWrite: New T-Head CPU Bugs Expose Devices to Unrestricted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ghostwrite-new-t-head-cpu-bugs-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ghostwrite-new-t-head-cpu-bugs-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A team of researchers from the CISPA Helmholtz Center for Information Security in Germany has disclosed an architectural bug impacting Chinese chip company T-Head's XuanTie C910 and C920 RISC-V CPUs that could allow attackers to gain unrestricted access to susceptible devices.
The vulnerability has been codenamed GhostWrite. It has been described as a direct CPU bug embedded in the hardware, as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider Electric (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0673/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0673/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider Electric. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0672/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0672/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:33:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Vulnerabilities in AI-Powered Azure Health Bot Service]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in_0471960302.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in_0471960302.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered two security flaws in Microsoft's Azure Health Bot Service that, if exploited, could permit a malicious actor to achieve lateral movement within customer environments and access sensitive patient data.
The critical issues, now patched by Microsoft, could have allowed access to cross-tenant resources within the service, Tenable said in a new report shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0671/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0671/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T12:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Hardsec Matters: From Protecting Critical Services to Enhancing Resilience]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/why-hardsec-matters-from-protecting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/why-hardsec-matters-from-protecting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditionally, the focus has been on defending against digital threats such as malware, ransomware, and phishing attacks by detecting them and responding. However, as cyber threats become more sophisticated. There is a growing recognition of the importance of measures that stop new attacks before they are recognized. With high-value assets, it’s not good enough to have the protection, it’s]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Shuts Down Dispossessor Ransomware Group's Servers Across U.S., U.K., and Germany]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-shuts-down-dispossessor-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/fbi-shuts-down-dispossessor-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) on Monday announced the disruption of online infrastructure associated with a nascent ransomware group called Dispossessor (aka Radar).
The effort saw the dismantling of three U.S. servers, three United Kingdom servers, 18 German servers, eight U.S.-based criminal domains, and one German-based criminal domain. Dispossessor is said to be led by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit (13 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0670/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0670/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T08:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Splunk Machine Learning Toolkit. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Warns of New Phishing Campaign Targeting Government Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ukraine-warns-of-new-phishing-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/ukraine-warns-of-new-phishing-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-13T05:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of a new phishing campaign that masquerades as the Security Service of Ukraine to distribute malware capable of remote desktop access.
The agency is tracking the activity under the name UAC-0198. More than 100 computers are estimated to have been infected since July 2024, including those related to government bodies in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Phishing Attacks Adapt Quickly to Capitalize on Current Events]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-phishing-attacks-adapt-quickly-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-phishing-attacks-adapt-quickly-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In 2023, no fewer than 94 percent of businesses were impacted by phishing attacks, a 40 percent increase compared to the previous year, according to research from Egress.
What's behind the surge in phishing? One popular answer is AI – particularly generative AI, which has made it trivially easier for threat actors to craft content that they can use in phishing campaigns, like malicious emails]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Vulnerabilities in Solarman and Deye Solar Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-vulnerabilities-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified a number of security shortcomings in photovoltaic system management platforms operated by Chinese companies Solarman and Deye that could enable malicious actors to cause disruption and power blackouts.
"If exploited, these vulnerabilities could allow an attacker to control inverter settings that could take parts of the grid down, potentially causing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Hangover is Here – The End of the Beginning]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-ai-hangover-is-here-end-of-beginning.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/the-ai-hangover-is-here-end-of-beginning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[After a good year of sustained exuberance, the hangover is finally here. It’s a gentle one (for now), as the market corrects the share price of the major players (like Nvidia, Microsoft, and Google), while other players reassess the market and adjust priorities. Gartner calls it the trough of disillusionment, when interest wanes and implementations fail to deliver the promised breakthroughs.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FreeBSD Releases Urgent Patch for High-Severity OpenSSH Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/freebsd-releases-urgent-patch-for-high.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/freebsd-releases-urgent-patch-for-high.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of the FreeBSD Project have released security updates to address a high-severity flaw in OpenSSH that attackers could potentially exploit to execute arbitrary code remotely with elevated privileges.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7589, carries a CVSS score of 7.4 out of a maximum of 10.0, indicating high severity.
"A signal handler in sshd(8) may call a logging function]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-036 (12 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-036/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-036/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T06:57:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Industrial Remote Access Tool Ewon Cosy+ Vulnerable to Root Access Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/industrial-remote-access-tool-ewon-cosy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/industrial-remote-access-tool-ewon-cosy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T06:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in the industrial remote access solution Ewon Cosy+ that could be abused to gain root privileges to the devices and stage follow-on attacks.
The elevated access could then be weaponized to decrypt encrypted firmware files and encrypted data such as passwords in configuration files, and even get correctly signed X.509 VPN certificates for foreign]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EastWind Attack Deploys PlugY and GrewApacha Backdoors Using Booby-Trapped LNK Files]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-government-hit-by-eastwind.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-government-hit-by-eastwind.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-12T03:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian government and IT organizations are the target of a new campaign that delivers a number of backdoors and trojans as part of a spear-phishing campaign codenamed EastWind.
The attack chains are characterized by the use of RAR archive attachments containing a Windows shortcut (LNK) file that, upon opening, activates the infection sequence, culminating in the deployment of malware such]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rogue PyPI Library Solana Users, Steals Blockchain Wallet Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/rogue-pypi-library-solana-users-steals.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/rogue-pypi-library-solana-users-steals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-11T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new malicious package on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that masquerades as a library from the Solana blockchain platform but is actually designed to steal victims' secrets.
"The legitimate Solana Python API project is known as 'solana-py' on GitHub, but simply 'solana' on the Python software registry, PyPI," Sonatype researcher Ax Sharma]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover 10 Flaws in Google's File Transfer Tool Quick Share]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-10-flaws-in-googles.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/researchers-uncover-10-flaws-in-googles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T19:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 10 security flaws have been uncovered in Google's Quick Share data transfer utility for Android and Windows that could be assembled to trigger remote code execution (RCE) chain on systems that have the software installed.
"The Quick Share application implements its own specific application-layer communication protocol to support file transfers between nearby, compatible devices,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Hits 300,000 Users with Rogue Chrome and Edge Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-hits-300000-users-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-hits-300000-users-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T14:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An ongoing, widespread malware campaign has been observed installing rogue Google Chrome and Microsoft Edge extensions via a trojan distributed via fake websites masquerading as popular software.
"The trojan malware contains different deliverables ranging from simple adware extensions that hijack searches to more sophisticated malicious scripts that deliver local extensions to steal private data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Unpatched Office Vulnerability Leading to Data Breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-warns-of-unpatched-office.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-warns-of-unpatched-office.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-10T05:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has disclosed an unpatched zero-day in Office that, if successfully exploited, could result in unauthorized disclosure of sensitive information to malicious actors.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38200 (CVSS score: 7.5), has been described as a spoofing flaw that affects the following versions of Office -

Microsoft Office 2016 for 32-bit edition and 64-bit editions
Microsoft]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Uncover Severe AWS Flaws Leading to RCE, Data Theft, and Full-Service Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/experts-uncover-severe-aws-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/experts-uncover-severe-aws-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T21:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered multiple critical flaws in Amazon Web Services (AWS) offerings that, if successfully exploited, could result in serious consequences.
"The impact of these vulnerabilities range between remote code execution (RCE), full-service user takeover (which might provide powerful administrative access), manipulation of AI modules, exposing sensitive data, data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Reveals Four OpenVPN Flaws Leading to Potential RCE and LPE]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-reveals-four-openvpn-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/microsoft-reveals-four-openvpn-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-09T18:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Thursday disclosed four medium-severity security flaws in the open-source OpenVPN software that could be chained to achieve remote code execution (RCE) and local privilege escalation (LPE).
"This attack chain could enable attackers to gain full control over targeted endpoints, potentially resulting in data breaches, system compromise, and unauthorized access to sensitive information]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>