<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-06-09T09:43:26.413Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PHP Vulnerability Exposes Windows Servers to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-php-vulnerability-exposes-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/new-php-vulnerability-exposes-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a new critical security flaw impacting PHP that could be exploited to achieve remote code execution under certain circumstances.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-4577, has been described as a CGI argument injection vulnerability affecting all versions of PHP installed on the Windows operating system.
According to DEVCORE security researcher, the shortcoming makes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Revamps Controversial AI-Powered Recall Feature Amid Privacy Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-revamps-controversial-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/microsoft-revamps-controversial-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-08T06:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Friday said it will disable its much-criticized artificial intelligence (AI)-powered Recall feature by default and make it an opt-in.
Recall, currently in preview and coming exclusively to Copilot+ PCs on June 18, 2024, functions as an "explorable visual timeline" by capturing screenshots of what appears on users' screens every five seconds, which are subsequently analyzed and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ultimate Cyber Hygiene Guide: Learn How to Simplify Your Security Efforts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ultimate-cyber-hygiene-guide-learn-how.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ultimate-cyber-hygiene-guide-learn-how.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2023 was a year of unprecedented cyberattacks. Ransomware crippled businesses, DDoS attacks disrupted critical services, and data breaches exposed millions of sensitive records. The cost of these attacks? Astronomical. The damage to reputations? Irreparable.
But here's the shocking truth: many of these attacks could have been prevented with basic cyber hygiene.
Are you ready to transform your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LightSpy Spyware's macOS Variant Found with Advanced Surveillance Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lightspy-spywares-macos-variant-found.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/lightspy-spywares-macos-variant-found.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed that the LightSpy spyware allegedly targeting Apple iOS users is in fact a previously undocumented macOS variant of the implant.
The findings come from both Huntress Labs and ThreatFabric, which separately analyzed the artifacts associated with the cross-platform malware framework that likely possesses capabilities to infect Android, iOS, Windows, macOS,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Serv-U (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0467</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0467"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Serv-U. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Debian (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0472</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0472"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:33:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Debian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0471</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0471"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T13:20:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0470</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0470"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:50:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Elastic (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0469</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0469"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Elastic. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Landscape is Evolving - So Should Your SCA]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cyber-landscape-is-evolving-so-should.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/cyber-landscape-is-evolving-so-should.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional SCAs Are Broken: Did You Know You Are Missing Critical Pieces?
Application Security professionals face enormous challenges securing their software supply chains, racing against time to beat the attacker to the mark. 
Software Composition Analysis (SCA) tools have become a basic instrument in the application security arsenal in the last 7 years. Although essential, many platforms]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The AI Debate: Google's Guidelines, Meta's GDPR Dispute, Microsoft's Recall Backlash]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-ai-debate-googles-guidelines-metas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-ai-debate-googles-guidelines-metas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is urging third-party Android app developers to incorporate generative artificial intelligence (GenAI) features in a responsible manner.
The new guidance from the search and advertising giant is an effort to combat problematic content, including sexual content and hate speech, created through such tools.
To that end, apps that generate content using AI must ensure they don't create]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans PHP (07 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0468</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0468"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T08:48:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PHP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Distributes 7,000 LockBit Ransomware Decryption Keys to Help Victims]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/fbi-distributes-7000-lockbit-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/fbi-distributes-7000-lockbit-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI) has disclosed that it's in possession of more than 7,000 decryption keys associated with the LockBit ransomware operation to help victims get their data back at no cost.
"We are reaching out to known LockBit victims and encouraging anyone who suspects they were a victim to visit our Internet Crime Complaint Center at ic3.gov," FBI Cyber Division]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SPECTR Malware Targets Ukraine Defense Forces in SickSync Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/spectr-malware-targets-ukraine-defense.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/spectr-malware-targets-ukraine-defense.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T07:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned of cyber attacks targeting defense forces in the country with a malware called SPECTR as part of an espionage campaign dubbed SickSync.
The agency attributed the attacks to a threat actor it tracks under the moniker UAC-0020, which is also called Vermin and is assessed to be associated with security agencies of the Luhansk]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Commando Cat Cryptojacking Attacks Target Misconfigured Docker Instances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/commando-cat-cryptojacking-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/commando-cat-cryptojacking-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-07T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Commando Cat has been linked to an ongoing cryptojacking attack campaign that leverages poorly secured Docker instances to deploy cryptocurrency miners for financial gain.
"The attackers used the cmd.cat/chattr docker image container that retrieves the payload from their own command-and-control (C&C) infrastructure," Trend Micro researchers Sunil Bharti and Shubham]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Muhstik Botnet Exploiting Apache RocketMQ Flaw to Expand DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/muhstik-botnet-exploiting-apache.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/muhstik-botnet-exploiting-apache.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T13:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) botnet known as Muhstik has been observed leveraging a now-patched security flaw impacting Apache RocketMQ to co-opt susceptible servers and expand its scale.
"Muhstik is a well-known threat targeting IoT devices and Linux-based servers, notorious for its ability to infect devices and utilize them for cryptocurrency mining and launching Distributed Denial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third-Party Cyber Attacks: The Threat No One Sees Coming – Here's How to Stop Them]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/third-party-cyber-attacks-threat-no-one.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/third-party-cyber-attacks-threat-no-one.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Learn about critical threats that can impact your organization and the bad actors behind them from Cybersixgill’s threat experts. Each story shines a light on underground activities, the threat actors involved, and why you should care, along with what you can do to mitigate risk. 
In an increasingly interconnected world, supply chain attacks have emerged as a formidable threat, compromising]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Prevent Account Takeover with Better Password Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prevent-account-takeover-with-better.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/prevent-account-takeover-with-better.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Tom works for a reputable financial institution. He has a long, complex password that would be near-impossible to guess. He’s memorized it by heart, so he started using it for his social media accounts and on his personal devices too. Unbeknownst to Tom, one of these sites has had its password database compromised by hackers and put it up for sale on the dark web. Now threat actors are working]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Legitimate Packer Software to Spread Malware Undetected]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-packer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-exploit-legitimate-packer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T09:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are increasingly abusing legitimate and commercially available packer software such as BoxedApp to evade detection and distribute malware such as remote access trojans and information stealers.
"The majority of the attributed malicious samples targeted financial institutions and government industries," Check Point security researcher Jiri Vinopal said in an analysis.
The volume of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Elastic (06 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0466</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0466"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:24:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Elastic. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Maps Timeline Data to be Stored Locally on Your Device for Privacy]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-maps-timeline-data-to-be-stored.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/google-maps-timeline-data-to-be-stored.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced plans to store Maps Timeline data locally on users' devices instead of their Google account effective December 1, 2024.
The changes were originally announced by the tech giant in December 2023, alongside changes to the auto-delete control when enabling Location History by setting it to three months by default, down from the previous limit of 18 months.
Google Maps Timeline,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB PyMongo (06 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0465</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0465"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T07:11:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB PyMongo. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Target Python Developers with Fake "Crytic-Compilers" Package on PyPI]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-target-python-developers-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-target-python-developers-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-06T05:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a malicious Python package uploaded to the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that's designed to deliver an information stealer called Lumma (aka LummaC2).
The package in question is crytic-compilers, a typosquatted version of a legitimate library named crytic-compile. The rogue package was downloaded 441 times before it was taken down by PyPI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese State-Backed Cyber Espionage Targets Southeast Asian Government]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-state-backed-cyber-espionage.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/chinese-state-backed-cyber-espionage.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unnamed high-profile government organization in Southeast Asia emerged as the target of a "complex, long-running" Chinese state-sponsored cyber espionage operation codenamed Crimson Palace.
"The overall goal behind the campaign was to maintain access to the target network for cyberespionage in support of Chinese state interests," Sophos researchers Paul Jaramillo, Morgan Demboski, Sean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpacking 2024's SaaS Threat Predictions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/unpacking-2024s-saas-threat-predictions.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/unpacking-2024s-saas-threat-predictions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Early in 2024, Wing Security released its State of SaaS Security report, offering surprising insights into emerging threats and best practices in the SaaS domain. Now, halfway through the year, several SaaS threat predictions from the report have already proven accurate. Fortunately, SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM) solutions have prioritized mitigation capabilities to address many of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rebranded Knight Ransomware Targeting Healthcare and Businesses Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rebranded-knight-ransomware-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/rebranded-knight-ransomware-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An analysis of a nascent ransomware strain called RansomHub has revealed it to be an updated and rebranded version of Knight ransomware, itself an evolution of another ransomware known as Cyclops.
Knight (aka Cyclops 2.0) ransomware first arrived in May 2023, employing double extortion tactics to steal and encrypt victims' data for financial gain. It's operational across multiple platforms,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel Releases Patches for Firmware Vulnerabilities in EoL NAS Models]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zyxel-releases-patches-for-firmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/zyxel-releases-patches-for-firmware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel has released security updates to address critical flaws impacting two of its network-attached storage (NAS) devices that have currently reached end-of-life (EoL) status.
Successful exploitation of three of the five vulnerabilities could permit an unauthenticated attacker to execute operating system (OS) commands and arbitrary code on affected installations.
Impacted models include NAS326]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans SolarWinds Platform (05 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0464</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0464"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:25:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SolarWinds Platform. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Celebrity TikTok Accounts Compromised Using Zero-Click Attack via DMs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/celebrity-tiktok-accounts-compromised.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/celebrity-tiktok-accounts-compromised.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular video-sharing platform TikTok has acknowledged a security issue that has been exploited by threat actors to take control of high-profile accounts on the platform.
The development was first reported by Semafor and Forbes, which detailed a zero-click account takeover campaign that allows malware propagated via direct messages to compromise brand and celebrity accounts without having to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ruby on Rails (05 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0463</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0463"/>
        <updated>2024-06-05T06:08:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ruby on Rails. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Power Companies, IT Firms, and Govt Agencies Hit by Decoy Dog Trojan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-power-companies-it-firms-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/russian-power-companies-it-firms-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T15:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian organizations are at the receiving end of cyber attacks that have been found to deliver a Windows version of a malware called Decoy Dog.
Cybersecurity company Positive Technologies is tracking the activity cluster under the name Operation Lahat, attributing it to an advanced persistent threat (APT) group called HellHounds.
"The Hellhounds group compromises organizations they select and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telerik Report Server Flaw Could Let Attackers Create Rogue Admin Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/telerik-report-server-flaw-could-let.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/telerik-report-server-flaw-could-let.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has rolled out updates to address a critical security flaw impacting the Telerik Report Server that could be potentially exploited by a remote attacker to bypass authentication and create rogue administrator users.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2024-4358, carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.0.
"In Progress Telerik Report Server, version 2024 Q1 (10.0.24.305) or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Platform (04 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0462</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0462"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:58:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Platform. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Next Generation of RBI (Remote Browser Isolation)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-next-generation-of-rbi-remote.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/the-next-generation-of-rbi-remote.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of browser security has undergone significant changes over the past decade. While Browser Isolation was once considered the gold standard for protecting against browser exploits and malware downloads, it has become increasingly inadequate and insecure in today's SaaS-centric world.
The limitations of Browser Isolation, such as degraded browser performance and inability to tackle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Use MS Excel Macro to Launch Multi-Stage Malware Attack in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-use-ms-excel-macro-to-launch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/hackers-use-ms-excel-macro-to-launch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new sophisticated cyber attack has been observed targeting endpoints geolocated to Ukraine with an aim to deploy Cobalt Strike and seize control of the compromised hosts.
The attack chain, per Fortinet FortiGuard Labs, involves a Microsoft Excel file that carries an embedded VBA macro to initiate the infection,
"The attacker uses a multi-stage malware strategy to deliver the notorious 'Cobalt]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Snowflake Warns: Targeted Credential Theft Campaign Hits Cloud Customers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-warns-targeted-credential.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/snowflake-warns-targeted-credential.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing and analytics company Snowflake said a "limited number" of its customers have been singled out as part of a targeted campaign.
"We have not identified evidence suggesting this activity was caused by a vulnerability, misconfiguration, or breach of Snowflake’s platform," the company said in a joint statement along with CrowdStrike and Google-owned Mandiant.
"We have not identified]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (04 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0461</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0461"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T07:50:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkGate Malware Replaces AutoIt with AutoHotkey in Latest Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/darkgate-malware-replaces-autoit-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/darkgate-malware-replaces-autoit-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber attacks involving the DarkGate malware-as-a-service (MaaS) operation have shifted away from AutoIt scripts to an AutoHotkey mechanism to deliver the last stages, underscoring continued efforts on the part of the threat actors to continuously stay ahead of the detection curve.
The updates have been observed in version 6 of DarkGate released in March 2024 by its developer RastaFarEye, who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Oracle WebLogic Server OS Command Injection Flaw Under Active Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oracle-weblogic-server-os-command.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/oracle-weblogic-server-os-command.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-04T03:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a security flaw impacting the Oracle WebLogic Server to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2017-3506 (CVSS score: 7.4), the issue concerns an operating system (OS) command injection vulnerability that could be exploited to obtain unauthorized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover RAT-Dropping npm Package Targeting Gulp Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-rat-dropping-npm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researchers-uncover-rat-dropping-npm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new suspicious package uploaded to the npm package registry that's designed to drop a remote access trojan (RAT) on compromised systems.
The package in question is glup-debugger-log, which targets users of the gulp toolkit by masquerading as a "logger for gulp and gulp plugins." It has been downloaded 175 times to date.
Software supply chain security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities Ramp Up Efforts to Capture the Mastermind Behind Emotet]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/authorities-ramp-up-efforts-to-capture.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/authorities-ramp-up-efforts-to-capture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement authorities behind Operation Endgame are seeking information related to an individual who goes by the name Odd and is allegedly the mastermind behind the Emotet malware. 
Odd is also said to go by the nicknames Aron, C700, Cbd748, Ivanov Odd, Mors, Morse, Veron over the past few years, according to a video released by the agencies.
"Who is he working with? What is his]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-024 (03 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-024</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-024"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T12:01:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SASE Threat Report: 8 Key Findings for Enterprise Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sase-threat-report-8-key-findings-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/sase-threat-report-8-key-findings-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are evolving, yet Cyber Threat Intelligence (CTI) remains confined to each isolated point solution. Organizations require a holistic analysis across external data, inbound and outbound threats and network activity. This will enable evaluating the true state of cybersecurity in the enterprise.
Cato’s Cyber Threat Research Lab (Cato CTRL, see more details below) has recently released]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researcher Uncovers Flaws in Cox Modems, Potentially Impacting Millions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researcher-uncovers-flaws-in-cox-modems.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/researcher-uncovers-flaws-in-cox-modems.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Now-patched authorization bypass issues impacting Cox modems that could have been abused as a starting point to gain unauthorized access to the devices and run malicious commands.
"This series of vulnerabilities demonstrated a way in which a fully external attacker with no prerequisites could've executed commands and modified the settings of millions of modems, accessed any business customer's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les caméras Synology (03 juin 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0460</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0460"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:49:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les caméras Synology. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Andariel Hackers Target South Korean Institutes with New Dora RAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/andariel-hackers-target-south-korean.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/andariel-hackers-target-south-korean.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T07:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Andariel has been observed using a new Golang-based backdoor called Dora RAT in its attacks targeting educational institutes, manufacturing firms, and construction businesses in South Korea.
"Keylogger, Infostealer, and proxy tools on top of the backdoor were utilized for the attacks," the AhnLab Security Intelligence Center (ASEC) said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Fake Browser Updates Deliver BitRAT and Lumma Stealer Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/beware-fake-browser-updates-deliver.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/beware-fake-browser-updates-deliver.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-03T03:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fake web browser updates are being used to deliver remote access trojans (RATs) and information stealer malware such as BitRAT and Lumma Stealer (aka LummaC2).
"Fake browser updates have been responsible for numerous malware infections, including those of the well-known SocGholish malware," cybersecurity firm eSentire said in a new report. "In April 2024, we observed FakeBat being distributed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AI Company Hugging Face Notifies Users of Suspected Unauthorized Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ai-company-hugging-face-notifies-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/06/ai-company-hugging-face-notifies-users.html"/>
        <updated>2024-06-01T07:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) company Hugging Face on Friday disclosed that it detected unauthorized access to its Spaces platform earlier this week.
"We have suspicions that a subset of Spaces’ secrets could have been accessed without authorization," it said in an advisory.
Spaces offers a way for users to create, host, and share AI and machine learning (ML) applications. It also functions as a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mysterious Cyber Attack Took Down 600,000+ Routers in the U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/mysterious-cyber-attack-takes-down.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/mysterious-cyber-attack-takes-down.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 600,000 small office/home office (SOHO) routers are estimated to have been bricked and taken offline following a destructive cyber attack staged by unidentified cyber actors, disrupting users' access to the internet.
The mysterious event, which took place between October 25 and 27, 2023, and impacted a single internet service provider (ISP) in the U.S., has been codenamed Pumpkin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of Surge in Cyber Attacks Targeting Internet-Exposed OT Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-warns-of-surge-in-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-warns-of-surge-in-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has emphasized the need for securing internet-exposed operational technology (OT) devices following a spate of cyber attacks targeting such environments since late 2023.
"These repeated attacks against OT devices emphasize the crucial need to improve the security posture of OT devices and prevent critical systems from becoming easy targets," the Microsoft Threat Intelligence team said.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0459</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0459"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:22:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0458</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0458"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T13:00:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0457</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0457"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T12:54:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0456</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0456"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T12:22:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beyond Threat Detection – A Race to Digital Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/beyond-threat-detection-race-to-digital.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/beyond-threat-detection-race-to-digital.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Digital content is a double-edged sword, providing vast benefits while simultaneously posing significant threats to organizations across the globe. The sharing of digital content has increased significantly in recent years, mainly via email, digital documents, and chat. In turn, this has created an expansive attack surface and has made ‘digital content’ the preferred carrier for cybercriminals]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Target Europe with HeadLace Malware and Credential Harvesting]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-hackers-target-europe-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/russian-hackers-target-europe-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian GRU-backed threat actor APT28 has been attributed as behind a series of campaigns targeting networks across Europe with the HeadLace malware and credential-harvesting web pages.
APT28, also known by the names BlueDelta, Fancy Bear, Forest Blizzard, FROZENLAKE, Iron Twilight, ITG05, Pawn Storm, Sednit, Sofacy, and TA422, is an advanced persistent threat (APT) group affiliated with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI, Meta, TikTok Disrupt Multiple AI-Powered Disinformation Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/openai-meta-tiktok-disrupt-multiple-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/openai-meta-tiktok-disrupt-multiple-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T08:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[OpenAI on Thursday disclosed that it took steps to cut off five covert influence operations (IO) originating from China, Iran, Israel, and Russia that sought to abuse its artificial intelligence (AI) tools to manipulate public discourse or political outcomes online while obscuring their true identity.
These activities, which were detected over the past three months, used its AI models to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Trend Micro (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0455</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0455"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T07:30:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Trend Micro. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (31 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0454</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0454"/>
        <updated>2024-05-31T07:26:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Alerts Federal Agencies to Patch Actively Exploited Linux Kernel Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-alerts-federal-agencies-to-patch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-alerts-federal-agencies-to-patch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T17:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a security flaw impacting the Linux kernel to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2024-1086 (CVSS score: 7.8), the high-severity issue relates to a use-after-free bug in the netfilter component that permits a local attacker to elevate privileges]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FlyingYeti Exploits WinRAR Vulnerability to Deliver COOKBOX Malware in Ukraine]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/flyingyeti-exploits-winrar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/flyingyeti-exploits-winrar.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T16:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare on Thursday said it took steps to disrupt a month-long phishing campaign orchestrated by a Russia-aligned threat actor called FlyingYeti targeting Ukraine.
"The FlyingYeti campaign capitalized on anxiety over the potential loss of access to housing and utilities by enticing targets to open malicious files via debt-themed lures," Cloudflare's threat intelligence team Cloudforce One]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Espionage Alert: LilacSquid Targets IT, Energy, and Pharma Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cyber-espionage-alert-lilacsquid.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cyber-espionage-alert-lilacsquid.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T15:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented cyber espionage-focused threat actor named LilacSquid has been linked to targeted attacks spanning various sectors in the United States (U.S.), Europe, and Asia as part of a data theft campaign since at least 2021.
"The campaign is geared toward establishing long-term access to compromised victim organizations to enable LilacSquid to siphon data of interest to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RedTail Crypto-Mining Malware Exploiting Palo Alto Networks Firewall Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/redtail-crypto-mining-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/redtail-crypto-mining-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T14:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the RedTail cryptocurrency mining malware have added a recently disclosed security flaw impacting Palo Alto Networks firewalls to its exploit arsenal.
The addition of the PAN-OS vulnerability to its toolkit has been complemented by updates to the malware, which now incorporates new anti-analysis techniques, according to findings from web infrastructure and security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Active Exploitation of WordPress Plugin Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-active-exploitation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-active-exploitation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T13:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have warned that multiple high-severity security vulnerabilities in WordPress plugins are being actively exploited by threat actors to create rogue administrator accounts for follow-on exploitation.
"These vulnerabilities are found in various WordPress plugins and are prone to unauthenticated stored cross-site scripting (XSS) attacks due to inadequate input sanitization]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Opération ENDGAME (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-004</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-004"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T12:58:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Entre le 27 et le 29 mai 2024, une opération de démantèlement de plusieurs infrastructures liées à des codes cybercriminels a été menée dans le cadre d’une coopération judiciaire internationale impliquant les autorités allemandes, néerlandaises, danoises, françaises, britanniques et américaines....]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Build Your Autonomous SOC Strategy]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/how-to-build-your-autonomous-soc.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/how-to-build-your-autonomous-soc.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T11:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security leaders are in a tricky position trying to discern how much new AI-driven cybersecurity tools could actually benefit a security operations center (SOC). The hype about generative AI is still everywhere, but security teams have to live in reality. They face constantly incoming alerts from endpoint security platforms, SIEM tools, and phishing emails reported by internal users. Security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europol Shuts Down 100+ Servers Linked to IcedID, TrickBot, and Other Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/europol-dismantles-100-servers-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/europol-dismantles-100-servers-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Europol on Thursday said it shut down the infrastructure associated with several malware loader operations such as IcedID, SystemBC, PikaBot, SmokeLoader, Bumblebee, and TrickBot as part of a coordinated law enforcement effort codenamed Operation Endgame.
"The actions focused on disrupting criminal services through arresting High Value Targets, taking down the criminal infrastructures and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Ivanti Endpoint Manager (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0453</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0453"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T09:29:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Ivanti Endpoint Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Check Point  (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-008</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-008"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T09:07:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Check Point. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. L'éditeur indique avoir connaissance de tentatives d'exploitation depuis le 30 avril 2024. Le CERT-FR a connaissance de l’exploitation de cette...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Dismantles World's Largest 911 S5 Botnet, with 19 Million Infected Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/us-dismantles-worlds-largest-911-s5.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/us-dismantles-worlds-largest-911-s5.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Wednesday said it dismantled what it described as "likely the world's largest botnet ever," which consisted of an army of 19 million infected devices that was leased to other threat actors to commit a wide array of offenses.
The botnet, which has a global footprint spanning more than 190 countries, functioned as a residential proxy service known as 911 S5.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans StormShield SSL VPN Client (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0452</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0452"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T07:26:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans StormShield SSL VPN Client. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0451</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0451"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T07:21:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mitel MiVoice MX-ONE. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nginx (30 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0450</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0450"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T07:20:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nginx. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Okta Warns of Credential Stuffing Attacks Targeting Customer Identity Cloud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/okta-warns-of-credential-stuffing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/okta-warns-of-credential-stuffing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-30T06:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Okta is warning that a cross-origin authentication feature in Customer Identity Cloud (CIC) is susceptible to credential stuffing attacks orchestrated by threat actors.
"We observed that the endpoints used to support the cross-origin authentication feature being attacked via credential stuffing for a number of our customers," the Identity and access management (IAM) services provider said.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Abuse StackOverflow to Promote Malicious Python Package]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cybercriminals-abuse-stackoverflow-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cybercriminals-abuse-stackoverflow-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T17:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have warned of a new malicious Python package that has been discovered in the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository to facilitate cryptocurrency theft as part of a broader campaign.
The package in question is pytoileur, which has been downloaded 316 times as of writing. Interestingly, the package author, who goes by the name PhilipsPY, has uploaded a new version of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Check Point Warns of Zero-Day Attacks on its VPN Gateway Products]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/check-point-warns-of-zero-day-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/check-point-warns-of-zero-day-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T15:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Check Point is warning of a zero-day vulnerability in its Network Security gateway products that threat actors have exploited in the wild.
Tracked as CVE-2024-24919, the issue impacts CloudGuard Network, Quantum Maestro, Quantum Scalable Chassis, Quantum Security Gateways, and Quantum Spark appliances.
"The vulnerability potentially allows an attacker to read certain information on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Banks Targeted by New AllaKore RAT Variant Called AllaSenha]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/brazilian-banks-targeted-by-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/brazilian-banks-targeted-by-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T14:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian banking institutions are the target of a new campaign that distributes a custom variant of the Windows-based AllaKore remote access trojan (RAT) called AllaSenha.
The malware is "specifically aimed at stealing credentials that are required to access Brazilian bank accounts, [and] leverages Azure cloud as command-and-control (C2) infrastructure," French cybersecurity company HarfangLab]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Check Point (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0449</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0449"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T14:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Check Point. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Check Point indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-24919 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nagios XI (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0448</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0448"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T13:11:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nagios XI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SPIP (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0447</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0447"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T12:16:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SPIP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sentences 31-Year-Old to 10 Years for Laundering $4.5M in Email Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/us-sentences-31-year-old-to-10-years.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/us-sentences-31-year-old-to-10-years.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T11:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has sentenced a 31-year-old to 10 years in prison for laundering more than $4.5 million through business email compromise (BEC) schemes and romance scams.
Malachi Mullings, 31, of Sandy Springs, Georgia pleaded guilty to the money laundering offenses in January 2023.
According to court documents, Mullings is said to have opened 20 bank accounts in the name of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Research Warns About Weak Offboarding Management and Insider Risks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-research-warns-about-weak.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-research-warns-about-weak.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T11:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recent study by Wing Security found that 63% of businesses may have former employees with access to organizational data, and that automating SaaS Security can help mitigate offboarding risks. 
Employee offboarding is typically seen as a routine administrative task, but it can pose substantial security risks, if not handled correctly. Failing to quickly and thoroughly remove access for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Uncovers 'Moonstone Sleet' — New North Korean Hacker Group]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-uncovers-moonstone-sleet-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-uncovers-moonstone-sleet-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T10:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A never-before-seen North Korean threat actor codenamed Moonstone Sleet has been attributed as behind cyber attacks targeting individuals and organizations in the software and information technology, education, and defense industrial base sectors with ransomware and bespoke malware previously associated with the infamous Lazarus Group.
"Moonstone Sleet is observed to set up fake companies and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0446</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0446"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T09:18:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Cloud Skipper (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0445</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0445"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T09:11:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Cloud Skipper. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Citrix Workspace app pour Mac (29 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0444</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0444"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T08:04:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Citrix Workspace app pour Mac. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BreachForums Returns Just Weeks After FBI Seizure - Honeypot or Blunder?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/breachforums-returns-just-weeks-after.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/breachforums-returns-just-weeks-after.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-29T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The online criminal bazaar BreachForums has been resurrected merely two weeks after a U.S.-led coordinated law enforcement action dismantled and seized control of its infrastructure.
Cybersecurity researchers and dark web trackers Brett Callow, Dark Web Informer, and FalconFeeds revealed the site's online return at breachforums[.]st – one of the dismantled sites – by a user named ShinyHunters,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Indian National Pleads Guilty to $37 Million Cryptocurrency Theft Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/indian-national-pleads-guilty-to-37.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/indian-national-pleads-guilty-to-37.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Indian national has pleaded guilty in the U.S. over charges of stealing more than $37 million by setting up a website that impersonated the Coinbase cryptocurrency exchange platform.
Chirag Tomar, 30, pleaded guilty to wire fraud conspiracy, which carries a maximum sentence of 20 years in prison and a $250,000 fine. He was arrested on December 20, 2023, upon entering the country.
"Tomar and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4-Step Approach to Mapping and Securing Your Organization's Most Critical Assets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/4-step-approach-to-mapping-and-securing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/4-step-approach-to-mapping-and-securing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[You’re probably familiar with the term “critical assets”.
These are the technology assets within your company's IT infrastructure that are essential to the functioning of your organization. If anything happens to these assets, such as application servers, databases, or privileged identities, the ramifications to your security posture can be severe. 
But is every technology asset considered]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warn of CatDDoS Botnet and DNSBomb DDoS Attack Technique]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-warn-of-catddos-botnet-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-warn-of-catddos-botnet-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T10:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the CatDDoS malware botnet have exploited over 80 known security flaws in various software over the past three months to infiltrate vulnerable devices and co-opt them into a botnet for conducting distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks.
"CatDDoS-related gangs' samples have used a large number of known vulnerabilities to deliver samples," the QiAnXin XLab team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Plugin Exploited to Steal Credit Card Data from E-commerce Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/wordpress-plugin-exploited-to-steal.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/wordpress-plugin-exploited-to-steal.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unknown threat actors are abusing lesser-known code snippet plugins for WordPress to insert malicious PHP code in victim sites that are capable of harvesting credit card data.
The campaign, observed by Sucuri on May 11, 2024, entails the abuse of a WordPress plugin called Dessky Snippets, which allows users to add custom PHP code. It has over 200 active installations.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TP-Link Gaming Router Vulnerability Exposes Users to Remote Code Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/tp-link-gaming-router-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/tp-link-gaming-router-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-28T05:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A maximum-severity security flaw has been disclosed in the TP-Link Archer C5400X gaming router that could lead to remote code execution on susceptible devices by sending specially crafted requests.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-5035, carries a CVSS score of 10.0. It impacts all versions of the router firmware including and prior to 1_1.1.6. It has]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Moroccan Cybercrime Group Steals Up to $100K Daily Through Gift Card Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/moroccan-cybercrime-group-steals-up-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/moroccan-cybercrime-group-steals-up-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T12:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft is calling attention to a Morocco-based cybercrime group dubbed Storm-0539 that's behind gift card fraud and theft through highly sophisticated email and SMS phishing attacks.
"Their primary motivation is to steal gift cards and profit by selling them online at a discounted rate," the company said in its latest Cyber Signals report. "We've seen some examples where]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Report: The Dark Side of Phishing Protection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/report-dark-side-of-phishing-protection.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/report-dark-side-of-phishing-protection.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T11:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The transition to the cloud, poor password hygiene and the evolution in webpage technologies have all enabled the rise in phishing attacks. But despite sincere efforts by security stakeholders to mitigate them - through email protection, firewall rules and employee education - phishing attacks are still a very risky attack vector.
A new report by LayerX explores the state of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Tricks in the Phishing Playbook: Cloudflare Workers, HTML Smuggling, GenAI]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-tricks-in-phishing-playbook.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-tricks-in-phishing-playbook.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are alerting of phishing campaigns that abuse Cloudflare Workers to serve phishing sites that are used to harvest users' credentials associated with Microsoft, Gmail, Yahoo!, and cPanel Webmail.
The attack method, called transparent phishing or adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) phishing, "uses Cloudflare Workers to act as a reverse proxy server for a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-023 (27 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-023</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-023"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T07:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (27 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0443</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0443"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T07:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-5274 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pakistan-linked Hackers Deploy Python, Golang, and Rust Malware on Indian Targets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/pakistan-linked-hackers-deploy-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/pakistan-linked-hackers-deploy-python.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-27T06:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Pakistan-nexus Transparent Tribe actor has been linked to a new set of attacks targeting Indian government, defense, and aerospace sectors using cross-platform malware written in Python, Golang, and Rust.
"This cluster of activity spanned from late 2023 to April 2024 and is anticipated to persist," the BlackBerry Research and Intelligence Team said in a technical report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Find Flaw in Replicate AI Service Exposing Customers' Models and Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/experts-find-flaw-in-replicate-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/experts-find-flaw-in-replicate-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-25T09:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a critical security flaw in an artificial intelligence (AI)-as-a-service provider Replicate that could have allowed threat actors to gain access to proprietary AI models and sensitive information.
"Exploitation of this vulnerability would have allowed unauthorized access to the AI prompts and results of all Replicate's platform customers,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Created Rogue VMs to Evade Detection in Recent MITRE Cyber Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-created-rogue-vms-to-evade.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/hackers-created-rogue-vms-to-evade.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T16:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MITRE Corporation has revealed that the cyber attack targeting the not-for-profit company towards late December 2023 by exploiting zero-day flaws in Ivanti Connect Secure (ICS) involved the actor creating rogue virtual machines (VMs) within its VMware environment.
"The adversary created their own rogue VMs within the VMware environment, leveraging compromised vCenter Server access," MITRE]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fake Antivirus Websites Deliver Malware to Android and Windows Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fake-antivirus-websites-deliver-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fake-antivirus-websites-deliver-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T12:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed making use of fake websites masquerading as legitimate antivirus solutions from Avast, Bitdefender, and Malwarebytes to propagate malware capable of stealing sensitive information from Android and Windows devices.
"Hosting malicious software through sites which look legitimate is predatory to general consumers, especially those who look to protect their devices]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0442</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0442"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T11:55:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Do Hackers Blend In So Well? Learn Their Tricks in This Expert Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/how-do-hackers-blend-in-so-well-learn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/how-do-hackers-blend-in-so-well-learn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Don't be fooled into thinking that cyber threats are only a problem for large organizations. The truth is that cybercriminals are increasingly targeting smaller businesses, and they're getting smarter every day.
Join our FREE webinar "Navigating the SMB Threat Landscape: Key Insights from Huntress' Threat Report," in which Jamie Levy — Director of Adversary Tactics at Huntress, a renowned]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits WithSecure (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0441</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0441"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T11:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits WithSecure. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0440</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0440"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T11:15:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0439</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0439"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T11:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DevOps Dilemma: How Can CISOs Regain Control in the Age of Speed?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/devops-dilemma-how-can-cisos-regain.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/devops-dilemma-how-can-cisos-regain.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
The infamous Colonial pipeline ransomware attack (2021) and SolarWinds supply chain attack (2020) were more than data leaks; they were seismic shifts in cybersecurity. These attacks exposed a critical challenge for Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs): holding their ground while maintaining control over cloud security in the accelerating world of DevOps.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Detects 4th Chrome Zero-Day in May Actively Under Attack - Update ASAP]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-detects-4th-chrome-zero-day-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-detects-4th-chrome-zero-day-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Thursday rolled out fixes to address a high-severity security flaw in its Chrome browser that it said has been exploited in the wild.
Assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-5274, the vulnerability relates to a type confusion bug in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine. It was reported by Clément Lecigne of Google's Threat Analysis Group and Brendon Tiszka of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Courtroom Software Backdoored to Deliver RustDoor Malware in Supply Chain Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/courtroom-software-backdoored-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/courtroom-software-backdoored-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors have backdoored the installer associated with courtroom video recording software developed by Justice AV Solutions (JAVS) to deliver malware that's associated with a known backdoor called RustDoor.
The software supply chain attack, tracked as CVE-2024-4978, impacts JAVS Viewer v8.3.7, a component of the JAVS Suite 8 that allows users to create, manage, publish,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0438</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0438"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:14:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Japanese Experts Warn of BLOODALCHEMY Malware Targeting Government Agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/japanese-experts-warn-of-bloodalchemy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/japanese-experts-warn-of-bloodalchemy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered that the malware known as BLOODALCHEMY used in attacks targeting government organizations in Southern and Southeastern Asia is in fact an updated version of Deed RAT, which is believed to be a successor to ShadowPad.
"The origin of BLOODALCHEMY and Deed RAT is ShadowPad and given the history of ShadowPad being utilized in numerous APT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0437</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0437"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:08:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-5274 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (24 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0436</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0436"/>
        <updated>2024-05-24T09:01:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware Attacks Exploit VMware ESXi Vulnerabilities in Alarming Pattern]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ransomware-attacks-exploit-vmware-esxi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ransomware-attacks-exploit-vmware-esxi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T17:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware attacks targeting VMware ESXi infrastructure following an established pattern regardless of the file-encrypting malware deployed.
"Virtualization platforms are a core component of organizational IT infrastructure, yet they often suffer from inherent misconfigurations and vulnerabilities, making them a lucrative and highly effective target for threat actors to abuse,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Actively Exploited Apache Flink Security Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-apache.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-apache.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T16:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a security flaw impacting Apache Flink, the open-source, unified stream-processing and batch-processing framework, to the Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
Tracked as CVE-2020-17519, the issue relates to a case of improper access control that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Frontiers, Old Tactics: Chinese Espionage Group Targets Africa & Caribbean Govts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-frontiers-old-tactics-chinese-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-frontiers-old-tactics-chinese-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked threat actor known as Sharp Panda has expanded their targeting to include governmental organizations in Africa and the Caribbean as part of an ongoing cyber espionage campaign.
"The campaign adopts Cobalt Strike Beacon as the payload, enabling backdoor functionalities like C2 communication and command execution while minimizing the exposure of their custom tools," Check Point]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Are Your SaaS Backups as Secure as Your Production Data?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/are-your-saas-backups-as-secure-as-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/are-your-saas-backups-as-secure-as-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Conversations about data security tend to diverge into three main threads:

How can we protect the data we store on our on-premises or cloud infrastructure?
What strategies and tools or platforms can reliably backup and restore data?
What would losing all this data cost us, and how quickly could we get it back?

All are valid and necessary conversations for technology organizations of all shapes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Inside Operation Diplomatic Specter: Chinese APT Group's Stealthy Tactics Exposed]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/inside-operation-diplomatic-specter.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/inside-operation-diplomatic-specter.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Governmental entities in the Middle East, Africa, and Asia are the target of a Chinese advanced persistent threat (APT) group as part of an ongoing cyber espionage campaign dubbed Operation Diplomatic Specter since at least late 2022.
"An analysis of this threat actor’s activity reveals long-term espionage operations against at least seven governmental entities," Palo Alto Networks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (23 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0435</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0435"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:32:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Patches Critical Remote Code Execution Flaws in Endpoint Manager]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ivanti-patches-critical-remote-code.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ivanti-patches-critical-remote-code.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T09:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti on Tuesday rolled out fixes to address multiple critical security flaws in Endpoint Manager (EPM) that could be exploited to achieve remote code execution under certain circumstances.
Six of the 10 vulnerabilities – from CVE-2024-29822 through CVE-2024-29827 (CVSS scores: 9.6) – relate to SQL injection flaws that allow an unauthenticated attacker within the same network to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The End of an Era: Microsoft Phases Out VBScript for JavaScript and PowerShell]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-end-of-era-microsoft-phases-out.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-end-of-era-microsoft-phases-out.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-23T05:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Wednesday outlined its plans to deprecate Visual Basic Script (VBScript) in the second half of 2024 in favor of more advanced alternatives such as JavaScript and PowerShell.
"Technology has advanced over the years, giving rise to more powerful and versatile scripting languages such as JavaScript and PowerShell," Microsoft Program Manager Naveen Shankar said. "These languages]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0434</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0434"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:45:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0433</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0433"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:29:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Warn of Chinese-Aligned Hackers Targeting South China Sea Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-warn-of-chinese-aligned.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-warn-of-chinese-aligned.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed details of a previously undocumented threat group called Unfading Sea Haze that's believed to have been active since 2018.
The intrusion singled out high-level organizations in South China Sea countries, particularly military and government targets, Bitdefender said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
"The investigation revealed a troubling]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0432</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0432"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T14:01:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Veeam (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0431</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0431"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Veeam. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0430</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0430"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits SolarWinds (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0429</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0429"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:17:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits SolarWinds. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0428</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0428"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T13:12:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (22 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0427</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0427"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T12:59:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rockwell Advises Disconnecting Internet-Facing ICS Devices Amid Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/rockwell-advises-disconnecting-internet.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/rockwell-advises-disconnecting-internet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Rockwell Automation is urging its customers to disconnect all industrial control systems (ICSs) not meant to be connected to the public-facing internet to mitigate unauthorized or malicious cyber activity.
The company said it's issuing the advisory due to "heightened geopolitical tensions and adversarial cyber activity globally."
To that end, customers are required to take immediate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The Ultimate SaaS Security Posture Management Checklist, 2025 Edition]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-ultimate-saas-security-posture.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-ultimate-saas-security-posture.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since the first edition of The Ultimate SaaS Security Posture Management (SSPM) Checklist was released three years ago, the corporate SaaS sprawl has been growing at a double-digit pace. In large enterprises, the number of SaaS applications in use today is in the hundreds, spread across departmental stacks, complicating the job of security teams to protect organizations against]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GHOSTENGINE Exploits Vulnerable Drivers to Disable EDRs in Cryptojacking Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ghostengine-exploits-vulnerable-drivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ghostengine-exploits-vulnerable-drivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T08:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new cryptojacking campaign that employs vulnerable drivers to disable known security solutions (EDRs) and thwart detection in what's called a Bring Your Own Vulnerable Driver (BYOVD) attack.
Elastic Security Labs is tracking the campaign under the name REF4578 and the primary payload as GHOSTENGINE. Previous research from Chinese]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MS Exchange Server Flaws Exploited to Deploy Keylogger in Targeted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ms-exchange-server-flaws-exploited-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ms-exchange-server-flaws-exploited-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T07:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unknown threat actor is exploiting known security flaws in Microsoft Exchange Server to deploy a keylogger malware in attacks targeting entities in Africa and the Middle East.
Russian cybersecurity firm Positive Technologies said it identified over 30 victims spanning government agencies, banks, IT companies, and educational institutions. The first-ever compromise dates back to 2021.
"This]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QNAP Patches New Flaws in QTS and QuTS hero Impacting NAS Appliances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/qnap-patches-new-flaws-in-qts-and-quts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/qnap-patches-new-flaws-in-qts-and-quts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T05:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Taiwanese company QNAP has rolled out fixes for a set of medium-severity flaws impacting QTS and QuTS hero, some of which could be exploited to achieve code execution on its network-attached storage (NAS) appliances.
The issues, which impact QTS 5.1.x and QuTS hero h5.1.x, are listed below -

CVE-2024-21902 - An incorrect permission assignment for critical resource]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zoom Adopts NIST-Approved Post-Quantum End-to-End Encryption for Meetings]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/zoom-adopts-nist-approved-post-quantum.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/zoom-adopts-nist-approved-post-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T04:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular enterprise services provider Zoom has announced the rollout of post-quantum end-to-end encryption (E2EE) for Zoom Meetings, with support for Zoom Phone and Zoom Rooms coming in the future.
"As adversarial threats become more sophisticated, so does the need to safeguard user data," the company said in a statement. "With the launch of post-quantum E2EE, we are doubling down on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager Flaw Allows Authentication Bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-veeam-backup-enterprise.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-veeam-backup-enterprise.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-22T03:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users of Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager are being urged to update to the latest version following the discovery of a critical security flaw that could permit an adversary to bypass authentication protections.
Tracked as CVE-2024-29849 (CVSS score: 9.8), the vulnerability could allow an unauthenticated attacker to log in to the Veeam Backup Enterprise Manager web interface as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical GitHub Enterprise Server Flaw Allows Authentication Bypass]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-github-enterprise-server-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-github-enterprise-server-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T16:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub has rolled out fixes to address a maximum severity flaw in the GitHub Enterprise Server (GHES) that could allow an attacker to bypass authentication protections.
Tracked as CVE-2024-4985 (CVSS score: 10.0), the issue could permit unauthorized access to an instance without requiring prior authentication.
"On instances that use SAML single sign-on (SSO) authentication with the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware Delivery via Cloud Services Exploits Unicode Trick to Deceive Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/malware-delivery-via-cloud-services.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/malware-delivery-via-cloud-services.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T14:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new attack campaign dubbed CLOUD#REVERSER has been observed leveraging legitimate cloud storage services like Google Drive and Dropbox to stage malicious payloads.
"The VBScript and PowerShell scripts in the CLOUD#REVERSER inherently involves command-and-control-like activities by using Google Drive and Dropbox as staging platforms to manage file uploads and downloads," Securonix]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Roundcube (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0426</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0426"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:34:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Roundcube. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0426 : Vulnérabilité dans Roundcube (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0426/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0426/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:34:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Roundcube. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Ruby on Rails (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0425</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0425"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:21:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Ruby on Rails. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0425 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ruby on Rails (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0425/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0425/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:21:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Ruby on Rails. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Asterisk (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0424</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0424"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:14:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Asterisk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0424 : Vulnérabilité dans Asterisk (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0424/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0424/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:14:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Asterisk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarMarker Malware Evolves to Resist Takedown Attempts with Multi-Tiered Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/solarmarker-malware-evolves-to-resist.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/solarmarker-malware-evolves-to-resist.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The persistent threat actors behind the SolarMarker information-stealing malware have established a multi-tiered infrastructure to complicate law enforcement takedown efforts, new findings from Recorded Future show.
"The core of SolarMarker's operations is its layered infrastructure, which consists of at least two clusters: a primary one for active operations and a secondary one likely]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0423</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0423"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:02:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0423 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits NetApp (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0423/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0423/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T13:02:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits NetApp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Core Tenets Of Highly Effective DevSecOps Practices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/five-core-tenets-of-highly-effective.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/five-core-tenets-of-highly-effective.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the enduring challenges of building modern applications is to make them more secure without disrupting high-velocity DevOps processes or degrading the developer experience. Today’s cyber threat landscape is rife with sophisticated attacks aimed at all different parts of the software supply chain and the urgency for software-producing organizations to adopt DevSecOps practices that deeply]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Achieve security compliance with Wazuh File Integrity Monitoring]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/achieve-security-compliance-with-wazuh.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/achieve-security-compliance-with-wazuh.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) is an IT security control that monitors and detects file changes in computer systems. It helps organizations audit important files and system configurations by routinely scanning and verifying their integrity. Most information security standards mandate the use of FIM for businesses to ensure the integrity of their data.
IT security compliance involves adhering to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover Flaws in Python Package for AI Models and PDF.js Used by Firefox]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-flaws-in-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-flaws-in-python.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the llama_cpp_python Python package that could be exploited by threat actors to achieve arbitrary code execution.
Tracked as CVE-2024-34359 (CVSS score: 9.7), the flaw has been codenamed Llama Drama by software supply chain security firm Checkmarx.
"If exploited, it could allow attackers to execute arbitrary code on your system,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Streamlining IT Security Compliance Using the Wazuh FIM Capability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/streamlining-it-security-compliance.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/streamlining-it-security-compliance.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T10:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[File Integrity Monitoring (FIM) is an IT security control that monitors and detects file changes in computer systems. It helps organizations audit important files and system configurations by routinely scanning and verifying their integrity. Most information security standards mandate the use of FIM for businesses to ensure the integrity of their data.
IT security compliance involves adhering to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Windows 11 to Deprecate NTLM, Add AI-Powered App Controls and Security Defenses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/windows-11-to-deprecate-ntlm-add-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/windows-11-to-deprecate-ntlm-add-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Monday confirmed its plans to deprecate NT LAN Manager (NTLM) in Windows 11 in the second half of the year, as it announced a slew of new security measures to harden the widely-used desktop operating system.
"Deprecating NTLM has been a huge ask from our security community as it will strengthen user authentication, and deprecation is planned in the second half of 2024," the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-022 (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-022</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-022"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:50:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-022 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-022 (21 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-022/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-022/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T08:50:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NextGen Healthcare Mirth Connect Under Attack - CISA Issues Urgent Warning]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/nextgen-healthcare-mirth-connect-under.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/nextgen-healthcare-mirth-connect-under.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T07:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday added a security flaw impacting NextGen Healthcare Mirth Connect to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2023-43208 (CVSS score: N/A), concerns a case of unauthenticated remote code execution arising from an incomplete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA["Linguistic Lumberjack" Vulnerability Discovered in Popular Logging Utility Fluent Bit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/linguistic-lumberjack-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/linguistic-lumberjack-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-21T06:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a critical security flaw in a popular logging and metrics utility called Fluent Bit that could be exploited to achieve denial-of-service (DoS), information disclosure, or remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-4323, has been codenamed Linguistic Lumberjack by Tenable Research. It impacts versions from 2.0.7 through]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian MOIS-Linked Hackers Behind Destructive Attacks on Albania and Israel]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/iranian-mois-linked-hackers-behind.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/iranian-mois-linked-hackers-behind.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Iranian threat actor affiliated with the Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS) has been attributed as behind destructive wiping attacks targeting Albania and Israel under the personas Homeland Justice and Karma, respectively.
Cybersecurity firm Check Point is tracking the activity under the moniker Void Manticore, which is also known as Storm-0842 (formerly DEV-0842) by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Foxit PDF Reader Flaw Exploited by Hackers to Deliver Diverse Malware Arsenal]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/foxit-pdf-reader-flaw-exploited-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/foxit-pdf-reader-flaw-exploited-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T12:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple threat actors are weaponizing a design flaw in Foxit PDF Reader to deliver a variety of malware such as Agent Tesla, AsyncRAT, DCRat, NanoCore RAT, NjRAT, Pony, Remcos RAT, and XWorm.
"This exploit triggers security warnings that could deceive unsuspecting users into executing harmful commands," Check Point said in a technical report. "This exploit has been used by multiple]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Defending Your Commits From Known CVEs With GitGuardian SCA And Git Hooks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/defending-your-commits-from-known-cves.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/defending-your-commits-from-known-cves.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T10:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[All developers want to create secure and dependable software. They should feel proud to release their code with the full confidence they did not introduce any weaknesses or anti-patterns into their applications. Unfortunately, developers are not writing their own code for the most part these days. 96% of all software contains some open-source components, and open-source components make]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyber Criminals Exploit GitHub and FileZilla to Deliver Cocktail Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cyber-criminals-exploit-github-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cyber-criminals-exploit-github-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T09:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A "multi-faceted campaign" has been observed abusing legitimate services like GitHub and FileZilla to deliver an array of stealer malware and banking trojans such as Atomic (aka AMOS), Vidar, Lumma (aka LummaC2), and Octo by impersonating credible software like 1Password, Bartender 5, and Pixelmator Pro.
"The presence of multiple malware variants suggests a broad cross-platform targeting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Latrodectus Malware Loader Emerges as IcedID's Successor in Phishing Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/latrodectus-malware-loader-emerges-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/latrodectus-malware-loader-emerges-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-20T05:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have observed a spike in email phishing campaigns starting early March 2024 that delivers Latrodectus, a nascent malware loader believed to be the successor to the IcedID malware.
"These campaigns typically involve a recognizable infection chain involving oversized JavaScript files that utilize WMI's ability to invoke msiexec.exe and install a remotely-hosted MSI]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Nationals Arrested for Laundering $73 Million in Pig Butchering Crypto Scam]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/chinese-nationals-arrested-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/chinese-nationals-arrested-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) has charged two arrested Chinese nationals for allegedly orchestrating a pig butchering scam that laundered at least $73 million from victims through shell companies.
The individuals, Daren Li, 41, and Yicheng Zhang, 38, were arrested in Atlanta and Los Angeles on April 12 and May 16, respectively.
The foreign nationals have been "charged for leading a scheme]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Grandoreiro Banking Trojan Resurfaces, Targeting Over 1,500 Banks Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/grandoreiro-banking-trojan-resurfaces.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/grandoreiro-banking-trojan-resurfaces.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-19T07:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the Windows-based Grandoreiro banking trojan have returned in a global campaign since March 2024 following a law enforcement takedown in January.
The large-scale phishing attacks, likely facilitated by other cybercriminals via a malware-as-a-service (MaaS) model, target over 1,500 banks across the world, spanning more than 60 countries in Central and South]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kinsing Hacker Group Exploits More Flaws to Expand Botnet for Cryptojacking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/kinsing-hacker-group-exploits-more.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/kinsing-hacker-group-exploits-more.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T17:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptojacking group known as Kinsing has demonstrated its ability to continuously evolve and adapt, proving to be a persistent threat by swiftly integrating newly disclosed vulnerabilities to exploit arsenal and expand its botnet.
The findings come from cloud security firm Aqua, which described the threat actor as actively orchestrating illicit cryptocurrency mining]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0422 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0422/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0422/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T12:30:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0421 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0421/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0421/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T12:19:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0420 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0420/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0420/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T11:51:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0419 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0419/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0419/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T11:29:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New XM Cyber Research: 80% of Exposures from Misconfigurations, Less Than 1% from CVEs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-xm-cyber-research-80-of-exposures.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-xm-cyber-research-80-of-exposures.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new report from XM Cyber has found – among other insights - a dramatic gap between where most organizations focus their security efforts, and where the most serious threats actually reside.
The new report, Navigating the Paths of Risk: The State of Exposure Management in 2024, is based on hundreds of thousands of attack path assessments conducted by the XM Cyber]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Adopt Two-Stage Infection Tactic to Deploy Deuterbear RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-adopt-two-stage.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/china-linked-hackers-adopt-two-stage.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed more light on a remote access trojan (RAT) known as Deuterbear used by the China-linked BlackTech hacking group as part of a cyber espionage campaign targeting the Asia-Pacific region this year.
"Deuterbear, while similar to Waterbear in many ways, shows advancements in capabilities such as including support for shellcode plugins, avoiding handshakes]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky APT Deploying Linux Backdoor Gomir in South Korean Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/kimsuky-apt-deploying-linux-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/kimsuky-apt-deploying-linux-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Kimsuky (aka Springtail) advanced persistent threat (APT) group, which is linked to North Korea's Reconnaissance General Bureau (RGB), has been observed deploying a Linux version of its GoBear backdoor as part of a campaign targeting South Korean organizations.
The backdoor, codenamed Gomir, is "structurally almost identical to GoBear, with extensive sharing of code between]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0418 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure Monitor Agent (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0418/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0418/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:29:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure Monitor Agent. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0417 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0417/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0417/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:29:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.
 Google indique que la vulnérabilité …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0416 : Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0416/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0416/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:22:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0415 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0415/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0415/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T08:08:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0414 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0414/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0414/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0413 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits MongoDB (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0413/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0413/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:39:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MongoDB. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0412 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0412/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0412/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T07:32:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Actively Exploited D-Link Router Vulnerabilities - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-d-link.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited-d-link.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T06:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added two security flaws impacting D-Link routers to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The list of vulnerabilities is as follows -

CVE-2014-100005 - A cross-site request forgery (CSRF) vulnerability impacting D-Link DIR-600 routers that allows an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0417</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0417"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4947 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits MongoDB (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0413</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0413"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MongoDB. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure Monitor Agent (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0418</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0418"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure Monitor Agent. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0414</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0414"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0419</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0419"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0420</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0420"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0416</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0416"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0415</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0415"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0421</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0421"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mitel (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0412</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0412"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mitel. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (17 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0422</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0422"/>
        <updated>2024-05-17T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Wi-Fi Vulnerability Enables Network Eavesdropping via Downgrade Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-wi-fi-vulnerability-enabling.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-wi-fi-vulnerability-enabling.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers have discovered a new security vulnerability stemming from a design flaw in the IEEE 802.11 Wi-Fi standard that tricks victims into connecting to a less secure wireless network and eavesdrop on their network traffic.
The SSID Confusion attack, tracked as CVE-2023-52424, impacts all operating systems and Wi-Fi clients, including home and mesh networks that are based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Exploit Facebook Messenger in Targeted Malware Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/north-korean-hackers-exploit-facebook.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/north-korean-hackers-exploit-facebook.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T13:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked Kimsuky hacking group has been attributed to a new social engineering attack that employs fictitious Facebook accounts to targets via Messenger and ultimately delivers malware.
"The threat actor created a Facebook account with a fake identity disguised as a public official working in the North Korean human rights field," South Korean cybersecurity company Genians]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover 11 Security Flaws in GE HealthCare Ultrasound Machines]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-11-security-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/researchers-uncover-11-security-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security researchers have disclosed almost a dozen security flaws impacting the GE HealthCare Vivid Ultrasound product family that could be exploited by malicious actors to tamper with patient data and even install ransomware under certain circumstances.
"The impacts enabled by these flaws are manifold: from the implant of ransomware on the ultrasound machine to the access and manipulation of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0411 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Wireshark (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0411/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0411/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:42:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Wireshark. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0410 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0410/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0410/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:26:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.
 Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4947 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0409 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0409/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0409/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T07:04:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploiting Microsoft’s Quick Assist Feature in Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cybercriminals-exploiting-microsofts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/cybercriminals-exploiting-microsofts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T03:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Microsoft Threat Intelligence team said it has observed a threat it tracks under the name Storm-1811 abusing the client management tool Quick Assist to target users in social engineering attacks.
"Storm-1811 is a financially motivated cybercriminal group known to deploy Black Basta ransomware," the company said in a report published on May 15, 2024.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Patches Yet Another Actively Exploited Chrome Zero-Day Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-patches-yet-another-actively.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-patches-yet-another-actively.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T03:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has rolled out fixes to address a set of nine security issues in its Chrome browser, including a new zero-day that has been exploited in the wild.
Assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-4947, the vulnerability relates to a type confusion bug in the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine. It was reported by Kaspersky researchers Vasily Berdnikov and Boris]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Wireshark (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0411</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0411"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Wireshark. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0409</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0409"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (16 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0410</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0410"/>
        <updated>2024-05-16T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google indique que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4947 est activement exploitée.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Seizes BreachForums Again, Urges Users to Report Criminal Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fbi-seizes-breachforums-again-urges.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fbi-seizes-breachforums-again-urges.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement agencies have officially seized control of the notorious BreachForums platform, an online bazaar known for peddling stolen data, for the second time within a year.
The website ("breachforums[.]st") has been replaced by a seizure banner stating the clearnet cybercrime forum is under the control of the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI). 
The operation is the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Launches AI-Powered Theft and Data Protection Features for Android Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-adds-ai-powered-theft-protection.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/google-adds-ai-powered-theft-protection.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced a slew of privacy and security features in Android, including a suite of advanced protection features to help secure users' devices and data in the event of a theft.
These features aim to help protect data before, during and after a theft attempt, the tech giant said, adding they are expected to be available via an update to Google Play services for devices running]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Android 15 Rolls Out Advanced Features to Protect Users from Scams and Malicious Apps]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/android-15-introduces-new-features-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/android-15-introduces-new-features-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google is unveiling a set of new features in Android 15 to prevent malicious apps installed on the device from capturing sensitive data.
This constitutes an update to the Play Integrity API that third-party app developers can take advantage of to secure their applications against malware.
"Developers can check if there are other apps running that could be capturing the screen, creating]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0408 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0408/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0408/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T12:36:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0407 : Vulnérabilité dans LibreOffice (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0407/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0407/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T12:32:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Libreoffice. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Turla Group Deploys LunarWeb and LunarMail Backdoors in Diplomatic Missions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/turla-group-deploys-lunarweb-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/turla-group-deploys-lunarweb-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T12:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unnamed European Ministry of Foreign Affairs (MFA) and its three diplomatic missions in the Middle East were targeted by two previously undocumented backdoors tracked as LunarWeb and LunarMail.
ESET, which identified the activity, attributed it with medium confidence to the Russia-aligned cyberespionage group Turla (aka Iron Hunter, Pensive Ursa, Secret Blizzard, Snake, Uroburos, and Venomous]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0406 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0406/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0406/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T12:02:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0405 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0405/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0405/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:49:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[(Cyber) Risk = Probability of Occurrence x Damage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/get-cyber-resilient-with-cvss.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/get-cyber-resilient-with-cvss.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Here’s How to Enhance Your Cyber Resilience with CVSS
In late 2023, the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) v4.0 was unveiled, succeeding the eight-year-old CVSS v3.0, with the aim to enhance vulnerability assessment for both industry and the public. This latest version introduces additional metrics like safety and automation to address criticism of lacking granularity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0404 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0404/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0404/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T11:23:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ebury Botnet Malware Compromises 400,000 Linux Servers Over Past 14 Years]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ebury-botnet-malware-compromises-400000.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ebury-botnet-malware-compromises-400000.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malware botnet called Ebury is estimated to have compromised 400,000 Linux servers since 2009, out of which more than 100,000 were still compromised as of late 2023.
The findings come from Slovak cybersecurity firm ESET, which characterized it as one of the most advanced server-side malware campaigns for financial gain.
"Ebury actors have been pursuing monetization activities [...],]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[It's Time to Master the Lift & Shift: Migrating from VMware vSphere to Microsoft Azure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/its-time-to-master-lift-shift-migrating.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/its-time-to-master-lift-shift-migrating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[While cloud adoption has been top of mind for many IT professionals for nearly a decade, it’s only in recent months, with industry changes and announcements from key players, that many recognize the time to make the move is now. It may feel like a daunting task, but tools exist to help you move your virtual machines (VMs) to a public cloud provider – like Microsoft Azure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0403 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0403/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0403/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.
 Microsoft indique …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0402 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure Migrate (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0402/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0402/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:42:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure Migrate. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0401 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft .Net (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0401/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0401/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:42:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft .Net. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0400 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0400/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0400/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:42:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0399 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0399/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0399/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:42:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0398 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0398/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0398/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T09:42:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.
 Google a connaissance d'une exploitation active de la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4761.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0397 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0397/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0397/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T08:46:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dutch Court Sentences Tornado Cash Co-Founder to 5 Years in Prison for Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/dutch-court-sentences-tornado-cash-co.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/dutch-court-sentences-tornado-cash-co.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T08:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Dutch court on Tuesday sentenced one of the co-founders of the now-sanctioned Tornado Cash cryptocurrency mixer service to 5 years and 4 months in prison.
While the name of the defendant was redacted in the verdict, it's known that Alexey Pertsev, a 31-year-old Russian national, has been awaiting trial in the Netherlands on money laundering charges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Patches 61 Flaws, Including Two Actively Exploited Zero-Days]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-patches-61-flaws-including.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/microsoft-patches-61-flaws-including.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has addressed a total of 61 new security flaws in its software as part of its Patch Tuesday updates for May 2024, including two zero-days which have been actively exploited in the wild.
Of the 61 flaws, one is rated Critical, 59 are rated Important, and one is rated Moderate in severity. This is in addition to 30 vulnerabilities&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0396 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0396/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0396/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T07:05:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Azure Migrate (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0402</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0402"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Azure Migrate. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0408</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0408"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0404</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0404"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0396</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0396"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0405</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0405"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0398</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0398"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google a connaissance d'une exploitation active de la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4761.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0406</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0406"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0397</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0397"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0400</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0400"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0399</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0399"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0403</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0403"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que la...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft .Net (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0401</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0401"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft .Net. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans LibreOffice (15 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0407</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0407"/>
        <updated>2024-05-15T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Libreoffice. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Patches Severe Security Flaws in Workstation and Fusion Products]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/vmware-patches-severe-security-flaws-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/vmware-patches-severe-security-flaws-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T15:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security flaws have been disclosed in VMware Workstation and Fusion products that could be exploited by threat actors to access sensitive information, trigger a denial-of-service (DoS) condition, and execute code under certain circumstances.
The four vulnerabilities impact Workstation versions 17.x and Fusion versions 13.x, with fixes available in version 17.5.2 and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Chrome Zero-Day Vulnerability CVE-2024-4761 Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/new-chrome-zero-day-vulnerability-cve.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T13:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Monday shipped emergency fixes to address a new zero-day flaw in the Chrome web browser that has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-4761, is an out-of-bounds write bug impacting the V8 JavaScript and WebAssembly engine. It was reported anonymously on May 9, 2024.
Out-of-bounds write bugs could be typically]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0395 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0395/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0395/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:59:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0394 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Typo3 (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0394/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0394/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:42:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Typo3. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0393 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0393/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0393/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:24:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws in Cacti Framework Could Let Attackers Execute Malicious Code]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-flaws-in-cacti-framework-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/critical-flaws-in-cacti-framework-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of the Cacti open-source network monitoring and fault management framework have addressed a dozen security flaws, including two critical issues that could lead to the execution of arbitrary code.
The most severe of the vulnerabilities are listed below -

CVE-2024-25641 (CVSS score: 9.1) - An arbitrary file write vulnerability in the "Package Import" feature that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Mistakes Organizations Make When Deploying Advanced Authentication]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/6-mistakes-organizations-make-when.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/6-mistakes-organizations-make-when.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Deploying advanced authentication measures is key to helping organizations address their weakest cybersecurity link: their human users. Having some form of 2-factor authentication in place is a great start, but many organizations may not yet be in that spot or have the needed level of authentication sophistication to adequately safeguard organizational data. When deploying]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ongoing Campaign Bombarded Enterprises with Spam Emails and Phone Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ongoing-campaign-bombarded-enterprises.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/ongoing-campaign-bombarded-enterprises.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered an ongoing social engineering campaign that bombards enterprises with spam emails with the goal of obtaining initial access to their environments for follow-on exploitation.
"The incident involves a threat actor overwhelming a user's email with junk and calling the user, offering assistance," Rapid7 researchers Tyler McGraw, Thomas Elkins, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0392 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0392/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0392/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T07:33:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0391 : Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0391/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0391/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T07:19:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.
 Google a connaissance d'une exploitation active de la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4761.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0390 : Vulnérabilité dans StrongSwan (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0390/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0390/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T07:12:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Strongswan. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0389 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Belden (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0389/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0389/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T07:02:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Belden. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Google Launch Cross-Platform Feature to Detect Unwanted Bluetooth Tracking Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/apple-and-google-launch-cross-platform.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/apple-and-google-launch-cross-platform.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T05:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple and Google on Monday officially announced the rollout of a new feature that notifies users across both iOS and Android if a Bluetooth tracking device is being used to stealthily keep tabs on them without their knowledge or consent.
"This will help mitigate the misuse of devices designed to help keep track of belongings," the companies said in a joint statement, adding it aims to address "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0392</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0392"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0395</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0395"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Belden (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0389</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0389"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Belden. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0391</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0391"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur. Google a connaissance d'une exploitation active de la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-4761.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Typo3 (14 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0394</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0394"/>
        <updated>2024-05-14T02:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Typo3. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MITRE Unveils EMB3D: A Threat-Modeling Framework for Embedded Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/mitre-unveils-emb3d-threat-modeling.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/mitre-unveils-emb3d-threat-modeling.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T14:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The MITRE Corporation has officially made available a new threat-modeling framework called EMB3D for makers of embedded devices used in critical infrastructure environments.

"The model provides a cultivated knowledge base of cyber threats to embedded devices, providing a common understanding of these threats with the security mechanisms required to mitigate them," the non-profit said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 Browser Security Report Uncovers How Every Web Session Could be a Security Minefield]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-2024-browser-security-report.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/the-2024-browser-security-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T12:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With the browser becoming the most prevalent workspace in the enterprise, it is also turning into a popular attack vector for cyber attackers. From account takeovers to malicious extensions to phishing attacks, the browser is a means for stealing sensitive data and accessing organizational systems.
Security leaders who are planning their security architecture]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0388 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (13 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0388/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0388/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:55:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF), un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0387 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans VMware Avi Load Balancer (13 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0387/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0387/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans VMware Avi Load Balancer. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-021 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-021 (13 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-021/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-021/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T11:19:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SHQ Response Platform and Risk Centre to Enable Management and Analysts Alike]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/shq-response-platform-and-risk-centre.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/shq-response-platform-and-risk-centre.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the last decade, there has been a growing disconnect between front-line analysts and senior management in IT and Cybersecurity. Well-documented challenges facing modern analysts revolve around a high volume of alerts, false positives, poor visibility of technical environments, and analysts spending too much time on manual tasks.
The Impact of Alert Fatigue and False Positives 
Analysts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Severe Vulnerabilities in Cinterion Cellular Modems Pose Risks to Various Industries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/severe-vulnerabilities-in-cinterion.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/severe-vulnerabilities-in-cinterion.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed multiple security flaws in Cinterion cellular modems that could be potentially exploited by threat actors to access sensitive information and achieve code execution.
"These vulnerabilities include critical flaws that permit remote code execution and unauthorized privilege escalation, posing substantial risks to integral communication networks and IoT]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Black Basta Ransomware Strikes 500+ Entities Across North America, Europe, and Australia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/black-basta-ransomware-strikes-500.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/black-basta-ransomware-strikes-500.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T10:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Black Basta ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation has targeted more than 500 private industry and critical infrastructure entities in North America, Europe, and Australia since its emergence in April 2022.
In a joint advisory published by the Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA), the Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI), the Department of Health and Human Services (HHS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0386 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (13 mai 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0386/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0386/"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T07:34:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Python Package Hides Sliver C2 Framework in Fake Requests Library Logo]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/malicious-python-package-hides-sliver.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/malicious-python-package-hides-sliver.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-13T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified a malicious Python package that purports to be an offshoot of the popular requests library and has been found concealing a Golang-version of the Sliver command-and-control (C2) framework within a PNG image of the project's logo. 
The package employing this steganographic trickery is requests-darwin-lite, which has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FIN7 Hacker Group Leverages Malicious Google Ads to Deliver NetSupport RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fin7-hacker-group-leverages-malicious.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/05/fin7-hacker-group-leverages-malicious.html"/>
        <updated>2024-05-11T07:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The financially motivated threat actor known as FIN7 has been observed leveraging malicious Google ads spoofing legitimate brands as a means to deliver MSIX installers that culminate in the deployment of NetSupport RAT.
"The threat actors used malicious websites to impersonate well-known brands, including AnyDesk, WinSCP, BlackRock, Asana, Concur, The Wall]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>