<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-02-26T05:27:19.276Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware Group Resurfaces After Law Enforcement Takedown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomware-group-resurfaces.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomware-group-resurfaces.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-26T04:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the LockBit ransomware operation have resurfaced on the dark web using new infrastructure, days after an international law enforcement exercise seized control of its servers.
To that end, the notorious group has moved its data leak portal to a new .onion address on the TOR network, listing 12 new victims as of writing.
The administrator behind LockBit, in a&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Authorities Claim LockBit Admin "LockBitSupp" Has Engaged with Law Enforcement]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/authorities-claim-lockbit-admin.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/authorities-claim-lockbit-admin.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-25T08:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[LockBitSupp, the individual(s) behind the persona representing the LockBit ransomware service on cybercrime forums such as Exploit and XSS, "has engaged with law enforcement," authorities said.
The development comes following the takedown of the prolific ransomware-as-a-service (RaaS) operation as part of a coordinated international operation codenamed Cronos. Over 14,000 rogue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Expands Free Logging Capabilities for all U.S. Federal Agencies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-expands-free-logging.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-expands-free-logging.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-24T11:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has expanded free logging capabilities to all U.S. federal agencies using Microsoft Purview Audit irrespective of the license tier, more than six months after a China-linked cyber espionage campaign targeting two dozen organizations came to light.
"Microsoft will automatically enable the logs in customer accounts and increase the default log retention period from 90 days to 180 days,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Dormant PyPI Package Compromised to Spread Nova Sentinel Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/dormant-pypi-package-compromised-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/dormant-pypi-package-compromised-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T17:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A dormant package available on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository was updated nearly after two years to propagate an information stealer malware called Nova Sentinel.
The package, named django-log-tracker, was first published to PyPI in April 2022, according to software supply chain security firm Phylum, which detected an anomalous update to the library on February 21,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0164 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0164/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0164/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T13:13:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0163 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0163/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0163/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:40:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0162 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0162/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0162/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T12:27:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Releases PyRIT - A Red Teaming Tool for Generative AI]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-releases-pyrit-red-teaming.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-releases-pyrit-red-teaming.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T11:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released an open access automation framework called PyRIT (short for Python Risk Identification Tool) to proactively identify risks in generative artificial intelligence (AI) systems.
The red teaming tool is designed to "enable every organization across the globe to innovate responsibly with the latest artificial intelligence advances," Ram Shankar Siva Kumar, AI red team]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Use Tines's SOC Automation Capability Matrix]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-to-use-tiness-soc-automation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-to-use-tiness-soc-automation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Created by John Tuckner and the team at workflow and automation platform Tines, the SOC Automation Capability Matrix (SOC ACM) is a set of techniques designed to help security operations teams understand their automation capabilities and respond more effectively to incidents. 
A customizable, vendor-agnostic tool featuring lists of automation opportunities, it's been shared]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0161 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits SonicWall (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0161/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0161/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T10:16:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans la gamme de produits SonicWall SMA100. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0160 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ruby on Rails (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0160/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0160/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T09:35:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ruby on Rails. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0159 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (23 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0159/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0159/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T07:45:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Detail Apple's Recent Zero-Click Shortcuts Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/researchers-detail-apples-recent-zero.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/researchers-detail-apples-recent-zero.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T05:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a now-patched high-severity security flaw in Apple's Shortcuts app that could permit a shortcut to access sensitive information on the device without users' consent.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23204 (CVSS score: 7.5), was addressed by Apple on January 22, 2024, with the release of iOS 17.3, iPadOS 17.3, macOS Sonoma 14.3, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FTC Slams Avast with $16.5 Million Fine for Selling Users' Browsing Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ftc-slams-avast-with-165-million-fine.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ftc-slams-avast-with-165-million-fine.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-23T03:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has hit antivirus vendor Avast with a $16.5 million fine over charges that the firm sold users' browsing data to advertisers after claiming its products would block online tracking.
In addition, the company has been banned from selling or licensing any web browsing data for advertising purposes. It will also have to notify users whose browsing data was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Unveils PQ3 Protocol - Post-Quantum Encryption for iMessage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/apple-unveils-pq3-protocol-post-quantum.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/apple-unveils-pq3-protocol-post-quantum.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T16:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has announced a new post-quantum cryptographic protocol called PQ3 that it said will be integrated into iMessage to secure the messaging platform against future attacks arising from the threat of a practical quantum computer.
"With compromise-resilient encryption and extensive defenses against even highly sophisticated quantum attacks, PQ3 is the first messaging protocol to reach]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0158 : Vulnérabilité dans Kaspersky Endpoint Security (22 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0158/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0158/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T12:39:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Kaspersky Endpoint Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Weaponizing Open-Source SSH-Snake Tool for Network Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybercriminals-weaponizing-open-source.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybercriminals-weaponizing-open-source.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently open-sourced network mapping tool called SSH-Snake has been repurposed by threat actors to conduct malicious activities.
"SSH-Snake is a self-modifying worm that leverages SSH credentials discovered on a compromised system to start spreading itself throughout the network," Sysdig researcher Miguel Hernández said.
"The worm automatically searches through known credential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Age of Hacktivism]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/a-new-age-of-hacktivism.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/a-new-age-of-hacktivism.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T10:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the past 2 years, we have observed a significant surge in hacktivism activity due to ongoing wars and geopolitical conflicts in various regions. Since the war against Ukraine began, we have witnessed a notable mobilization of non-state and state-backed actors alike, forming new groups or joining existing hacker collectives. 
We understand hacktivism as a form of computer hacking that is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Government Software Backdoored to Deploy Konni RAT Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-government-software-backdoored.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-government-software-backdoored.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An installer for a tool likely used by the Russian Consular Department of the Ministry of Foreign Affairs (MID) has been backdoored to deliver a remote access trojan called Konni RAT (aka UpDog).
The findings come from German cybersecurity company DCSO, which linked the activity as originating from the Democratic People's Republic of Korea (DPRK)-nexus actors targeting Russia.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0157 : Vulnérabilité dans PostgreSQL JDBC (22 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0157/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0157/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T09:06:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans PostgreSQL JDBC. Elles permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0156 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (22 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0156/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0156/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T08:23:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0155 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Gitlab (22 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0155/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0155/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T08:11:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Gitlab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0154 : Vulnérabilité dans Spring Framework (22 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0154/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0154/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T08:00:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Framework. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Offers $15 Million Bounty to Hunt Down LockBit Ransomware Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-offers-15-million-bounty-to-hunt.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-offers-15-million-bounty-to-hunt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-22T05:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. State Department has announced monetary rewards of up to $15 million for information that could lead to the identification of key leaders within the LockBit ransomware group and the arrest of any individual participating in the operation.
"Since January 2020, LockBit actors have executed over 2,000 attacks against victims in the United States, and around the world, causing costly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Wi-Fi Vulnerabilities Expose Android and Linux Devices to Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-wi-fi-vulnerabilities-expose.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-wi-fi-vulnerabilities-expose.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T16:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified two authentication bypass flaws in open-source Wi-Fi software found in Android, Linux, and ChromeOS devices that could trick users into joining a malicious clone of a legitimate network or allow an attacker to join a trusted network without a password.
The vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2023-52160 and CVE-2023-52161, have been discovered following a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mustang Panda Targets Asia with Advanced PlugX Variant DOPLUGS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/mustang-panda-targets-asia-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/mustang-panda-targets-asia-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked threat actor known as Mustang Panda has targeted various Asian countries using a variant of the PlugX (aka Korplug) backdoor dubbed DOPLUGS.
"The piece of customized PlugX malware is dissimilar to the general type of the PlugX malware that contains a completed backdoor command module, and that the former is only used for downloading the latter," Trend Micro researchers Sunny Lu]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[6 Ways to Simplify SaaS Identity Governance]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/6-ways-to-simplify-saas-identity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/6-ways-to-simplify-saas-identity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With SaaS applications now making up the vast majority of technology used by employees in most organizations, tasks related to identity governance need to happen across a myriad of individual SaaS apps. This presents a huge challenge for centralized IT teams who are ultimately held responsible for managing and securing app access, but can’t possibly become experts in the nuances of the native]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity for Healthcare—Diagnosing the Threat Landscape and Prescribing Solutions for Recovery]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybersecurity-for-healthcarediagnosing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybersecurity-for-healthcarediagnosing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T09:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[On Thanksgiving Day 2023, while many Americans were celebrating, hospitals across the U.S. were doing quite the opposite. Systems were failing. Ambulances were diverted. Care was impaired. Hospitals in three states were hit by a ransomware attack, and in that moment, the real-world repercussions came to light—it wasn’t just computer networks that were brought to a halt, but actual patient]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0153 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (21 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0153/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0153/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T08:08:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0152 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (21 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0152/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0152/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T08:03:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0151 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Joomla! (21 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0151/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0151/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Joomla!. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'VietCredCare' Stealer Targeting Facebook Advertisers in Vietnam]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-vietcredcare-stealer-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-vietcredcare-stealer-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T08:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook advertisers in Vietnam are the target of a previously unknown information stealer dubbed VietCredCare at least since August 2022.
The malware is “notable for its ability to automatically filter out Facebook session cookies and credentials stolen from compromised devices, and assess whether these accounts manage business profiles and if they maintain a positive Meta ad credit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0150 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (21 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0150/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0150/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T07:46:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Signal Introduces Usernames, Allowing Users to Keep Their Phone Numbers Private]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/signal-introduces-usernames-allowing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/signal-introduces-usernames-allowing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T07:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[End-to-end encrypted (E2EE) messaging app Signal said it’s piloting a new feature that allows users to create unique usernames (not to be confused with profile names) and keep the phone numbers away from prying eyes.
“If you use Signal, your phone number will no longer be visible to everyone you chat with by default,” Signal’s Randall Sarafa said. “People who have your number saved in their]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Target Ukraine with Disinformation and Credential-Harvesting Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-hackers-target-ukraine-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-hackers-target-ukraine-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unearthed a new influence operation targeting Ukraine that leverages spam emails to propagate war-related disinformation.
The activity has been linked to Russia-aligned threat actors by Slovak cybersecurity company ESET, which also identified a spear-phishing campaign aimed at a Ukrainian defense company in October 2023 and a European Union agency in November 2023]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Alert: Uninstall EAP Now - Critical Flaw Puts Active Directory at Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/vmware-alert-uninstall-eap-now-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/vmware-alert-uninstall-eap-now-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-21T05:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware is urging users to uninstall the deprecated Enhanced Authentication Plugin (EAP) following the discovery of a critical security flaw.
Tracked as CVE-2024-22245 (CVSS score: 9.6), the vulnerability has been described as an arbitrary authentication relay bug.
"A malicious actor could trick a target domain user with EAP installed in their web browser into requesting and relaying]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Migo Malware Targeting Redis Servers for Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-migo-malware-targeting-redis.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-migo-malware-targeting-redis.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T15:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel malware campaign has been observed targeting Redis servers for initial access with the ultimate goal of mining cryptocurrency on compromised Linux hosts.
"This particular campaign involves the use of a number of novel system weakening techniques against the data store itself," Cado security researcher Matt Muir said in a technical report.
The cryptojacking attack is facilitated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware Operation Shut Down; Criminals Arrested; Decryption Keys Released]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomware-operation-shut-down.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomware-operation-shut-down.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. National Crime Agency (NCA) on Tuesday confirmed that it obtained LockBit's source code as well as intelligence pertaining to its activities and their affiliates as part of a dedicated task force called Operation Cronos.
"Some of the data on LockBit's systems belonged to victims who had paid a ransom to the threat actors, evidencing that even when a ransom is paid, it does not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malicious PyPI Packages Caught Using Covert Side-Loading Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-malicious-pypi-packages-caught.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-malicious-pypi-packages-caught.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T12:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered two malicious packages on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that were found leveraging a technique called DLL side-loading to circumvent detection by security software and run malicious code.
The packages, named NP6HelperHttptest and NP6HelperHttper, were each downloaded 537 and 166 times, respectively,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS Compliance through the NIST Cybersecurity Framework]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/saas-compliance-through-nist.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/saas-compliance-through-nist.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The US National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) cybersecurity framework is one of the world's most important guidelines for securing networks. It can be applied to any number of applications, including SaaS. 
One of the challenges facing those tasked with securing SaaS applications is the different settings found in each application. It makes it difficult to develop a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Learn How to Build an Incident Response Playbook Against Scattered Spider in Real-Time]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/learn-how-to-build-incident-response.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/learn-how-to-build-incident-response.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the tumultuous landscape of cybersecurity, the year 2023 left an indelible mark with the brazen exploits of the Scattered Spider threat group. Their attacks targeted the nerve centers of major financial and insurance institutions, culminating in what stands as one of the most impactful ransomware assaults in recent memory. 
When organizations have no response plan in place for such an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Report Reveals North Korean Hackers Targeting Defense Firms Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-report-reveals-north-korean-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-report-reveals-north-korean-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korean state-sponsored threat actors have been attributed to a cyber espionage campaign targeting the defense sector across the world.
In a joint advisory published by Germany's Federal Office for the Protection of the Constitution (BfV) and South Korea's National Intelligence Service (NIS), the agencies said the goal of the attacks is to plunder advanced defense technologies in a "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaws Found in ConnectWise ScreenConnect Software  - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-flaws-found-in-connectwise.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-flaws-found-in-connectwise.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[ConnectWise has released software updates to address two security flaws in its ScreenConnect remote desktop and access software, including a critical bug that could enable remote code execution on affected systems.
The vulnerabilities, which currently lack CVE identifiers, are listed below -

Authentication bypass using an alternate path or channel (CVSS score: 10.0)
Improper limitation of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0149 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (20 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0149/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0149/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T09:38:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Bricks Theme Under Active Attack: Critical Flaw Impacts 25,000+ Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/wordpress-bricks-theme-under-active.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/wordpress-bricks-theme-under-active.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T09:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw in the Bricks theme for WordPress is being actively exploited by threat actors to run arbitrary PHP code on susceptible installations.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-25600 (CVSS score: 9.8), enables unauthenticated attackers to achieve remote code execution. It impacts all versions of the Bricks up to and including 1.9.6.
It has been addressed by the theme developers in&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0148 : Vulnérabilité dans Kaspersky Anti Targeted Attack (20 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0148/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0148/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T07:42:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Kaspersky Anti Targeted Attack. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran and Hezbollah Hackers Launch Attacks to Influence Israel-Hamas Narrative]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iran-and-hezbollah-hackers-launch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iran-and-hezbollah-hackers-launch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers backed by Iran and Hezbollah staged cyber attacks designed to undercut public support for the Israel-Hamas war after October 2023.
This includes destructive attacks against key Israeli organizations, hack-and-leak operations targeting entities in Israel and the U.S., phishing campaigns designed to steal intelligence, and information operations to turn public opinion against Israel.
Iran]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware's Darknet Domains Seized in Global Law Enforcement Raid]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomwares-darknet-domains.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lockbit-ransomwares-darknet-domains.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-20T05:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An international law enforcement operation has led to the seizure of multiple darknet domains operated by LockBit, one of the most prolific ransomware groups, marking the latest in a long list of digital takedowns.
While the full extent of the effort, codenamed Operation Cronos, is presently unknown, visiting the group's .onion website displays a seizure banner containing the message "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0147 : Vulnérabilité dans Spring Security (19 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0147/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0147/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T13:15:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Warns of 8 Spyware Firms Targeting iOS, Android, and Windows Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/meta-warns-of-8-spyware-firms-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/meta-warns-of-8-spyware-firms-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T13:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Platforms said it took a series of steps to curtail malicious activity from eight different firms based in Italy, Spain, and the United Arab Emirates (U.A.E.) operating in the surveillance-for-hire industry.
The findings are part of its Adversarial Threat Report for the fourth quarter of 2023. The spyware targeted iOS, Android, and Windows devices.
"Their various malware included]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-009 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-009 (19 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-009/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-009/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T12:31:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Achieve the Best Risk-Based Alerting (Bye-Bye SIEM)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/bye-bye-siem-hello-risk-based-alerting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/bye-bye-siem-hello-risk-based-alerting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that Network Detection and Response (NDR) has become the most effective technology to detect cyber threats? In contrast to SIEM, NDR offers adaptive cybersecurity with reduced false alerts and efficient threat response.
Are you aware of Network Detection and Response (NDR) and how it’s become the most effective technology to detect cyber threats? 
NDR massively]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Anatsa Android Trojan Bypasses Google Play Security, Expands Reach to New Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/anatsa-android-trojan-bypasses-google.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/anatsa-android-trojan-bypasses-google.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T10:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Android banking trojan known as Anatsa has expanded its focus to include Slovakia, Slovenia, and Czechia as part of a new campaign observed in November 2023.
"Some of the droppers in the campaign successfully exploited the accessibility service, despite Google Play's enhanced detection and protection mechanisms," ThreatFabric said in a report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-Linked Hackers Breach 80+ Organizations via Roundcube Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-linked-hackers-breach-80.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-linked-hackers-breach-80.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T05:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors operating with interests aligned to Belarus and Russia have been linked to a new cyber espionage campaign that likely exploited cross-site scripting (XSS) vulnerabilities in Roundcube webmail servers to target over 80 organizations.
These entities are primarily located in Georgia, Poland, and Ukraine, according to Recorded Future, which attributed the intrusion set to a threat]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Target Middle East Policy Experts with New BASICSTAR Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iranian-hackers-target-middle-east.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iranian-hackers-target-middle-east.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-19T04:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iranian-origin threat actor known as Charming Kitten has been linked to a new set of attacks aimed at Middle East policy experts with a new backdoor called BASICSTAR by creating a fake webinar portal.
Charming Kitten, also called APT35, CharmingCypress, Mint Sandstorm, TA453, and Yellow Garuda, has a history of orchestrating a wide range of social engineering campaigns that cast a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI's Most-Wanted Zeus and IcedID Malware Mastermind Pleads Guilty]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fbis-most-wanted-zeus-and-icedid.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fbis-most-wanted-zeus-and-icedid.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-18T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Ukrainian national has pleaded guilty in the U.S. to his role in two different malware schemes, Zeus and IcedID, between May 2009 and February 2021.
Vyacheslav Igorevich Penchukov (aka Vyacheslav Igoravich Andreev, father, and tank), 37, was arrested by Swiss authorities in October 2022 and extradited to the U.S. last year. He was added to the FBI's most-wanted list in 2012.
The U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Businesses Can Safeguard Their Communication Channels Against Hackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-businesses-can-safeguard-their.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-businesses-can-safeguard-their.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T08:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Efficient communication is a cornerstone of business success. Internally, making sure your team communicates seamlessly helps you avoid friction losses, misunderstandings, delays, and overlaps. Externally, frustration-free customer communication is directly correlated to a positive customer experience and higher satisfaction. 
However, business communication channels are also a major target]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Open Sources Magika: AI-Powered File Identification Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/google-open-sources-magika-ai-powered.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/google-open-sources-magika-ai-powered.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-17T07:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's open-sourcing Magika, an artificial intelligence (AI)-powered tool to identify file types, to help defenders accurately detect binary and textual file types.
"Magika outperforms conventional file identification methods providing an overall 30% accuracy boost and up to 95% higher precision on traditionally hard to identify, but potentially problematic content]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warning: Akira Ransomware Exploiting Cisco ASA/FTD Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-warning-akira-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-warning-akira-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T15:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a now-patched security flaw impacting Cisco Adaptive Security Appliance (ASA) and Firepower Threat Defense (FTD) software to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, following reports that it's being likely exploited in Akira ransomware attacks.
The vulnerability in question is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RustDoor macOS Backdoor Targets Cryptocurrency Firms with Fake Job Offers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/rustdoor-macos-backdoor-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/rustdoor-macos-backdoor-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T13:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Several companies operating in the cryptocurrency sector are the target of a newly discovered Apple macOS backdoor codenamed RustDoor.
RustDoor was first documented by Bitdefender last week, describing it as a Rust-based malware capable of harvesting and uploading files, as well as gathering information about the infected machines. It's distributed by masquerading itself as a Visual]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0146 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0146/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0146/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:45:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0145 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0145/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0145/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:43:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0144 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0144/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0144/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0143 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux Ubuntu (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0143/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0143/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:34:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0142 : Vulnérabilité dans NetApp SnapCenter (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0142/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0142/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T12:10:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans NetApp SnapCenter. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why We Must Democratize Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-we-must-democratize-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-we-must-democratize-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T10:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With breaches making the headlines on an almost weekly basis, the cybersecurity challenges we face are becoming visible not only to large enterprises, who have built security capabilities over the years, but also to small to medium businesses and the broader public. While this is creating greater awareness among smaller businesses of the need to improve their security posture, SMBs are often]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious 'SNS Sender' Script Abuses AWS for Bulk Smishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/malicious-sns-sender-script-abuses-aws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/malicious-sns-sender-script-abuses-aws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A malicious Python script known as SNS Sender is being advertised as a way for threat actors to send bulk smishing messages by abusing Amazon Web Services (AWS) Simple Notification Service (SNS).
The SMS phishing messages are designed to propagate malicious links that are designed to capture victims' personally identifiable information (PII) and payment card details, SentinelOne]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0141 : Vulnérabilité dans Liferay (16 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0141/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0141/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T09:45:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Liferay. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. State Government Network Breached via Former Employee's Account]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-state-government-network-breached.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-state-government-network-breached.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has revealed that an unnamed state government organization's network environment was compromised via an administrator account belonging to a former employee.
"This allowed the threat actor to successfully authenticate to an internal virtual private network (VPN) access point," the agency said in a joint advisory published]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Government Disrupts Russian-Linked Botnet Engaged in Cyber Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-government-disrupts-russian-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-government-disrupts-russian-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-16T06:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Thursday said it disrupted a botnet comprising hundreds of small office and home office (SOHO) routers in the country that was put to use by the Russia-linked APT28 actor to conceal its malicious activities.
"These crimes included vast spear-phishing and similar credential harvesting campaigns against targets of intelligence interest to the Russian government, such as U.S.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ALE-005 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Outlook (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-005/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-005/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T16:32:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 13 février 2024, Microsoft a publié un correctif pour la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-21413 affectant le produit Outlook pour Windows.
 Elle permet à un attaquant non authentifié de divulguer le condensat …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Turla Hackers Target Polish NGOs with New TinyTurla-NG Backdoor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-turla-hackers-target-polish.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-turla-hackers-target-polish.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russia-linked threat actor known as Turla has been observed using a new backdoor called TinyTurla-NG as part of a three-month-long campaign targeting Polish non-governmental organizations in December 2023.
"TinyTurla-NG, just like TinyTurla, is a small 'last chance' backdoor that is left behind to be used when all other unauthorized access/backdoor mechanisms have failed or been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Pulse Secure Found Using 11-Year-Old Linux Version and Outdated Libraries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ivanti-pulse-secure-found-using-11-year.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ivanti-pulse-secure-found-using-11-year.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A reverse engineering of the firmware running on Ivanti Pulse Secure appliances has revealed numerous weaknesses, once again underscoring the challenge of securing software supply chains.
Eclypsiusm, which acquired firmware version 9.1.18.2-24467.1 as part of the process, said the base operating system used by the Utah-based software company for the device is CentOS 6.4.
"Pulse Secure runs an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0140 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Liferay (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0140/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0140/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T13:49:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Liferay. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0139 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0139/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0139/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T12:44:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0138 : Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0138/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0138/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T12:36:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Stormshield Network Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0137 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits F5 (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0137/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0137/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T12:31:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits F5. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Nation-State Actors Target Your Business: New Research Exposes Major SaaS Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-nation-state-actors-target-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-nation-state-actors-target-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[With many of the highly publicized 2023 cyber attacks revolving around one or more SaaS applications, SaaS has become a cause for genuine concern in many boardroom discussions. More so than ever, considering that GenAI applications are, in fact, SaaS applications.
Wing Security (Wing), a SaaS security company, conducted an analysis of 493 SaaS-using companies in Q4 of 2023. Their study]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0136 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits ESET (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0136/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0136/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T09:37:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits ESET. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Using Deepfakes in Advanced Mobile Banking Malware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-using-deepfakes-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-using-deepfakes-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese-speaking threat actor codenamed GoldFactory has been attributed to the development of highly sophisticated banking trojans, including a previously undocumented iOS malware called GoldPickaxe that's capable of harvesting identity documents, facial recognition data, and intercepting SMS.
"The GoldPickaxe family is available for both iOS and Android platforms,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0135 : Vulnérabilité dans Squid (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0135/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0135/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T09:28:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Squid. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0134 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0134/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0134/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T09:10:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0133 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nginx (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0133/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0133/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T08:59:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nginx. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0132 : Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (15 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0132/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0132/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T08:02:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Exchange Server Flaw (CVE-2024-21410) Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-exchange-server-flaw-cve-2024.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-exchange-server-flaw-cve-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-15T05:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Wednesday acknowledged that a newly disclosed critical security flaw in Exchange Server has been actively exploited in the wild, a day after it released fixes for the vulnerability as part of its Patch Tuesday updates.
Tracked as CVE-2024-21410 (CVSS score: 9.8), the issue has been described as a case of privilege escalation impacting the Exchange Server.
"An attacker]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0131 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0131/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0131/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:00:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans les produits Microsoft. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service, une élévation de privilèges, une usurpation d'identité et une exécution de …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0130 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0130/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0130/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:00:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une usurpation d'identité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0129 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0129/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0129/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:00:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0128 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0128/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0128/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:00:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Windows. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la fonctionnalité de sécurité, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un déni de service, une élévation de privilèges, …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0127 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0127/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0127/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T16:00:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft, OpenAI Warn of Nation-State Hackers Weaponizing AI for Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-openai-warn-of-nation-state.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-openai-warn-of-nation-state.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-state actors associated with Russia, North Korea, Iran, and China are experimenting with artificial intelligence (AI) and large language models (LLMs) to complement their ongoing cyber attack operations.
The findings come from a report published by Microsoft in collaboration with OpenAI, both of which said they disrupted efforts made by five state-affiliated actors that used its]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0126 : Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0126/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0126/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T13:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0125 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans SAP (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0125/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0125/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T13:26:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ubuntu 'command-not-found' Tool Could Trick Users into Installing Rogue Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ubuntu-command-not-found-tool-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ubuntu-command-not-found-tool-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T13:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have found that it's possible for threat actors to exploit a well-known utility called command-not-found to recommend their own rogue packages and compromise systems running Ubuntu operating system.
"While 'command-not-found' serves as a convenient tool for suggesting installations for uninstalled commands, it can be inadvertently manipulated by attackers through the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Tactics FinServ Institutions Can Bank On in 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybersecurity-tactics-finserv.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cybersecurity-tactics-finserv.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T11:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The landscape of cybersecurity in financial services is undergoing a rapid transformation. Cybercriminals are exploiting advanced technologies and methodologies, making traditional security measures obsolete. The challenges are compounded for community banks that must safeguard sensitive financial data against the same level of sophisticated threats as larger institutions, but often with more]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bumblebee Malware Returns with New Tricks, Targeting U.S. Businesses]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/bumblebee-malware-returns-with-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/bumblebee-malware-returns-with-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T11:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The infamous malware loader and initial access broker known as Bumblebee has resurfaced after a four-month absence as part of a new phishing campaign observed in February 2024.
Enterprise security firm Proofpoint said the activity targets organizations in the U.S. with voicemail-themed lures containing links to OneDrive URLs.
"The URLs led to a Word file with names such as "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0124 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0124/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0124/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T10:38:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0123 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (14 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0123/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0123/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T09:14:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et injection de code indirecte à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkMe Malware Targets Traders Using Microsoft SmartScreen Zero-Day Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/darkme-malware-targets-traders-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/darkme-malware-targets-traders-using.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A newly disclosed security flaw in the Microsoft Defender SmartScreen has been exploited as a zero-day by an advanced persistent threat actor called Water Hydra (aka DarkCasino) targeting financial market traders.
Trend Micro, which began tracking the campaign in late December 2023, said it entails the exploitation of CVE-2024-21412, a security bypass vulnerability related to Internet]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Rolls Out Patches for 73 Flaws, Including 2 Windows Zero-Days]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-rolls-out-patches-for-73.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-rolls-out-patches-for-73.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-14T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has released patches to address 73 security flaws spanning its software lineup as part of its Patch Tuesday updates for February 2024, including two zero-days that have come under active exploitation.
Of the 73 vulnerabilities, 5 are rated Critical, 65 are rated Important, and three and rated Moderate in severity. This is in addition to 24 flaws that have been fixed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0122 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Bind (13 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0122/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0122/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T17:07:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Bind. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Glupteba Botnet Evades Detection with Undocumented UEFI Bootkit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/glupteba-botnet-evades-detection-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/glupteba-botnet-evades-detection-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Glupteba botnet has been found to incorporate a previously undocumented Unified Extensible Firmware Interface (UEFI) bootkit feature, adding another layer of sophistication and stealth to the malware.
"This bootkit can intervene and control the [operating system] boot process, enabling Glupteba to hide itself and create a stealthy persistence that can be extremely difficult to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PikaBot Resurfaces with Streamlined Code and Deceptive Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/pikabot-resurfaces-with-streamlined.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/pikabot-resurfaces-with-streamlined.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T14:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the PikaBot malware have made significant changes to the malware in what has been described as a case of "devolution."
"Although it appears to be in a new development cycle and testing phase, the developers have reduced the complexity of the code by removing advanced obfuscation techniques and changing the network communications," Zscaler ThreatLabz researcher Nikolaos]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0121 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Typo3 (13 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0121/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0121/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T13:12:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Typo3. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0120 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider (13 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0120/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0120/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0119 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (13 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0119/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0119/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T12:13:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Midnight Blizzard and Cloudflare-Atlassian Cybersecurity Incidents: What to Know]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/midnight-blizzard-and-cloudflare.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/midnight-blizzard-and-cloudflare.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T11:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Midnight Blizzard and Cloudflare-Atlassian cybersecurity incidents raised alarms about the vulnerabilities inherent in major SaaS platforms. These incidents illustrate the stakes involved in SaaS breaches — safeguarding the integrity of SaaS apps and their sensitive data is critical but is not easy. Common threat vectors such as sophisticated spear-phishing, misconfigurations and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0118 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (13 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0118/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0118/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Vulnerability Exploited to Install 'DSLog' Backdoor on 670+ IT Infrastructures]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ivanti-vulnerability-exploited-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/ivanti-vulnerability-exploited-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are leveraging a recently disclosed security flaw impacting Ivanti Connect Secure, Policy Secure, and ZTA gateways to deploy a backdoor codenamed DSLog on susceptible devices.
That's according to findings from Orange Cyberdefense, which said it observed the exploitation of CVE-2024-21893 within hours of the public release of the proof-the-concept (PoC) code.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: CISA Warns of Active 'Roundcube' Email Attacks - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/alert-cisa-warns-of-active-roundcube.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/alert-cisa-warns-of-active-roundcube.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-13T04:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday added a medium-severity security flaw impacting Roundcube email software to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2023-43770 (CVSS score: 6.1), relates to a cross-site scripting (XSS) flaw that stems from the handling of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-008 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-008 (12 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-008/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-008/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T14:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0117 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans SolarWinds Platform (12 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0117/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0117/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T13:13:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SolarWinds Platform. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rhysida Ransomware Cracked, Free Decryption Tool Released]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/rhysida-ransomware-cracked-free.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/rhysida-ransomware-cracked-free.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T13:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered an "implementation vulnerability" that has made it possible to reconstruct encryption keys and decrypt data locked by Rhysida ransomware.
The findings were published last week by a group of researchers from Kookmin University and the Korea Internet and Security Agency (KISA).
"Through a comprehensive analysis of Rhysida Ransomware, we identified an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Ways Hackers use Social Engineering to Bypass MFA]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/4-ways-hackers-use-social-engineering.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/4-ways-hackers-use-social-engineering.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T11:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When it comes to access security, one recommendation stands out above the rest: multi-factor authentication (MFA). With passwords alone being simple work for hackers, MFA provides an essential layer of protection against breaches. However, it's important to remember that MFA isn't foolproof. It can be bypassed, and it often is. 
If a password is compromised, there are several options]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA and OpenSSF Release Framework for Package Repository Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-and-openssf-release-framework-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-and-openssf-release-framework-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) announced that it's partnering with the Open Source Security Foundation (OpenSSF) Securing Software Repositories Working Group to publish a new framework to secure package repositories.
Called the Principles for Package Repository Security, the framework aims to establish a set of foundational rules for package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Are Compromised Identities the Nightmare to IR Speed and Efficiency?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-are-compromised-identities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-are-compromised-identities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T10:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Incident response (IR) is a race against time. You engage your internal or external team because there's enough evidence that something bad is happening, but you’re still blind to the scope, the impact, and the root cause. The common set of IR tools and practices provides IR teams with the ability to discover malicious files and outbound network connections. However, the identity aspect - namely]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Introduces Linux-Like 'sudo' Command to Windows 11]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-introduces-linux-like-sudo.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/microsoft-introduces-linux-like-sudo.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T05:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft said it's introducing Sudo for Windows 11 as part of an early preview version to help users execute commands with administrator privileges.
"Sudo for Windows is a new way for users to run elevated commands directly from an unelevated console session," Microsoft Product Manager Jordi Adoumie said.
"It is an ergonomic and familiar solution for users who want to elevate a command]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Offers $10 Million Bounty for Info Leading to Arrest of Hive Ransomware Leaders]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-offers-10-million-bounty-for-info.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-offers-10-million-bounty-for-info.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-12T04:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of State has announced monetary rewards of up to $10 million for information about individuals holding key positions within the Hive ransomware operation.
It is also giving away an additional $5 million for specifics that could lead to the arrest and/or conviction of any person "conspiring to participate in or attempting to participate in Hive ransomware activity."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. DoJ Dismantles Warzone RAT Infrastructure, Arrests Key Operators]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-doj-dismantles-warzone-rat.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-doj-dismantles-warzone-rat.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-11T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Justice Department (DoJ) on Friday announced the seizure of online infrastructure that was used to sell a remote access trojan (RAT) called Warzone RAT.
The domains – www.warzone[.]ws and three others – were "used to sell computer malware used by cybercriminals to secretly access and steal data from victims' computers," the DoJ said.
Alongside the takedown, the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: New Stealthy "RustDoor" Backdoor Targeting Apple macOS Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/alert-new-stealthy-rustdoor-backdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/alert-new-stealthy-rustdoor-backdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-10T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple macOS users are the target of a new Rust-based backdoor that has been operating under the radar since November 2023.
The backdoor, codenamed RustDoor by Bitdefender, has been found to impersonate an update for Microsoft Visual Studio and target both Intel and Arm architectures.
The exact initial access pathway used to propagate the implant is currently not known, although]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Raspberry Robin Malware Upgrades with Discord Spread and New Exploits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/raspberry-robin-malware-upgrades-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/raspberry-robin-malware-upgrades-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T16:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The operators of Raspberry Robin are now using two new one-day exploits to achieve local privilege escalation, even as the malware continues to be refined and improved to make it stealthier than before.
This means that "Raspberry Robin has access to an exploit seller or its authors develop the exploits themselves in a short period of time," Check Point said in a report this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0116 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0116/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0116/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T14:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[MoqHao Android Malware Evolves with Auto-Execution Capability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-variant-of-moqhao-android-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-variant-of-moqhao-android-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T13:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have identified a new variant of Android malware called MoqHao that automatically executes on infected devices without requiring any user interaction.
"Typical MoqHao requires users to install and launch the app to get their desired purpose, but this new variant requires no execution," McAfee Labs said in a report published this week. "While the app is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0115 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0115/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0115/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T13:00:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0114 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux Ubuntu (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0114/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0114/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T12:56:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0113 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0113/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0113/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T12:19:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0112 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans MISP (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0112/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0112/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T12:12:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MISP. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0111 : Vulnérabilité dans PostgreSQL (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0111/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0111/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T12:00:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans PostgreSQL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0110 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0110/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0110/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T11:55:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-on Review: Myrror Security Code-Aware and Attack-Aware SCA]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hands-on-review-myrror-security-code.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hands-on-review-myrror-security-code.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T10:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Introduction
The modern software supply chain represents an ever-evolving threat landscape, with each package added to the manifest introducing new attack vectors. To meet industry requirements, organizations must maintain a fast-paced development process while staying up-to-date with the latest security patches. However, in practice, developers often face a large amount of security work without]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Coyote Trojan Targets 61 Brazilian Banks with Nim-Powered Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-coyote-trojan-targets-61-brazilian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-coyote-trojan-targets-61-brazilian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Sixty-one banking institutions, all of them originating from Brazil, are the target of a new banking trojan called Coyote.
"This malware utilizes the Squirrel installer for distribution, leveraging Node.js and a relatively new multi-platform programming language called Nim as a loader to complete its infection," Russian cybersecurity firm Kaspersky said in a Thursday report.
What]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ALE-004 : Vulnérabilité dans Fortinet FortiOS (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-004/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-004/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T10:10:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 8 février 2024, Fortinet a publié l'avis de sécurité concernant la vulnérabilité critique CVE-2024-21762 affectant le VPN SSL de FortiOS. Cette vulnérabilité permet à un attaquant non authentifié de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0109 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Ivanti (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0109/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0109/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T08:36:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Ivanti. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0108 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (09 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0108/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0108/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T08:18:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wazuh in the Cloud Era: Navigating the Challenges of Cybersecurity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/wazuh-in-cloud-era-navigating.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/wazuh-in-cloud-era-navigating.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T07:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloud computing has innovated how organizations operate and manage IT operations, such as data storage, application deployment, networking, and overall resource management. The cloud offers scalability, adaptability, and accessibility, enabling businesses to achieve sustainable growth. However, adopting cloud technologies into your infrastructure presents various cybersecurity risks and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Stealthy Zardoor Backdoor Targets Saudi Islamic Charity Organizations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/stealthy-zardoor-backdoor-targets-saudi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/stealthy-zardoor-backdoor-targets-saudi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T06:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An unnamed Islamic non-profit organization in Saudi Arabia has been targeted as part of a stealthy cyber espionage campaign designed to drop a previously undocumented backdoor called Zardoor.
Cisco Talos, which discovered the activity in May 2023, said the campaign has likely persisted since at least March 2021, adding it has identified only one compromised target to date, although it's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet Warns of Critical FortiOS SSL VPN Vulnerability Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fortinet-warns-of-critical-fortios-ssl.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fortinet-warns-of-critical-fortios-ssl.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T05:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has disclosed a new critical security flaw in FortiOS SSL VPN that it said is likely being exploited in the wild.
The vulnerability, CVE-2024-21762 (CVSS score: 9.6), allows for the execution of arbitrary code and commands.
"A out-of-bounds write vulnerability [CWE-787] in FortiOS may allow a remote unauthenticated attacker to execute arbitrary code or command via specially]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: New Ivanti Auth Bypass Flaw Affects Connect Secure and ZTA Gateways]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/warning-new-ivanti-auth-bypass-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/warning-new-ivanti-auth-bypass-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-09T03:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has alerted customers of yet another high-severity security flaw in its Connect Secure, Policy Secure, and ZTA gateway devices that could allow attackers to bypass authentication.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2024-22024, is rated 8.3 out of 10 on the CVSS scoring system.
"An XML external entity or XXE vulnerability in the SAML component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x), Ivanti]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Operate Undetected in U.S. Critical Infrastructure for Half a Decade]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-operate-undetected-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-operate-undetected-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T13:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Wednesday said the Chinese state-sponsored hacking group known as Volt Typhoon had been embedded into some critical infrastructure networks in the country for at least five years.
Targets of the threat actor include communications, energy, transportation, and water and wastewater systems sectors in the U.S. and Guam.
"Volt Typhoon's choice of targets and pattern]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0107 : Vulnérabilité dans Elastic Kibana (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0107/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0107/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T12:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Elastic Kibana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0106 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Fortinet FortiSIEM (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0106/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0106/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:43:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Fortinet FortiSIEM. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unified Identity – look for the meaning behind the hype!]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/unified-identity-look-for-meaning.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/unified-identity-look-for-meaning.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[If you've listened to software vendors in the identity space lately, you will have noticed that “unified” has quickly become the buzzword that everyone is adopting to describe their portfolio. And this is great! Unified identity has some amazing benefits! 
However (there is always a however, right?) not every “unified” “identity” “security” “platform” is made equal. Some vendors call the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HijackLoader Evolves: Researchers Decode the Latest Evasion Methods]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hijackloader-evolves-researchers-decode.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hijackloader-evolves-researchers-decode.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind a loader malware called HijackLoader have added new techniques for defense evasion, as the malware continues to be increasingly used by other threat actors to deliver additional payloads and tooling.
"The malware developer used a standard process hollowing technique coupled with an additional trigger that was activated by the parent process writing to a pipe,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0105 : Vulnérabilité dans SonicWall SonicOS (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0105/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0105/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:21:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SonicWall SonicOS. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Starts Blocking Sideloading of Potentially Dangerous Android Apps in Singapore]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/google-starts-blocking-sideloading-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/google-starts-blocking-sideloading-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has unveiled a new pilot program in Singapore that aims to prevent users from sideloading certain apps that abuse Android app permissions to read one-time passwords and gather sensitive data.
"This enhanced fraud protection will analyze and automatically block the installation of apps that may use sensitive runtime permissions frequently abused for financial fraud when the user attempts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0104 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits ClamAV (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0104/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0104/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:11:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits ClamAV. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service et une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0103 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0103/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0103/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T10:07:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0102 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (08 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0102/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0102/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T08:23:30.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kimsuky's New Golang Stealer 'Troll' and 'GoBear' Backdoor Target South Korea]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/kimsukys-new-golang-stealer-troll-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/kimsukys-new-golang-stealer-troll-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked nation-state actor known as Kimsuky is suspected of using a previously undocumented Golang-based information stealer called Troll Stealer.
The malware steals "SSH, FileZilla, C drive files/directories, browsers, system information, [and] screen captures" from infected systems, South Korean cybersecurity company S2W said in a new technical report.
Troll]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Patches Released for New Flaws in Cisco, Fortinet, VMware Products]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-patches-released-for-new-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-patches-released-for-new-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-08T05:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco, Fortinet, and VMware have released security fixes for multiple security vulnerabilities, including critical weaknesses that could be exploited to perform arbitrary actions on affected devices.
The first set from Cisco consists of three flaws – CVE-2024-20252 and CVE-2024-20254 (CVSS score: 9.6) and CVE-2024-20255 (CVSS score: 8.2) – impacting Cisco Expressway Series that could allow an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[After FBI Takedown, KV-Botnet Operators Shift Tactics in Attempt to Bounce Back]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/after-fbi-takedown-kv-botnet-operators.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/after-fbi-takedown-kv-botnet-operators.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T15:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the KV-botnet made "behavioral changes" to the malicious network as U.S. law enforcement began issuing commands to neutralize the activity.
KV-botnet is the name given to a network of compromised small office and home office (SOHO) routers and firewall devices across the world, with one specific cluster acting as a covert data transfer system for other Chinese]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Bootloader Vulnerability in Shim Impacts Nearly All Linux Distros]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-bootloader-vulnerability-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-bootloader-vulnerability-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The maintainers of shim have released version 15.8 to address six security flaws, including a critical bug that could pave the way for remote code execution under specific circumstances.
Tracked as CVE-2023-40547 (CVSS score: 9.8), the vulnerability could be exploited to achieve a Secure Boot bypass. Bill Demirkapi of the Microsoft Security Response Center (MSRC) has been&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0101 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0101/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0101/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T13:08:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0100 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0100/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0100/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T11:50:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0099 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Elastic (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0099/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0099/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T11:38:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits ElasticSearch. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0098 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans VMware Aria Operations pour les réseaux (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0098/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0098/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T10:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Webinar: 5 Steps to vCISO Success for MSPs and MSSPs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-webinar-5-steps-to-vciso-success.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-webinar-5-steps-to-vciso-success.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[2024 will be the year of the vCISO. An incredible 45% of MSPs and MSSPs are planning to start offering vCISO services in 2024. As an MSP/MSSP providing vCISO services, you own the organization’s cybersecurity infrastructure and strategy. But you also need to position yourself as a reliable decision-maker, navigating professional responsibilities, business needs and leadership]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0097 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Veeam Recovery Orchestrator (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0097/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0097/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T10:34:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Veeam Recovery Orchestrator. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Global Coalition and Tech Giants Unite Against Commercial Spyware Abuse]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/global-coalition-and-tech-giants-unite.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/global-coalition-and-tech-giants-unite.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T09:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A coalition of dozens of countries, including France, the U.K., and the U.S., along with tech companies such as Google, MDSec, Meta, and Microsoft, have signed a joint agreement to curb the abuse of commercial spyware to commit human rights abuses.
The initiative, dubbed the Pall Mall Process, aims to tackle the proliferation and irresponsible use of commercial cyber intrusion tools by]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0096 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (07 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0096/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0096/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T09:33:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploited FortiGate Flaw to Breach Dutch Military Network]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-exploited-fortigate.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-exploited-fortigate.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T06:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese state-backed hackers broke into a computer network that's used by the Dutch armed forces by targeting Fortinet FortiGate devices.
"This [computer network] was used for unclassified research and development (R&D)," the Dutch Military Intelligence and Security Service (MIVD) said in a statement. "Because this system was self-contained, it did not lead to any damage to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical JetBrains TeamCity On-Premises Flaw Exposes Servers to Takeover - Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-jetbrains-teamcity-on-premises.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/critical-jetbrains-teamcity-on-premises.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-07T05:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[JetBrains is alerting customers of a critical security flaw in its TeamCity On-Premises continuous integration and continuous deployment (CI/CD) software that could be exploited by threat actors to take over susceptible instances.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23917, carries a CVSS rating of 9.8 out of 10, indicative of its severity.
"The vulnerability may enable an unauthenticated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0095 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Axis (06 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0095/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0095/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T16:20:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Axis. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: Fake Facebook Job Ads Spreading 'Ov3r_Stealer' to Steal Crypto and Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/beware-fake-facebook-job-ads-spreading.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/beware-fake-facebook-job-ads-spreading.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T14:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are leveraging bogus Facebook job advertisements as a lure to trick prospective targets into installing a new Windows-based stealer malware codenamed Ov3r_Stealer.
"This malware is designed to steal credentials and crypto wallets and send those to a Telegram channel that the threat actor monitors," Trustwave SpiderLabs said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
Ov3r_Stealer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Detail New Flaws in Azure HDInsight Spark, Kafka, and Hadoop Services]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/high-severity-flaws-found-in-azure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/high-severity-flaws-found-in-azure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T14:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Three new security vulnerabilities have been discovered in Azure HDInsight's Apache Hadoop, Kafka, and Spark services that could be exploited to achieve privilege escalation and a regular expression denial-of-service (ReDoS) condition.
"The new vulnerabilities affect any authenticated user of Azure HDInsight services such as Apache Ambari and Apache Oozie," Orca security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How a $10B Enterprise Customer Drastically Increased their SaaS Security Posture with 201% ROI by Using SSPM]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-10b-enterprise-customer-drastically.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/how-10b-enterprise-customer-drastically.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications are the darlings of the software world. They enable work from anywhere, facilitate collaboration, and offer a cost-effective alternative to owning the software outright. At the same time, the very features that make SaaS apps so embraced – access from anywhere and collaboration – can also be exploited by threat actors.
Recently, Adaptive Shield commissioned a Total Economic]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Job Boards in APAC, Steal Data of Millions of Job Seekers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hackers-exploit-job-boards-in-apac.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hackers-exploit-job-boards-in-apac.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T10:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Employment agencies and retail companies chiefly located in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region have been targeted by a previously undocumented threat actor known as ResumeLooters since early 2023 with the goal of stealing sensitive data.
Singapore-headquartered Group-IB said the hacking crew's activities are geared towards job search platforms and the theft of resumes, with as many as 65]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Recent SSRF Flaw in Ivanti VPN Products Undergoes Mass Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/recently-disclosed-ssrf-flaw-in-ivanti.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/recently-disclosed-ssrf-flaw-in-ivanti.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T06:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently disclosed server-side request forgery (SSRF) vulnerability impacting Ivanti Connect Secure and Policy Secure products has come under mass exploitation.
The Shadowserver Foundation said it observed exploitation attempts originating from more than 170 unique IP addresses that aim to establish a reverse shell, among others.
The attacks exploit CVE-2024-21893 (CVSS]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Imposes Visa Restrictions on those Involved in Illegal Spyware Surveillance]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-imposes-visa-restrictions-on-those.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-imposes-visa-restrictions-on-those.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-06T05:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. State Department said it's implementing a new policy that imposes visa restrictions on individuals who are linked to the illegal use of commercial spyware to surveil civil society members.
"The misuse of commercial spyware threatens privacy and freedoms of expression, peaceful assembly, and association," Secretary of State Antony Blinken said. "Such targeting has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ALE-003 : Multiples vulnérabilités affectant la solution Anydesk (05 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-003/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-003/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 29 janvier 2024 l'ANSSI a été alertée par le BSI que l'éditeur AnyDesk Software GmbH a été victime d'une fuite de données. Le code source des applications développées par l'éditeur ainsi que des certificats et clés privées pourraient avoir été dérobés.
 L'éditeur est spécialisé dans …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Belarusian National Linked to BTC-e Faces 25 Years for $4 Billion Crypto Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/belarusian-national-linked-to-btc-e.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/belarusian-national-linked-to-btc-e.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T16:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 42-year-old Belarusian and Cypriot national with alleged connections to the now-defunct cryptocurrency exchange BTC-e is facing charges related to money laundering and operating an unlicensed money services business.
Aliaksandr Klimenka, who was arrested in Latvia on December 21, 2023, was extradited to the U.S. If convicted, he faces a maximum penalty of 25 years in prison.
BTC-e, which had]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-007 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-007 (05 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-007/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-007/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T15:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0094 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (05 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0094/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0094/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T13:33:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patchwork Using Romance Scam Lures to Infect Android Devices with VajraSpy Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/patchwork-using-romance-scam-lures-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/patchwork-using-romance-scam-lures-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Patchwork likely used romance scam lures to trap victims in Pakistan and India, and infect their Android devices with a remote access trojan called VajraSpy.
Slovak cybersecurity firm ESET said it uncovered 12 espionage apps, six of which were available for download from the official Google Play Store and were collectively downloaded more than 1,400 times between]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hands-On Review: SASE-based XDR from Cato Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hands-on-review-sase-based-xdr-from.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/hands-on-review-sase-based-xdr-from.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Companies are engaged in a seemingly endless cat-and-mouse game when it comes to cybersecurity and cyber threats. As organizations put up one defensive block after another, malicious actors kick their game up a notch to get around those blocks. Part of the challenge is to coordinate the defensive abilities of disparate security tools, even as organizations have limited resources and a dearth of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Combined Security Practices Changing the Game for Risk Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/combined-security-practices-changing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/combined-security-practices-changing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A significant challenge within cyber security at present is that there are a lot of risk management platforms available in the market, but only some deal with cyber risks in a very good way. The majority will shout alerts at the customer as and when they become apparent and cause great stress in the process. The issue being that by using a reactive, rather than proactive approach, many risks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0093 : Vulnérabilité dans NetApp StorageGRID (05 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0093/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0093/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T09:19:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans  NetApp StorageGRID. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pegasus Spyware Targeted iPhones of Journalists and Activists in Jordan]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/pegasus-spyware-targeted-iphones-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/pegasus-spyware-targeted-iphones-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The iPhones belonging to nearly three dozen journalists, activists, human rights lawyers, and civil society members in Jordan have been targeted with NSO Group's Pegasus spyware, according to joint findings from Access Now and the Citizen Lab.
Nine of the 35 individuals have been publicly confirmed as targeted, out of whom had their devices compromised with the mercenary]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Mispadu Banking Trojan Exploiting Windows SmartScreen Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-mispadu-banking-trojan-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-mispadu-banking-trojan-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-05T03:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the Mispadu banking Trojan have become the latest to exploit a now-patched Windows SmartScreen security bypass flaw to compromise users in Mexico.
The attacks entail a new variant of the malware that was first observed in 2019, Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 said in a report published last week.
Propagated via phishing mails, Mispadu is a Delphi-based information stealer]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions 6 Iranian Officials for Critical Infrastructure Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-sanctions-6-iranian-officials-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-sanctions-6-iranian-officials-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T07:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) announced sanctions against six officials associated with the Iranian intelligence agency for attacking critical infrastructure entities in the U.S. and other countries.
The officials include Hamid Reza Lashgarian, Mahdi Lashgarian, Hamid Homayunfal, Milad Mansuri, Mohammad Bagher Shirinkar, and Reza Mohammad Amin]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mastodon Vulnerability Allows Hackers to Hijack Any Decentralized Account]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/mastodon-vulnerability-allows-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/mastodon-vulnerability-allows-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T06:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The decentralized social network Mastodon has disclosed a critical security flaw that enables malicious actors to impersonate and take over any account.
"Due to insufficient origin validation in all Mastodon, attackers can impersonate and take over any remote account," the maintainers said in a terse advisory.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-23832, has a severity rating of 9.4 out of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AnyDesk Hacked: Popular Remote Desktop Software Mandates Password Reset]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/anydesk-hacked-popular-remote-desktop.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/anydesk-hacked-popular-remote-desktop.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-03T03:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Remote desktop software maker AnyDesk disclosed on Friday that it suffered a cyber attack that led to a compromise of its production systems.
The German company said the incident, which it discovered following a security audit, is not a ransomware attack and that it has notified relevant authorities.
"We have revoked all security-related certificates and systems have been remediated or replaced]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian APT28 Hackers Targeting High-Value Orgs with NTLM Relay Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-apt28-hackers-targeting-high.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/russian-apt28-hackers-targeting-high.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T14:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian state-sponsored actors have staged NT LAN Manager (NTLM) v2 hash relay attacks through various methods from April 2022 to November 2023, targeting high-value targets worldwide.
The attacks, attributed to an "aggressive" hacking crew called APT28, have set their eyes on organizations dealing with foreign affairs, energy, defense, and transportation, as well as those involved with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0092 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (02 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0092/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0092/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:49:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0091 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (02 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0091/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0091/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:33:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DirtyMoe Malware Infects 2,000+ Ukrainian Computers for DDoS and Cryptojacking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/dirtymoe-malware-infects-2000-ukrainian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/dirtymoe-malware-infects-2000-ukrainian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T13:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Computer Emergency Response Team of Ukraine (CERT-UA) has warned that more than 2,000 computers in the country have been infected by a strain of malware called DirtyMoe.
The agency attributed the campaign to a threat actor it calls UAC-0027.
DirtyMoe, active since at least 2016, is capable of carrying out cryptojacking and distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks. In March]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0090 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (02 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0090/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0090/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T12:52:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Former CIA Engineer Sentenced to 40 Years for Leaking Classified Documents]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/former-cia-engineer-sentenced-to-40.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/former-cia-engineer-sentenced-to-40.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T10:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A former software engineer with the U.S. Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) has been sentenced to 40 years in prison by the Southern District of New York (SDNY) for transmitting classified documents to WikiLeaks and for possessing child pornographic material.
Joshua Adam Schulte, 35, was originally charged in June 2018. He was found guilty in July 2022. On September 13, 2023, he was&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudzy Elevates Cybersecurity: Integrating Insights from Recorded Future to Revolutionize Cloud Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cloudzy-elevates-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cloudzy-elevates-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudzy, a prominent cloud infrastructure provider, proudly announces a significant enhancement in its cybersecurity landscape. This breakthrough has been achieved through a recent consultation with Recorded Future, a leader in providing real-time threat intelligence and cybersecurity analytics. This initiative, coupled with an overhaul of Cloudzy's cybersecurity strategies, represents a major]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[INTERPOL Arrests 31 in Global Operation, Identifies 1,900+ Ransomware-Linked IPs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/interpol-arrests-31-in-global-operation.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/interpol-arrests-31-in-global-operation.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An INTERPOL-led collaborative operation targeting phishing, banking malware, and ransomware attacks has led to the identification of 1,300 suspicious IP addresses and URLs.
The law enforcement effort, codenamed Synergia, took place between September and November 2023 in an attempt to blunt the "growth, escalation and professionalization of transnational cybercrime."
Involving 60 law]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0089 : Vulnérabilité dans Kaspersky Security pour Linux Mail Server (02 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0089/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0089/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T10:09:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Kaspersky Security pour Linux Mail Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0088 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (02 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0088/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0088/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T08:33:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Breach: Nation-State Hackers Access Source Code and Internal Docs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cloudflare-breach-nation-state-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cloudflare-breach-nation-state-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-02T06:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare has revealed that it was the target of a likely nation-state attack in which the threat actor leveraged stolen credentials to gain unauthorized access to its Atlassian server and ultimately access some documentation and a limited amount of source code.
The intrusion, which took place between November 14 and 24, 2023, and detected on November 23, was carried out "with the goal of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FritzFrog Returns with Log4Shell and PwnKit, Spreading Malware Inside Your Network]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fritzfrog-returns-with-log4shell-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fritzfrog-returns-with-log4shell-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor behind a peer-to-peer (P2P) botnet known as FritzFrog has made a return with a new variant that leverages the Log4Shell vulnerability to propagate internally within an already compromised network.
"The vulnerability is exploited in a brute-force manner that attempts to target as many vulnerable Java applications as possible," web infrastructure and security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed Docker APIs Under Attack in 'Commando Cat' Cryptojacking Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/exposed-docker-apis-under-attack-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/exposed-docker-apis-under-attack-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed Docker API endpoints over the internet are under assault from a sophisticated cryptojacking campaign called Commando Cat.
"The campaign deploys a benign container generated using the Commando project," Cado security researchers Nate Bill and Matt Muir said in a new report published today. "The attacker escapes this container and runs multiple payloads on the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0087 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits GLPI (01 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0087/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0087/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T12:15:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits GLPI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0086 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper (01 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0086/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0086/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T12:13:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Juniper. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Feds Shut Down China-Linked "KV-Botnet" Targeting SOHO Routers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-feds-shut-down-china-linked-kv.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/us-feds-shut-down-china-linked-kv.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Wednesday said it took steps to neutralize a botnet comprising hundreds of U.S.-based small office and home office (SOHO) routers hijacked by a China-linked state-sponsored threat actor called Volt Typhoon and blunt the impact posed by the hacking campaign.
The existence of the botnet, dubbed KV-botnet, was first disclosed by the Black Lotus Labs team at]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why the Right Metrics Matter When it Comes to Vulnerability Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-right-metrics-matter-when-it-comes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-right-metrics-matter-when-it-comes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[How’s your vulnerability management program doing? Is it effective? A success? Let’s be honest, without the right metrics or analytics, how can you tell how well you’re doing, progressing, or if you’re getting ROI? If you’re not measuring, how do you know it’s working? 
And even if you are measuring, faulty reporting or focusing on the wrong metrics can create blind spots and make it harder to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[HeadCrab 2.0 Goes Fileless, Targeting Redis Servers for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/headcrab-20-goes-fileless-targeting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/headcrab-20-goes-fileless-targeting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T11:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detailed an updated version of the malware HeadCrab that's known to target Redis database servers across the world since early September 2021.
The development, which comes exactly a year after the malware was first publicly disclosed by Aqua, is a sign that the financially-motivated threat actor behind the campaign is actively adapting and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: New Malware Emerges in Attacks Exploiting Ivanti VPN Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/warning-new-malware-emerges-in-attacks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/warning-new-malware-emerges-in-attacks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T07:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google-owned Mandiant said it identified new malware employed by a China-nexus espionage threat actor known as UNC5221 and other threat groups during post-exploitation activity targeting Ivanti Connect Secure VPN and Policy Secure devices.
This includes custom web shells such as BUSHWALK, CHAINLINE, FRAMESTING, and a variant of LIGHTWIRE.
"CHAINLINE is a Python web shell backdoor that is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Active Exploitation of Critical Vulnerability in iOS, iPadOS, and macOS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/cisa-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-01T05:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Wednesday added a high-severity flaw impacting iOS, iPadOS, macOS, tvOS, and watchOS to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2022-48618 (CVSS score: 7.8), concerns a bug in the kernel component.
"An attacker with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RunC Flaws Enable Container Escapes, Granting Attackers Host Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/runc-flaws-enable-container-escapes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/runc-flaws-enable-container-escapes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T20:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in the runC command line tool that could be exploited by threat actors to escape the bounds of the container and stage follow-on attacks.
The vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2024-21626, CVE-2024-23651, CVE-2024-23652, and CVE-2024-23653, have been collectively dubbed Leaky Vessels by cybersecurity vendor Snyk.
"These container]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Ivanti Discloses 2 New Zero-Day Flaws, One Under Active Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/alert-ivanti-discloses-2-new-zero-day.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/alert-ivanti-discloses-2-new-zero-day.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T13:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti is alerting of two new high-severity flaws in its Connect Secure and Policy Secure products, one of which is said to have come under targeted exploitation in the wild.
The list of vulnerabilities is as follows -

CVE-2024-21888 (CVSS score: 8.8) - A privilege escalation vulnerability in the web component of Ivanti Connect Secure (9.x, 22.x) and Ivanti Policy Secure (9.x, 22.x) allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0085 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0085/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0085/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T13:28:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0084 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans WordPress (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0084/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0084/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T13:01:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Wordpress. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Marketplaces Fuel Phishing Attacks with Easy-to-Use Kits and Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/telegram-marketplaces-fuel-phishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/telegram-marketplaces-fuel-phishing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T12:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are calling attention to the "democratization" of the phishing ecosystem owing to the emergence of Telegram as an epicenter for cybercrime, enabling threat actors to mount a mass attack for as little as $230.
"This messaging app has transformed into a bustling hub where seasoned cybercriminals and newcomers alike exchange illicit tools and insights creating a dark and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC Won't Let CISOs Be: Understanding New SaaS Cybersecurity Rules]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/the-sec-wont-let-cisos-be-understanding.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/the-sec-wont-let-cisos-be-understanding.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The SEC isn’t giving SaaS a free pass. Applicable public companies, known as “registrants,” are now subject to cyber incident disclosure and cybersecurity readiness requirements for data stored in SaaS systems, along with the 3rd and 4th party apps connected to them. 
The new cybersecurity mandates make no distinction between data exposed in a breach that was stored on-premise, in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Businesses Hit by Weaponized USBs Spreading Cryptojacking Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/italian-businesses-hit-by-weaponized.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/italian-businesses-hit-by-weaponized.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A financially motivated threat actor known as UNC4990 is leveraging weaponized USB devices as an initial infection vector to target organizations in Italy.
Google-owned Mandiant said the attacks single out multiple industries, including health, transportation, construction, and logistics.
"UNC4990 operations generally involve widespread USB infection followed by the deployment of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0083 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0083/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0083/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T09:55:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été corrigée dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0082 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Xen (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0082/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0082/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T09:44:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0081 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Spring (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0081/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0081/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T09:23:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Spring. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0080 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Splunk (31 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0080/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0080/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T08:38:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Splunk. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploiting VPN Flaws to Deploy KrustyLoader Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/chinese-hackers-exploiting-critical-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/chinese-hackers-exploiting-critical-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T07:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A pair of recently disclosed zero-day flaws in Ivanti Connect Secure (ICS) virtual private network (VPN) devices have been exploited to deliver a Rust-based payload called KrustyLoader that's used to drop the open-source Sliver adversary simulation tool.
The security vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2023-46805 (CVSS score: 8.2) and CVE-2024-21887 (CVSS score: 9.1), could be abused]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Glibc Flaw Grants Attackers Root Access on Major Linux Distros]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/new-glibc-flaw-grants-attackers-root.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/new-glibc-flaw-grants-attackers-root.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-31T05:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious local attackers can obtain full root access on Linux machines by taking advantage of a newly disclosed security flaw in the GNU C library (aka glibc).
Tracked as CVE-2023-6246, the heap-based buffer overflow vulnerability is rooted in glibc's __vsyslog_internal() function, which is used by syslog() and vsyslog() for system logging purposes. It's said to have been accidentally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Brazilian Feds Dismantle Grandoreiro Banking Trojan, Arresting Top Operatives]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/brazilian-feds-dismantle-grandoreiro.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/brazilian-feds-dismantle-grandoreiro.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T16:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Brazilian law enforcement operation has led to the arrest of several Brazilian operators in charge of the Grandoreiro malware.
The Federal Police of Brazil said it served five temporary arrest warrants and 13 search and seizure warrants in the states of São Paulo, Santa Catarina, Pará, Goiás, and Mato Grosso.
Slovak cybersecurity firm ESET, which provided additional]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[URGENT: Upgrade GitLab - Critical Workspace Creation Flaw Allows File Overwrite]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/urgent-upgrade-gitlab-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/urgent-upgrade-gitlab-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab once again released fixes to address a critical security flaw in its Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE) that could be exploited to write arbitrary files while creating a workspace.
Tracked as CVE-2024-0402, the vulnerability has a CVSS score of 9.9 out of a maximum of 10.
"An issue has been discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions from 16.0 prior to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Hackers Target Myanmar's Top Ministries with Backdoor Blitz]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/china-linked-hackers-target-myanmars.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/china-linked-hackers-target-myanmars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-based threat actor known as Mustang Panda is suspected to have targeted Myanmar's Ministry of Defence and Foreign Affairs as part of twin campaigns designed to deploy backdoors and remote access trojans.
The findings come from CSIRT-CTI, which said the activities took place in November 2023 and January 2024 after artifacts in connection with the attacks were uploaded to the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top Security Posture Vulnerabilities Revealed]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/top-security-posture-vulnerabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/top-security-posture-vulnerabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Each New Year introduces a new set of challenges and opportunities for strengthening our cybersecurity posture. It's the nature of the field – the speed at which malicious actors carry out advanced persistent threats brings a constant, evolving battle for cyber resilience. The excitement in cybersecurity lies in this continuous adaptation and learning, always staying one step ahead of potential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Italian Data Protection Watchdog Accuses ChatGPT of Privacy Violations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/italian-data-protection-watchdog.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/italian-data-protection-watchdog.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Italy's data protection authority (DPA) has notified ChatGPT-maker OpenAI of supposedly violating privacy laws in the region.
"The available evidence pointed to the existence of breaches of the provisions contained in the E.U. GDPR [General Data Protection Regulation]," the Garante per la protezione dei dati personali (aka the Garante) said in a statement on Monday.
It also said it]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0079 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits ESET (30 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0079/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0079/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T10:00:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits ESET. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0078 : Vulnérabilité dans Progress MOVEit Transfer (30 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0078/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0078/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T09:59:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Progress MOVEit Transfer. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ZLoader Malware Variant Surfaces with 64-bit Windows Compatibility]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/new-zloader-malware-variant-surfaces.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/new-zloader-malware-variant-surfaces.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have identified a new campaign that delivers the ZLoader malware, resurfacing nearly two years after the botnet's infrastructure was dismantled in April 2022.
A new variant of the malware is said to have been in development since September 2023, Zscaler ThreatLabz said in an analysis published this month.
"The new version of Zloader made significant changes to the loader]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks Releases Urgent Junos OS Updates for High-Severity Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/juniper-networks-releases-urgent-junos.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/juniper-networks-releases-urgent-junos.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-30T05:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Juniper Networks has released out-of-band updates to address high-severity flaws in SRX Series and EX Series that could be exploited by a threat actor to take control of susceptible systems.
The vulnerabilities, tracked as CVE-2024-21619 and CVE-2024-21620, are rooted in the J-Web component and impact all versions of Junos OS. Two other shortcomings, CVE-2023-36846 and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Uncover How Outlook Vulnerability Could Leak Your NTLM Passwords]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/researchers-uncover-outlook.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/researchers-uncover-outlook.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T13:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security flaw in Microsoft Outlook could be exploited by threat actors to access NT LAN Manager (NTLM) v2 hashed passwords when opening a specially crafted file.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2023-35636 (CVSS score: 6.5), was addressed by the tech giant as part of its Patch Tuesday updates for December 2023.
"In an email attack scenario, an attacker could exploit the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-006 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-006 (29 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-006/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-006/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:46:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[493 Companies Share Their SaaS Security Battles – Get Insights in this Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/493-companies-share-their-saas-security.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/493-companies-share-their-saas-security.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital world, security risks are more prevalent than ever, especially when it comes to Software as a Service (SaaS) applications. Did you know that an alarming 97% of companies face serious risks from unsecured SaaS applications?Moreover, about 20% of these organizations are struggling with internal data threats. These statistics aren't just numbers; they're a wake-up call.
We're]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Riding the AI Waves: The Rise of Artificial Intelligence to Combat Cyber Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/riding-ai-waves-rise-of-artificial.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/riding-ai-waves-rise-of-artificial.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In nearly every segment of our lives, AI (artificial intelligence) now makes a significant impact: It can deliver better healthcare diagnoses and treatments; detect and reduce the risk of financial fraud; improve inventory management; and serve up the right recommendation for a streaming movie on Friday night. However, one can also make a strong case that some of AI’s most significant impacts]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Albabat, Kasseika, Kuiper: New Ransomware Gangs Rise with Rust and Golang]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/albabat-kasseika-kuiper-new-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/albabat-kasseika-kuiper-new-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T11:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detected in the wild yet another variant of the Phobos ransomware family known as Faust.
Fortinet FortiGuard Labs, which detailed the latest iteration of the ransomware, said it's being propagated by means of an infection that delivers a Microsoft Excel document (.XLAM) containing a VBA script.
"The attackers utilized the Gitea service to store several files]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0077 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits NetApp (29 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0077/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0077/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T09:19:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits NetApp. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0076 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Edge (29 janvier 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0076/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0076/"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T08:56:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été corrigée dans Microsoft Edge. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une usurpation d'identité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NSA Admits Secretly Buying Your Internet Browsing Data without Warrants]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/nsa-admits-secretly-buying-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/nsa-admits-secretly-buying-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T06:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. National Security Agency (NSA) has admitted to buying internet browsing records from data brokers to identify the websites and apps Americans use that would otherwise require a court order, U.S. Senator Ron Wyden said last week.
"The U.S. government should not be funding and legitimizing a shady industry whose flagrant violations of Americans' privacy are not just unethical, but illegal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious PyPI Packages Slip WhiteSnake InfoStealer Malware onto Windows Machines]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/malicious-pypi-packages-slip-whitesnake.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/01/malicious-pypi-packages-slip-whitesnake.html"/>
        <updated>2024-01-29T05:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have identified malicious packages on the open-source Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that deliver an information stealing malware called WhiteSnake Stealer on Windows systems.
The malware-laced packages are named nigpal, figflix, telerer, seGMM, fbdebug, sGMM, myGens, NewGends, and TestLibs111. They have been uploaded by a threat actor named "WS."
"These]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>