<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-03-28T18:12:58.573Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Linux Version of DinodasRAT Spotted in Cyber Attacks Across Several Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/linux-version-of-dinodasrat-spotted-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/linux-version-of-dinodasrat-spotted-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T17:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Linux version of a multi-platform backdoor called DinodasRAT has been detected in the wild targeting China, Taiwan, Turkey, and Uzbekistan, new findings from Kaspersky reveal.
DinodasRAT, also known as XDealer, is a C++-based malware that offers the ability to harvest a wide range of sensitive data from compromised hosts.
In October 2023, Slovak cybersecurity firm ESET]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Finland Blames Chinese Hacking Group APT31 for Parliament Cyber Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/finland-blames-chinese-hacking-group.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/finland-blames-chinese-hacking-group.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T16:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Police of Finland (aka Poliisi) has formally accused a Chinese nation-state actor tracked as APT31 for orchestrating a cyber attack targeting the country's Parliament in 2020.
The intrusion, per the authorities, is said to have occurred between fall 2020 and early 2021. The agency described the ongoing criminal probe as both demanding and time-consuming, involving extensive analysis of a "]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Darcula Phishing Network Leveraging RCS and iMessage to Evade Detection]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/darcula-phishing-network-leveraging-rcs.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/darcula-phishing-network-leveraging-rcs.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T14:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A sophisticated phishing-as-a-service (PhaaS) platform called Darcula has set its sights on organizations in over 100 countries by leveraging a massive network of more than 20,000 counterfeit domains to help cyber criminals launch attacks at scale.
"Using iMessage and RCS rather than SMS to send text messages has the side effect of bypassing SMS firewalls, which is being used to great]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Webinar: Avoiding Application Security Blind Spots with OPSWAT and F5]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-webinar-avoiding-application.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-webinar-avoiding-application.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T12:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Considering the ever-changing state of cybersecurity, it's never too late to ask yourself, "am I doing what's necessary to keep my organization's web applications secure?"
The continuous evolution of technology introduces new and increasingly sophisticated threats daily, posing challenges to organizations all over the world and across the broader spectrum of industries striving to maintain]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes: The Art of Safeguarding Non-Human Identities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/behind-scenes-art-of-safeguarding-non.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/behind-scenes-art-of-safeguarding-non.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the whirlwind of modern software development, teams race against time, constantly pushing the boundaries of innovation and efficiency. This relentless pace is fueled by an evolving tech landscape, where SaaS domination, the proliferation of microservices, and the ubiquity of CI/CD pipelines are not just trends but the new norm.
Amidst this backdrop, a critical aspect subtly weaves into the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New ZenHammer Attack Bypasses Rowhammer Defenses on AMD CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-zenhammer-attack-bypasses-rowhammer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-zenhammer-attack-bypasses-rowhammer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers from ETH Zurich have developed a new variant of the RowHammer DRAM (dynamic random-access memory) attack that, for the first time, successfully works against AMD Zen 2 and Zen 3 systems despite mitigations such as Target Row Refresh (TRR).
"This result proves that AMD systems are equally vulnerable to Rowhammer as Intel systems, which greatly increases the attack]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0261 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0261/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0261/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T10:34:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0260 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0260/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0260/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T10:31:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0259 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0259/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0259/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:56:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0258 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Splunk (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0258/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0258/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:53:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Splunk. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0257 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Elasticsearch (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0257/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0257/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:42:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Elasticsearch. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0256 : Vulnérabilité dans Wireshark (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0256/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0256/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:38:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Wireshark. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0255 : Vulnérabilité dans GLPI (28 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0255/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0255/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T09:36:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans GLPI. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Offers Premium Subscription in Exchange for Using Your Number to Send OTPs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/telegram-offers-premium-subscription-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/telegram-offers-premium-subscription-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-28T08:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In June 2017, a study of more than 3,000 Massachusetts Institute of Technology (MIT) students published by the National Bureau for Economic Research (NBER) found that 98% of them were willing to give away their friends' email addresses in exchange for free pizza.
"Whereas people say they care about privacy, they are willing to relinquish private data quite easily when]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Hit Indian Defense, Energy Sectors with Malware Posing as Air Force Invite]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-target-indian-defense-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-target-indian-defense-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T15:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Indian government entities and energy companies have been targeted by unknown threat actors with an aim to deliver a modified version of an open-source information stealer malware called HackBrowserData and exfiltrate sensitive information in some cases by using Slack as command-and-control (C2).
"The information stealer was delivered via a phishing email, masquerading as an invitation letter]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0254 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (27 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0254/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0254/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T13:42:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0253 : Vulnérabilité dans Aruba ArubaOS-Switch (27 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0253/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0253/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T13:39:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Aruba ArubaOS-Switch. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0252 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nagios XI (27 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0252/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0252/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T13:33:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nagios XI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns: Hackers Actively Attacking Microsoft SharePoint Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-warns-hackers-actively-attacking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-warns-hackers-actively-attacking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T13:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) has added a security flaw impacting the Microsoft Sharepoint Server to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog based on evidence of active exploitation in the wild.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2023-24955 (CVSS score: 7.2), is a critical remote code execution flaw that allows an authenticated attacker with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Edge Bug Could Have Allowed Attackers to Silently Install Malicious Extensions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsoft-edge-bug-could-have-allowed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsoft-edge-bug-could-have-allowed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T12:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security flaw in the Microsoft Edge web browser could have been abused to install arbitrary extensions on users' systems and carry out malicious actions. 
"This flaw could have allowed an attacker to exploit a private API, initially intended for marketing purposes, to covertly install additional browser extensions with broad permissions without the user's knowledge," Guardio]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SASE Solutions Fall Short Without Enterprise Browser Extensions, New Report Reveals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/sase-solutions-fall-short-without.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/sase-solutions-fall-short-without.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As SaaS applications dominate the business landscape, organizations need optimized network speed and robust security measures. Many of them have been turning to SASE, a product category that offers cloud-based network protection while enhancing network infrastructure performance.
However, a new report: "Better Together: SASE and Enterprise Browser Extension for the SaaS-First Enterprise" (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Unpatched Ray AI Platform Vulnerability Exploited for Cryptocurrency Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/critical-unpatched-ray-ai-platform.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/critical-unpatched-ray-ai-platform.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T10:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are warning that threat actors are actively exploiting a "disputed" and unpatched vulnerability in an open-source artificial intelligence (AI) platform called Anyscale Ray to hijack computing power for illicit cryptocurrency mining.
"This vulnerability allows attackers to take over the companies' computing power and leak sensitive data," Oligo Security researchers Avi]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: New Phishing Attack Delivers Keylogger Disguised as Bank Payment Notice]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-new-phishing-attack-delivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-new-phishing-attack-delivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T07:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing campaign has been observed leveraging a novel loader malware to deliver an information stealer and keylogger called Agent Tesla.
Trustwave SpiderLabs said it identified a phishing email bearing this attack chain on March 8, 2024. The message masquerades as a bank payment notification, urging the user to open an archive file attachment.
The archive ("Bank Handlowy w Warszawie]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Two Chinese APT Groups Ramp Up Cyber Espionage Against ASEAN Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/two-chinese-apt-groups-ramp-up-cyber.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/two-chinese-apt-groups-ramp-up-cyber.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-27T04:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two China-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) groups have been observed targeting entities and member countries affiliated with the Association of Southeast Asian Nations (ASEAN) as part of a cyber espionage campaign over the past three months.
This includes the threat actor known as Mustang Panda, which has been recently linked to cyber attacks against Myanmar as well as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious NuGet Package Linked to Industrial Espionage Targets Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malicious-nuget-package-linked-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malicious-nuget-package-linked-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T16:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have identified a suspicious package in the NuGet package manager that's likely designed to target developers working with tools made by a Chinese firm that specializes in industrial- and digital equipment manufacturing.
The package in question is SqzrFramework480, which ReversingLabs said was first published on January 24, 2024. It has been downloaded]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0251 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Kaspersky Anti Targeted Attack (26 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0251/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0251/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T12:43:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Kaspersky Anti Targeted Attack. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Charges 7 Chinese Nationals in Major 14-Year Cyber Espionage Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-charges-7-chinese-nationals-in-major.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-charges-7-chinese-nationals-in-major.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T12:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Monday unsealed indictments against seven Chinese nationals for their involvement in a hacking group that targeted U.S. and foreign critics, journalists, businesses, and political officials for about 14 years.
The defendants include Ni Gaobin (倪高彬), Weng Ming (翁明), Cheng Feng (程锋), Peng Yaowen (彭耀文), Sun Xiaohui (孙小辉), Xiong Wang (熊旺), and Zhao Guangzong (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting Shields: Defending Minecraft Servers Against DDoS Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/crafting-shields-defending-minecraft.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/crafting-shields-defending-minecraft.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T11:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Minecraft, with over 500 million registered users and 166 million monthly players, faces significant risks from distributed denial-of-service (DDoS) attacks, threatening server functionality, player experience, and the game’s reputation. Despite the prevalence of DDoS attacks on the game, the majority of incidents go unreported, leaving a gap in awareness and protection. This article explains]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0250 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Apple (26 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0250/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0250/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T09:39:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Apple. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0249 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Tenable Security Center (26 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0249/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0249/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T09:33:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Tenable Security Center. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions 3 Cryptocurrency Exchanges for Helping Russia Evade Sanctions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-sanctions-3-cryptocurrency-exchanges.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-sanctions-3-cryptocurrency-exchanges.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T08:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of the Treasury's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned three cryptocurrency exchanges for offering services used to evade economic restrictions imposed on Russia following its invasion of Ukraine in early 2022.
This includes Bitpapa IC FZC LLC, Crypto Explorer DMCC (AWEX), and Obshchestvo S Ogranichennoy Otvetstvennostyu Tsentr Obrabotki Elektronnykh Platezhey (]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Alerts on Active Exploitation of Flaws in Fortinet, Ivanti, and Nice Products]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-alerts-on-active-exploitation-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-alerts-on-active-exploitation-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-26T04:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Monday placed three security flaws to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, citing evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerabilities added are as follows -

CVE-2023-48788 (CVSS score: 9.3) - Fortinet FortiClient EMS SQL Injection Vulnerability
CVE-2021-44529 (CVSS score: 9.8) - Ivanti]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-014 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-014 (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-014/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-014/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T14:46:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d'actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0248 : Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft .Net (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0248/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0248/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T12:25:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été corrigée dans Microsoft .Net. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0247 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0247/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0247/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T12:25:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été corrigées dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un contournement de la fonctionnalité de sécurité et une usurpation d'identité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0246 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mozilla Firefox (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0246/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0246/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T12:24:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mozilla Firefox. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0245 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans MISP (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0245/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0245/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T12:20:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MISP. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0244 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Netapp (25 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0244/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0244/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T12:17:17.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Netapp. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Hijack GitHub Accounts in Supply Chain Attack Affecting Top-gg and Others]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-hijack-github-accounts-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-hijack-github-accounts-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unidentified adversaries orchestrated a sophisticated attack campaign that has impacted several individual developers as well as the GitHub organization account associated with Top.gg, a Discord bot discovery site.
"The threat actors used multiple TTPs in this attack, including account takeover via stolen browser cookies, contributing malicious code with verified commits, setting up a custom]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Key Lesson from Microsoft’s Password Spray Hack: Secure Every Account]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/key-lesson-from-microsofts-password.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/key-lesson-from-microsofts-password.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T11:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In January 2024, Microsoft discovered they’d been the victim of a hack orchestrated by Russian-state hackers Midnight Blizzard (sometimes known as Nobelium). The concerning detail about this case is how easy it was to breach the software giant. It wasn’t a highly technical hack that exploited a zero-day vulnerability – the hackers used a simple password spray attack to take control of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New "GoFetch" Vulnerability in Apple M-Series Chips Leaks Secret Encryption Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-gofetch-vulnerability-in-apple-m.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-gofetch-vulnerability-in-apple-m.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T09:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new security shortcoming discovered in Apple M-series chips could be exploited to extract secret keys used during cryptographic operations.
Dubbed GoFetch, the vulnerability relates to a microarchitectural side-channel attack that takes advantage of a feature known as data memory-dependent prefetcher (DMP) to target constant-time cryptographic implementations and capture sensitive data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Linked MuddyWater Deploys Atera for Surveillance in Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/iran-linked-muddywater-deploys-atera.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/iran-linked-muddywater-deploys-atera.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-25T07:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Iran-affiliated threat actor tracked as MuddyWater (aka Mango Sandstorm or TA450) has been linked to a new phishing campaign in March 2024 that aims to deliver a legitimate Remote Monitoring and Management (RMM) solution called Atera.
The activity, which took place from March 7 through the week of March 11, targeted Israeli entities spanning global manufacturing, technology, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korea-linked Kimsuky Shifts to Compiled HTML Help Files in Ongoing Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/n-korea-linked-kimsuky-shifts-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/n-korea-linked-kimsuky-shifts-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T05:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The North Korea-linked threat actor known as Kimsuky (aka Black Banshee, Emerald Sleet, or Springtail) has been observed shifting its tactics, leveraging Compiled HTML Help (CHM) files as vectors to deliver malware for harvesting sensitive data.
Kimsuky, active since at least 2012, is known to target entities located in South Korea as well as North America, Asia, and Europe.
According]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[German Police Seize 'Nemesis Market' in Major International Darknet Raid]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/german-police-seize-nemesis-market-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/german-police-seize-nemesis-market-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-24T05:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[German authorities have announced the takedown of an illicit underground marketplace called Nemesis Market that peddled narcotics, stolen data, and various cybercrime services.
The Federal Criminal Police Office (aka Bundeskriminalamt or BKA) said it seized the digital infrastructure associated with the darknet service located in Germany and Lithuania and confiscated €94,000 ($102,107)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Use 'WINELOADER' Malware to Target German Political Parties]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russian-hackers-use-wineloader-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russian-hackers-use-wineloader-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-23T06:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The WINELOADER backdoor used in recent cyber attacks targeting diplomatic entities with wine-tasting phishing lures has been attributed as the handiwork of a hacking group with links to Russia's Foreign Intelligence Service (SVR), which was responsible for breaching SolarWinds and Microsoft.
The findings come from Mandiant, which said Midnight Blizzard (aka APT29, BlueBravo, or]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New StrelaStealer Phishing Attacks Hit Over 100 Organizations in E.U. and U.S.]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-strelastealer-phishing-attacks-hit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-strelastealer-phishing-attacks-hit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T14:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have detected a new wave of phishing attacks that aim to deliver an ever-evolving information stealer referred to as StrelaStealer.
The campaigns impact more than 100 organizations in the E.U. and the U.S., Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 researchers said in a new report published today.
"These campaigns come in the form of spam emails with attachments that eventually]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AWS Patches Critical 'FlowFixation' Bug in Airflow Service to Prevent Session Hijacking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/aws-patches-critical-flowfixation-bug.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/aws-patches-critical-flowfixation-bug.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shared details of a now-patched security vulnerability in Amazon Web Services (AWS) Managed Workflows for Apache Airflow (MWAA) that could be potentially exploited by a malicious actor to hijack victims' sessions and achieve remote code execution on underlying instances.
The vulnerability, now addressed by AWS, has been codenamed FlowFixation by Tenable.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0243 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (22 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0243/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0243/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T13:23:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0242 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (22 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0242/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0242/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T13:04:15.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[China-Linked Group Breaches Networks via Connectwise, F5 Software Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/china-linked-group-breaches-networks.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/china-linked-group-breaches-networks.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T11:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A China-linked threat cluster leveraged security flaws in Connectwise ScreenConnect and F5 BIG-IP software to deliver custom malware capable of delivering additional backdoors on compromised Linux hosts as part of an "aggressive" campaign.
Google-owned Mandiant is tracking the activity under its uncategorized moniker UNC5174 (aka Uteus or Uetus), describing it as a "former]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Massive Sign1 Campaign Infects 39,000+ WordPress Sites with Scam Redirects]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/massive-sign1-campaign-infects-39000.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/massive-sign1-campaign-infects-39000.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A massive malware campaign dubbed Sign1 has compromised over 39,000 WordPress sites in the last six months, using malicious JavaScript injections to redirect users to scam sites.
The most recent variant of the malware is estimated to have infected no less than 2,500 sites over the past two months alone, Sucuri said in a report published this week.
The attacks entail injecting rogue]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Implementing Zero Trust Controls for Compliance]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/implementing-zero-trust-controls-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/implementing-zero-trust-controls-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The ThreatLocker® Zero Trust Endpoint Protection Platform implements a strict deny-by-default, allow-by-exception security posture to give organizations the ability to set policy-based controls within their environment and mitigate countless cyber threats, including zero-days, unseen network footholds, and malware attacks as a direct result of user error.
With the capabilities of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0241 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (22 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0241/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0241/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T07:25:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0240 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (22 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0240/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0240/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T06:54:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une exécution de code arbitraire et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Justice Department Sues Apple Over Monopoly and Messaging Security]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-justice-department-sues-apple-over.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-justice-department-sues-apple-over.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T06:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ), along with 16 other state and district attorneys general, on Thursday accused Apple of illegally maintaining a monopoly over smartphones, thereby undermining, among others, security and privacy of users when messaging non-iPhone users.
"Apple wraps itself in a cloak of privacy, security, and consumer preferences to justify its anticompetitive]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Target Ukrainian Telecoms with Upgraded 'AcidPour' Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russian-hackers-target-ukrainian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russian-hackers-target-ukrainian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-22T03:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The data wiping malware called AcidPour may have been deployed in attacks targeting four telecom providers in Ukraine, new findings from SentinelOne show.
The cybersecurity firm also confirmed connections between the malware and AcidRain, tying it to threat activity clusters associated with Russian military intelligence.
"AcidPour's expanded capabilities would enable it to better]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russia Hackers Using TinyTurla-NG to Breach European NGO's Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russia-hackers-using-tinyturla-ng-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/russia-hackers-using-tinyturla-ng-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T16:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russia-linked threat actor known as Turla infected several systems belonging to an unnamed European non-governmental organization (NGO) in order to deploy a backdoor called TinyTurla-NG.
"The attackers compromised the first system, established persistence and added exclusions to antivirus products running on these endpoints as part of their preliminary post-compromise actions," Cisco]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 800 npm Packages Found with Discrepancies, 18 Exploitable to 'Manifest Confusion']]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-800-npm-packages-found-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-800-npm-packages-found-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T14:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[New research has discovered over 800 packages in the npm registry which have discrepancies from their registry entries, out of which 18 have been found to exploit a technique called manifest confusion.
The findings come from cybersecurity firm JFrog, which said the issue could be exploited by threat actors to trick developers into running malicious code.
"It's an actual threat since]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[AndroxGh0st Malware Targets Laravel Apps to Steal Cloud Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/androxgh0st-malware-targets-laravel.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/androxgh0st-malware-targets-laravel.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T12:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have shed light on a tool referred to as AndroxGh0st that's used to target Laravel applications and steal sensitive data.
"It works by scanning and taking out important information from .env files, revealing login details linked to AWS and Twilio," Juniper Threat Labs researcher Kashinath T Pattan said.
"Classified as an SMTP cracker, it exploits SMTP]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Accelerate Vendor Risk Assessments in the Age of SaaS Sprawl]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-to-accelerate-vendor-risk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-to-accelerate-vendor-risk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital-first business environment dominated by SaaS applications, organizations increasingly depend on third-party vendors for essential cloud services and software solutions. As more vendors and services are added to the mix, the complexity and potential vulnerabilities within the SaaS supply chain snowball quickly. That’s why effective vendor risk management (VRM) is a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Launches AI-Powered Autofix Tool to Assist Devs in Patching Security Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/github-launches-ai-powered-autofix-tool.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/github-launches-ai-powered-autofix-tool.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub on Wednesday announced that it's making available a feature called code scanning autofix in public beta for all Advanced Security customers to provide targeted recommendations in an effort to avoid introducing new security issues.
"Powered by GitHub Copilot and CodeQL, code scanning autofix covers more than 90% of alert types in JavaScript, Typescript, Java, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0239 : Vulnérabilité dans  Microsoft Xbox Gaming Services (21 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0239/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0239/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T09:31:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Xbox Gaming Services. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Making Sense of Operational Technology Attacks: The Past, Present, and Future]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/making-sense-of-operational-technology.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/making-sense-of-operational-technology.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T09:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[When you read reports about cyber-attacks affecting operational technology (OT), it’s easy to get caught up in the hype and assume every single one is sophisticated. But are OT environments all over the world really besieged by a constant barrage of complex cyber-attacks? Answering that would require breaking down the different types of OT cyber-attacks and then looking back on all the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions Russians Behind 'Doppelganger' Cyber Influence Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-sanctions-russians-behind.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-sanctions-russians-behind.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T08:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Treasury Department's Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) on Wednesday announced sanctions against two 46-year-old Russian nationals and the respective companies they own for engaging in cyber influence operations.
Ilya Andreevich Gambashidze (Gambashidze), the founder of the Moscow-based company Social Design Agency (SDA), and Nikolai Aleksandrovich Tupikin (Tupikin), the CEO and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0238 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Ivanti (21 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0238/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0238/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T06:48:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ivanti. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Releases Urgent Fix for Critical Sentry RCE Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ivanti-releases-urgent-fix-for-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ivanti-releases-urgent-fix-for-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T03:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has disclosed details of a critical remote code execution flaw impacting Standalone Sentry, urging customers to apply the fixes immediately to stay protected against potential cyber threats.
Tracked as CVE-2023-41724, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 9.6.
"An unauthenticated threat actor can execute arbitrary commands on the underlying operating system of the appliance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Releases Fixes for Over 2 Dozen Flaws, Including Critical Bamboo Bug]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/atlassian-releases-fixes-for-over-2.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/atlassian-releases-fixes-for-over-2.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-21T03:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian has released patches for more than two dozen security flaws, including a critical bug impacting Bamboo Data Center and Server that could be exploited without requiring user interaction.
Tracked as CVE-2024-1597, the vulnerability carries a CVSS score of 10.0, indicating maximum severity.
Described as an SQL injection flaw, it's rooted in a dependency called org.postgresql:]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New 'Loop DoS' Attack Impacts Hundreds of Thousands of Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-loop-dos-attack-impacts-hundreds-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-loop-dos-attack-impacts-hundreds-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel denial-of-service (DoS) attack vector has been found to target application-layer protocols based on User Datagram Protocol (UDP), putting hundreds of thousands of hosts likely at risk.
Called Loop DoS attacks, the approach pairs "servers of these protocols in such a way that they communicate with each other indefinitely," researchers from the CISPA Helmholtz-Center for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0237 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Belden (20 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0237/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0237/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T12:34:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Belden. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Generative AI Security - Secure Your Business in a World Powered by LLMs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/generative-ai-security-secure-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/generative-ai-security-secure-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Did you know that 79% of organizations are already leveraging Generative AI technologies? Much like the internet defined the 90s and the cloud revolutionized the 2010s, we are now in the era of Large Language Models (LLMs) and Generative AI.
The potential of Generative AI is immense, yet it brings significant challenges, especially in security integration. Despite their powerful capabilities,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TeamCity Flaw Leads to Surge in Ransomware, Cryptomining, and RAT Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/teamcity-flaw-leads-to-surge-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/teamcity-flaw-leads-to-surge-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Multiple threat actors are exploiting the recently disclosed security flaws in JetBrains TeamCity software to deploy ransomware, cryptocurrency miners, Cobalt Strike beacons, and a Golang-based remote access trojan called Spark RAT.
The attacks entail the exploitation of CVE-2024-27198 (CVSS score: 9.8) that enables an adversary to bypass authentication measures and gain administrative]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New BunnyLoader Malware Variant Surfaces with Modular Attack Features]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-bunnyloader-malware-variant.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-bunnyloader-malware-variant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered an updated variant of a stealer and malware loader called BunnyLoader that modularizes its various functions as well as allow it to evade detection.
"BunnyLoader is dynamically developing malware with the capability to steal information, credentials and cryptocurrency, as well as deliver additional malware to its victims," Palo Alto Networks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0236 : Vulnérabilité dans Spring Authorization Server (20 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0236/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0236/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T07:16:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Spring Authorization Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0235 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (20 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0235/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0235/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T07:12:56.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0234 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (20 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0234/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0234/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T06:53:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Arrests Trio for Hijacking Over 100 Million Email and Instagram Accounts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ukraine-arrests-trio-for-hijacking-over.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ukraine-arrests-trio-for-hijacking-over.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T06:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Cyber Police of Ukraine has arrested three individuals on suspicion of hijacking more than 100 million emails and Instagram accounts from users across the world.
The suspects, aged between 20 and 40, are said to be part of an organized criminal group living in different parts of the country. If convicted, they face up to 15 years in prison.
The accounts, authorities said, were]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. EPA Forms Task Force to Protect Water Systems from Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-epa-forms-task-force-to-protect.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-epa-forms-task-force-to-protect.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-20T05:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) said it's forming a new "Water Sector Cybersecurity Task Force" to devise methods to counter the threats faced by the water sector in the country.
"In addition to considering the prevalent vulnerabilities of water systems to cyberattacks and the challenges experienced by some systems in adopting best practices, this Task Force in its deliberations]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APIs Drive the Majority of Internet Traffic and Cybercriminals are Taking Advantage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/apis-drive-majority-of-internet-traffic.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/apis-drive-majority-of-internet-traffic.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Application programming interfaces (APIs) are the connective tissue behind digital modernization, helping applications and databases exchange data more effectively. The State of API Security in 2024 Report from Imperva, a Thales company, found that the majority of internet traffic (71%) in 2023 was API calls. What’s more, a typical enterprise site saw an average of 1.5 billion API]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Deepfakes to Malware: AI's Expanding Role in Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/from-deepfakes-to-malware-ais-expanding.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/from-deepfakes-to-malware-ais-expanding.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Large language models (LLMs) powering artificial intelligence (AI) tools today could be exploited to develop self-augmenting malware capable of bypassing YARA rules.
"Generative AI can be used to evade string-based YARA rules by augmenting the source code of small malware variants, effectively lowering detection rates," Recorded Future said in a new report shared with The Hacker News.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0233 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans AXIS OS (19 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0233/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0233/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T12:35:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans AXIS OS. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Crafting and Communicating Your Cybersecurity Strategy for Board Buy-In]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/crafting-and-communicating-your.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/crafting-and-communicating-your.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In an era where digital transformation drives business across sectors, cybersecurity has transcended its traditional operational role to become a cornerstone of corporate strategy and risk management. This evolution demands a shift in how cybersecurity leaders—particularly Chief Information Security Officers (CISOs)—articulate the value and urgency of cybersecurity investments to their boards.&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploiting Popular Document Publishing Sites for Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploiting-popular-document.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploiting-popular-document.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are leveraging digital document publishing (DDP) sites hosted on platforms like FlipSnack, Issuu, Marq, Publuu, RelayTo, and Simplebooklet for carrying out phishing, credential harvesting, and session token theft, once again underscoring how threat actors are repurposing legitimate services for malicious ends.
"Hosting phishing lures on DDP sites increases the likelihood]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Suspected Russian Data-Wiping 'AcidPour' Malware Targeting Linux x86 Devices]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/suspected-russian-data-wiping-acidpour.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/suspected-russian-data-wiping-acidpour.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T09:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new variant of a data wiping malware called AcidRain has been detected in the wild that's specifically designed for targeting Linux x86 devices.
The malware, dubbed AcidPour, is compiled for Linux x86 devices, SentinelOne's Juan Andres Guerrero-Saade said in a series of posts on X.
"The new variant [...] is an ELF binary compiled for x86 (not MIPS) and while it refers to similar devices/]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0232 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Spring Security (19 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0232/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0232/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T07:03:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Spring Security. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0231 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits GLPI (19 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0231/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0231/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T06:50:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits GLPI. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Attack Uses Clever Microsoft Office Trick to Deploy NetSupport RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-phishing-attack-uses-clever.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-phishing-attack-uses-clever.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T05:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing campaign is targeting U.S. organizations with the intent to deploy a remote access trojan called NetSupport RAT.
Israeli cybersecurity company Perception Point is tracking the activity under the moniker Operation PhantomBlu.
"The PhantomBlu operation introduces a nuanced exploitation method, diverging from NetSupport RAT’s typical delivery mechanism by leveraging OLE (Object]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[E-Root Marketplace Admin Sentenced to 42 Months for Selling 350K Stolen Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/e-root-marketplace-admin-sentenced-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/e-root-marketplace-admin-sentenced-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-19T04:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 31-year-old Moldovan national has been sentenced to 42 months in prison in the U.S. for operating an illicit marketplace called E-Root Marketplace that offered for sale hundreds of thousands of compromised credentials, the Department of Justice (DoJ) announced.
Sandu Boris Diaconu was charged with conspiracy to commit access device and computer fraud and possession of 15 or more unauthorized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New DEEP#GOSU Malware Campaign Targets Windows Users with Advanced Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-deepgosu-malware-campaign-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-deepgosu-malware-campaign-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T17:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new elaborate attack campaign has been observed employing PowerShell and VBScript malware to infect Windows systems and harvest sensitive information.
Cybersecurity company Securonix, which dubbed the campaign DEEP#GOSU, said it's likely associated with the North Korean state-sponsored group tracked as Kimsuky.
"The malware payloads used in the DEEP#GOSU represent a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-013 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-013 (18 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-013/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-013/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T14:37:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortra Patches Critical RCE Vulnerability in FileCatalyst Transfer Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/fortra-patches-critical-rce.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/fortra-patches-critical-rce.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortra has released details of a now-patched critical security flaw impacting its FileCatalyst file transfer solution that could allow unauthenticated attackers to gain remote code execution on susceptible servers.
Tracked as CVE-2024-25153, the shortcoming carries a CVSS score of 9.8 out of a maximum of 10.
"A directory traversal within the 'ftpservlet' of the FileCatalyst Workflow]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0230 : Vulnérabilité dans Kaspersky Password Manager (18 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0230/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0230/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:45:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Kaspersky Password Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Using Sneaky HTML Smuggling to Deliver Malware via Fake Google Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-using-sneaky-html-smuggling-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-using-sneaky-html-smuggling-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T12:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new malware campaign that leverages bogus Google Sites pages and HTML smuggling to distribute a commercial malware called AZORult in order to facilitate information theft.
"It uses an unorthodox HTML smuggling technique where the malicious payload is embedded in a separate JSON file hosted on an external website," Netskope Threat Labs]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Admins Urged to Remove miniOrange Plugins Due to Critical Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/wordpress-admins-urged-to-remove.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/wordpress-admins-urged-to-remove.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress users of miniOrange's Malware Scanner and Web Application Firewall plugins are being urged to delete them from their websites following the discovery of a critical security flaw.
The flaw, tracked as CVE-2024-2172, is rated 9.8 out of a maximum of 10 on the CVSS scoring system. It impacts the following versions of the two plugins -

Malware Scanner (versions <= 4.7.2)
Web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0229 : Vulnérabilité dans Tenable Nessus (18 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0229/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0229/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T08:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Tenable Nessus. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[APT28 Hacker Group Targeting Europe, Americas, Asia in Widespread Phishing Scheme]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/apt28-hacker-group-targeting-europe.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/apt28-hacker-group-targeting-europe.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-18T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russia-linked threat actor known as APT28 has been linked to multiple ongoing phishing campaigns that employ lure documents imitating government and non-governmental organizations (NGOs) in Europe, the South Caucasus, Central Asia, and North and South America.
"The uncovered lures include a mixture of internal and publicly available documents, as well as possible actor-generated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Using Cracked Software on GitHub to Spread RisePro Info Stealer]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-using-cracked-software-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-using-cracked-software-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-16T12:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have found a number of GitHub repositories offering cracked software that are used to deliver an information stealer called RisePro.
The campaign, codenamed gitgub, includes 17 repositories associated with 11 different accounts, according to G DATA. The repositories in question have since been taken down by the Microsoft-owned subsidiary.
"The repositories look]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GhostRace – New Data Leak Vulnerability Affects Modern CPUs]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ghostrace-new-data-leak-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ghostrace-new-data-leak-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T17:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A group of researchers has discovered a new data leakage attack impacting modern CPU architectures supporting speculative execution.
Dubbed GhostRace (CVE-2024-2193), it is a variation of the transient execution CPU vulnerability known as Spectre v1 (CVE-2017-5753). The approach combines speculative execution and race conditions.
"All the common synchronization primitives implemented]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0228 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0228/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0228/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T13:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0227 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0227/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0227/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T12:54:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0226 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0226/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0226/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T12:53:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Third-Party ChatGPT Plugins Could Lead to Account Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/third-party-chatgpt-plugins-could-lead.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/third-party-chatgpt-plugins-could-lead.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T11:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have found that third-party plugins available for OpenAI ChatGPT could act as a new attack surface for threat actors looking to gain unauthorized access to sensitive data.
According to new research published by Salt Labs, security flaws found directly in ChatGPT and within the ecosystem could allow attackers to install malicious plugins without users' consent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0225 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0225/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0225/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T08:26:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Juniper Secure Analytics. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0224 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0224/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0224/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T08:11:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une usurpation d'identité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0223 : Vulnérabilité dans Spring Framework (15 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0223/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0223/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T08:08:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Framework. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Introduces Enhanced Real-Time URL Protection for Chrome Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/google-introduces-enhanced-real-time.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/google-introduces-enhanced-real-time.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T07:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Thursday announced an enhanced version of Safe Browsing to provide real-time, privacy-preserving URL protection and safeguard users from visiting potentially malicious sites.
“The Standard protection mode for Chrome on desktop and iOS will check sites against Google’s server-side list of known bad sites in real-time,” Google’s Jonathan Li and Jasika Bawa said.
“If we]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious Ads Targeting Chinese Users with Fake Notepad++ and VNote Installers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malicious-ads-targeting-chinese-users.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malicious-ads-targeting-chinese-users.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-15T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese users looking for legitimate software such as Notepad++ and VNote on search engines like Baidu are being targeted with malicious ads and bogus links to distribute trojanized versions of the software and ultimately deploy Geacon, a Golang-based implementation of Cobalt Strike.
“The malicious site found in the notepad++ search is distributed through an advertisement block,” Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LockBit Ransomware Hacker Ordered to Pay $860,000 After Guilty Plea in Canada]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/lockbit-ransomware-hacker-ordered-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/lockbit-ransomware-hacker-ordered-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T13:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 34-year-old Russian-Canadian national has been sentenced to nearly four years in jail in Canada for his participation in the LockBit global ransomware operation.
Mikhail Vasiliev, an Ontario resident, was originally arrested in November 2022 and charged by the U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) with "conspiring with others to intentionally damage protected computers and to transmit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0222 : Vulnérabilité dans Synology Router Manager (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0222/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0222/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T13:20:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synology Router Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Detail Kubernetes Vulnerability That Enables Windows Node Takeover]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/researchers-detail-kubernetes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/researchers-detail-kubernetes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T11:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have been made public about a now-patched high-severity flaw in Kubernetes that could allow a malicious attacker to achieve remote code execution with elevated privileges under specific circumstances.
“The vulnerability allows remote code execution with SYSTEM privileges on all Windows endpoints within a Kubernetes cluster,” Akamai security researcher Tomer Peled said. “To exploit]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[3 Things CISOs Achieve with Cato]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/3-things-cisos-achieve-with-cato.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/3-things-cisos-achieve-with-cato.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T10:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Being a CISO is a balancing act: ensuring organizations are secure without compromising users’ productivity. This requires taking multiple elements into consideration, like cost, complexity, performance and user experience. CISOs around the globe use Cato SSE 360, as part of the Cato SASE Cloud platform to balance these factors without compromise.
This article details how CISOs are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RedCurl Cybercrime Group Abuses Windows PCA Tool for Corporate Espionage]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/redcurl-cybercrime-group-abuses-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/redcurl-cybercrime-group-abuses-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T10:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Russian-speaking cybercrime group called RedCurl is leveraging a legitimate Microsoft Windows component called the Program Compatibility Assistant (PCA) to execute malicious commands.

“The Program Compatibility Assistant Service (pcalua.exe) is a Windows service designed to identify and address compatibility issues with older programs,” Trend Micro said in an analysis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0221 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0221/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0221/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T09:22:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0220 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Cisco IOS XR (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0220/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0220/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T09:21:35.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Cisco IOS XR. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0219 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Mitel (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0219/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0219/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:50:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Mitel. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0218 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Apache Tomcat (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0218/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0218/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:47:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Apache Tomcat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0217 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans SonicWall (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0217/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0217/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T08:45:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans SonicWall. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0216 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Xen (14 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0216/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0216/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T07:42:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Xen. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ande Loader Malware Targets Manufacturing Sector in North America]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ande-loader-malware-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ande-loader-malware-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T07:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Blind Eagle has been observed using a loader malware called Ande Loader to deliver remote access trojans (RATs) like Remcos RAT and NjRAT.

The attacks, which take the form of phishing emails, targeted Spanish-speaking users in the manufacturing industry based in North America, eSentire said.

Blind Eagle (aka APT-C-36) is a financially motivated threat actor&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DarkGate Malware Exploits Recently Patched Microsoft Flaw in Zero-Day Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/darkgate-malware-exploits-recently.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/darkgate-malware-exploits-recently.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T04:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A DarkGate malware campaign observed in mid-January 2024 leveraged a recently patched security flaw in Microsoft Windows as a zero-day using bogus software installers.
“During this campaign, users were lured using PDFs that contained Google DoubleClick Digital Marketing (DDM) open redirects that led unsuspecting victims to compromised sites hosting the Microsoft Windows SmartScreen bypass]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet Warns of Severe SQLi Vulnerability in FortiClientEMS Software]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/fortinet-warns-of-severe-sqli.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/fortinet-warns-of-severe-sqli.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-14T04:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Fortinet has warned of a critical security flaw impacting its FortiClientEMS software that could allow attackers to achieve code execution on affected systems.
"An improper neutralization of special elements used in an SQL Command ('SQL Injection') vulnerability [CWE-89] in FortiClientEMS may allow an unauthenticated attacker to execute unauthorized code or commands via specifically crafted]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Demystifying a Common Cybersecurity Myth]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/demystifying-common-cybersecurity-myth.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/demystifying-common-cybersecurity-myth.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[One of the most common misconceptions in file upload cybersecurity is that certain tools are “enough” on their own—this is simply not the case. In our latest whitepaper OPSWAT CEO and Founder, Benny Czarny, takes a comprehensive look at what it takes to prevent malware threats in today’s ever-evolving file upload security landscape, and a big part of that is understanding where the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[PixPirate Android Banking Trojan Using New Evasion Tactic to Target Brazilian Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/pixpirate-android-banking-trojan-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/pixpirate-android-banking-trojan-using.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the PixPirate Android banking trojan are leveraging a new trick to evade detection on compromised devices and harvest sensitive information from users in Brazil.
The approach allows it to hide the malicious app’s icon from the home screen of the victim’s device, IBM said in a technical report published today.
“Thanks to this new technique, during PixPirate reconnaissance]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0215 : Vulnérabilité dans Adobe ColdFusion (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0215/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0215/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:35:39.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Adobe ColdFusion. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0214 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Stormshield Network Security (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0214/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0214/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T13:20:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Stormshield Network Security. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0213 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0213/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0213/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T11:26:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0212 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0212/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0212/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T11:13:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Join Our Webinar on Protecting Human and Non-Human Identities in SaaS Platforms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/join-our-webinar-on-protecting-human.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/join-our-webinar-on-protecting-human.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T10:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Identities are the latest sweet spot for cybercriminals, now heavily targeting SaaS applications that are especially vulnerable in this attack vector. 
The use of SaaS applications involves a wide range of identities, including human and non-human, such as service accounts, API keys, and OAuth authorizations. Consequently, any identity in a SaaS app can create an opening for cybercriminals to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Researchers Highlight Google's Gemini AI Susceptibility to LLM Threats]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/researchers-highlight-googles-gemini-ai.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/researchers-highlight-googles-gemini-ai.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T10:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Gemini large language model (LLM) is susceptible to security threats that could cause it to divulge system prompts, generate harmful content, and carry out indirect injection attacks.
The findings come from HiddenLayer, which said the issues impact consumers using Gemini Advanced with Google Workspace as well as companies using the LLM API.
The first vulnerability involves]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0211 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0211/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0211/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T10:11:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0210 : Vulnérabilité dans Google Chrome (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0210/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0210/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T09:58:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Google Chrome. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: Cybercriminals Deploying VCURMS and STRRAT Trojans via AWS and GitHub]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-cybercriminals-deploying-vcurms.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-cybercriminals-deploying-vcurms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new phishing campaign has been observed delivering remote access trojans (RAT) such as VCURMS and STRRAT by means of a malicious Java-based downloader.
“The attackers stored malware on public services like Amazon Web Services (AWS) and GitHub, employing a commercial protector to avoid detection of the malware,” Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researcher Yurren Wan said.
An unusual aspect of the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0209 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0209/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0209/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:53:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0208 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0208/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0208/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:38:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0207 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0207/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0207/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:38:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une usurpation d'identité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0206 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft .Net (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0206/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0206/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:38:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft .Net. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0205 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0205/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0205/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:38:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0204 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (13 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0204/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0204/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T08:38:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft's March Updates Fix 61 Vulnerabilities, Including Critical Hyper-V Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsofts-march-updates-fix-61.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsofts-march-updates-fix-61.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-13T05:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Tuesday released its monthly security update, addressing 61 different security flaws spanning its software, including two critical issues impacting Windows Hyper-V that could lead to denial-of-service (DoS) and remote code execution.
Of the 61 vulnerabilities, two are rated Critical, 58 are rated Important, and one is rated Low in severity. None of the flaws are listed as]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0203 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (12 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0203/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0203/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:35:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out: These PyPI Python Packages Can Drain Your Crypto Wallets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/watch-out-these-pypi-python-packages.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/watch-out-these-pypi-python-packages.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T12:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have discovered a set of seven packages on the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository that are designed to steal BIP39 mnemonic phrases used for recovering private keys of a cryptocurrency wallet.
The software supply chain attack campaign has been codenamed BIPClip by ReversingLabs. The packages were collectively downloaded 7,451 times prior to them being removed from]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CTEM 101 - Go Beyond Vulnerability Management with Continuous Threat Exposure Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ctem-101-go-beyond-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ctem-101-go-beyond-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T11:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a world of ever-expanding jargon, adding another FLA (Four-Letter Acronym) to your glossary might seem like the last thing you’d want to do. But if you are looking for ways to continuously reduce risk across your environment while making significant and consistent improvements to security posture, in our opinion, you probably want to consider establishing a Continuous Threat Exposure]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0202 : [SCADA] Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Schneider (12 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0202/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0202/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T09:15:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Schneider. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware Campaign Exploits Popup Builder WordPress Plugin to Infect 3,900+ Sites]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malware-campaign-exploits-popup-builder.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/malware-campaign-exploits-popup-builder.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T09:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware campaign is leveraging a high-severity security flaw in the Popup Builder plugin for WordPress to inject malicious JavaScript code.
According to Sucuri, the campaign has infected more than 3,900 sites over the past three weeks.
"These attacks are orchestrated from domains less than a month old, with registrations dating back to February 12th, 2024," security researcher]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[South Korean Citizen Detained in Russia on Cyber Espionage Charges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/south-korean-citizen-detained-in-russia.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/south-korean-citizen-detained-in-russia.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-12T06:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russia has detained a South Korean national for the first time on cyber espionage charges and transferred from Vladivostok to Moscow for further investigation.
The development was first reported by Russian news agency TASS.
“During the investigation of an espionage case, a South Korean citizen Baek Won-soon was identified and detained in Vladivostok, and put into custody under a court]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Embracing the Cloud: Revolutionizing Privileged Access Management with One Identity PAM Essentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/embracing-cloud-revolutionizing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/embracing-cloud-revolutionizing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As cyber threats loom around every corner and privileged accounts become prime targets, the significance of implementing a robust Privileged Access Management (PAM) solution can't be overstated. With organizations increasingly migrating to cloud environments, the PAM Solution Market is experiencing a transformative shift toward cloud-based offerings. One Identity PAM Essentials stands]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Banking Trojan CHAVECLOAK Targets Brazilian Users via Phishing Tactics]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-banking-trojan-chavecloak-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-banking-trojan-chavecloak-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T14:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Users in Brazil are the target of a new banking trojan known as CHAVECLOAK that's propagated via phishing emails bearing PDF attachments.
"This intricate attack involves the PDF downloading a ZIP file and subsequently utilizing DLL side-loading techniques to execute the final malware," Fortinet FortiGuard Labs researcher Cara Lin said.
The attack chain involves the use of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Data Leakage Prevention in the Age of Cloud Computing: A New Approach]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/data-leakage-prevention-in-age-of-cloud.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/data-leakage-prevention-in-age-of-cloud.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As the shift of IT infrastructure to cloud-based solutions celebrates its 10-year anniversary, it becomes clear that traditional on-premises approaches to data security are becoming obsolete. Rather than protecting the endpoint, DLP solutions need to refocus their efforts to where corporate data resides - in the browser.
A new guide by LayerX titled "On-Prem is Dead. Have You Adjusted Your Web]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[BianLian Threat Actors Exploiting JetBrains TeamCity Flaws in Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/bianlian-threat-actors-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/bianlian-threat-actors-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T09:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the BianLian ransomware have been observed exploiting security flaws in JetBrains TeamCity software to conduct their extortion-only attacks.
According to a new report from GuidePoint Security, which responded to a recent intrusion, the incident "began with the exploitation of a TeamCity server which resulted in the deployment of a PowerShell implementation of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0201 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (11 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0201/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0201/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T09:32:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS), et une atteinte à la …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0200 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits MongoDB (11 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0200/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0200/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T09:18:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits MongoDB. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-012 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-012 (11 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-012/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-012/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T08:49:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Proof-of-Concept Exploit Released for Progress Software OpenEdge Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/proof-of-concept-exploit-released-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/proof-of-concept-exploit-released-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T06:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Technical specifics and a proof-of-concept (PoC) exploit have been made available for a recently disclosed critical security flaw in Progress Software OpenEdge Authentication Gateway and AdminServer, which could be potentially exploited to bypass authentication protections.
Tracked as CVE-2024-1403, the vulnerability has a maximum severity rating of 10.0 on the CVSS scoring system. It]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Magnet Goblin Hacker Group Leveraging 1-Day Exploits to Deploy Nerbian RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/magnet-goblin-hacker-group-leveraging-1.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/magnet-goblin-hacker-group-leveraging-1.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-11T05:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A financially motivated threat actor called Magnet Goblin is swiftly adopting one-day security vulnerabilities into its arsenal in order to opportunistically breach edge devices and public-facing services and deploy malware on compromised hosts.
“Threat actor group Magnet Goblin’s hallmark is its ability to swiftly leverage newly disclosed vulnerabilities, particularly targeting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Confirms Russian Hackers Stole Source Code, Some Customer Secrets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsoft-confirms-russian-hackers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/microsoft-confirms-russian-hackers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-09T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Friday revealed that the Kremlin-backed threat actor known as Midnight Blizzard (aka APT29 or Cozy Bear) managed to gain access to some of its source code repositories and internal systems following a hack that came to light in January 2024.
"In recent weeks, we have seen evidence that Midnight Blizzard is using information initially exfiltrated from our]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0199 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans IBM (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0199/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0199/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:23:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0198 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0198/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0198/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:13:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0197 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0197/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0197/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:13:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0196 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0196/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0196/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T14:12:55.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0195 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0195/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0195/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:34:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta Details WhatsApp and Messenger Interoperability to Comply with EU's DMA Regulations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/meta-details-whatsapp-and-messenger.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/meta-details-whatsapp-and-messenger.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T13:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has offered details on how it intends to implement interoperability in WhatsApp and Messenger with third-party messaging services as the Digital Markets Act (DMA) went into effect in the European Union.
“This allows users of third-party providers who choose to enable interoperability (interop) to send and receive messages with opted-in users of either Messenger or WhatsApp – both designated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets Sensei: Conquering Secrets Management Challenges]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/secrets-sensei-conquering-secrets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/secrets-sensei-conquering-secrets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the realm of cybersecurity, the stakes are sky-high, and at its core lies secrets management — the foundational pillar upon which your security infrastructure rests. We're all familiar with the routine: safeguarding those API keys, connection strings, and certificates is non-negotiable. However, let's dispense with the pleasantries; this isn't a simple 'set it and forget it' scenario. It's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0194 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0194/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0194/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T09:02:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0193 : Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (08 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0193/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0193/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T08:56:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Issues Patch for High-Severity VPN Hijacking Bug in Secure Client]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisco-issues-patch-for-high-severity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisco-issues-patch-for-high-severity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T08:09:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released patches to address a high-severity security flaw impacting its Secure Client software that could be exploited by a threat actor to open a VPN session with that of a targeted user.
The networking equipment company described the vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-20337 (CVSS score: 8.2), as allowing an unauthenticated, remote attacker to conduct a carriage return line feed (CRLF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[QEMU Emulator Exploited as Tunneling Tool to Breach Company Network]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cybercriminals-utilize-qemu-emulator-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cybercriminals-utilize-qemu-emulator-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T07:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed leveraging the QEMU open-source hardware emulator as tunneling software during a cyber attack targeting an unnamed "large company" to connect to their infrastructure.
While a number of legitimate tunneling tools like Chisel, FRP, ligolo, ngrok, and Plink have been used by adversaries to their advantage, the development marks the first QEMU that has been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Warns of Actively Exploited JetBrains TeamCity Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cisa-warns-of-actively-exploited.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-08T06:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Thursday added a critical security flaw impacting JetBrains TeamCity On-Premises software to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-27198 (CVSS score: 9.8), refers to an authentication bypass bug that allows for a complete]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacked WordPress Sites Abusing Visitors' Browsers for Distributed Brute-Force Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hacked-wordpress-sites-abusing-visitors.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hacked-wordpress-sites-abusing-visitors.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are conducting brute-force attacks against WordPress sites by leveraging malicious JavaScript injections, new findings from Sucuri reveal.
The attacks, which take the form of distributed brute-force attacks, “target WordPress websites from the browsers of completely innocent and unsuspecting site visitors,” security researcher Denis Sinegubko said.
The activity is part of a&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese State Hackers Target Tibetans with Supply Chain, Watering Hole Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/chinese-state-hackers-target-tibetans.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/chinese-state-hackers-target-tibetans.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked threat actor known as Evasive Panda orchestrated both watering hole and supply chain attacks targeting Tibetan users at least since September 2023.
The end of the attacks is to deliver malicious downloaders for Windows and macOS that deploy a known backdoor called MgBot and a previously undocumented Windows implant known as Nightdoor.
The findings come from ESET, which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0192 : Vulnérabilité dans VMware Cloud Director (07 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0192/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0192/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T13:21:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Cloud Director. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Human vs. Non-Human Identity in SaaS]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/human-vs-non-human-identity-in-saas.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/human-vs-non-human-identity-in-saas.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's rapidly evolving SaaS environment, the focus is on human users. This is one of the most compromised areas in SaaS security management and requires strict governance of user roles and permissions, monitoring of privileged users, their level of activity (dormant, active, hyperactive), their type (internal/ external), whether they are joiners, movers, or leavers, and more. 
Not]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Google Engineer Arrested for Stealing AI Technology Secrets for China]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ex-google-engineer-arrested-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/ex-google-engineer-arrested-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T10:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) announced the indictment of a 38-year-old Chinese national and a California resident of allegedly stealing proprietary information from Google while covertly working for two China-based tech companies.
Linwei Ding (aka Leon Ding), a former Google engineer who was arrested on March 6, 2024, "transferred sensitive Google trade secrets and other confidential]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0191 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (07 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0191/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0191/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T08:15:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0190 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (07 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0190/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0190/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T07:52:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Python-Based Snake Info Stealer Spreading Through Facebook Messages]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-python-based-snake-info-stealer.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-python-based-snake-info-stealer.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T07:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Facebook messages are being used by threat actors to a Python-based information stealer dubbed Snake that’s designed to capture credentials and other sensitive data.
“The credentials harvested from unsuspecting users are transmitted to different platforms such as Discord, GitHub, and Telegram,” Cybereason researcher Kotaro Ogino said in a technical report.
Details about the campaign&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watch Out for Spoofed Zoom, Skype, Google Meet Sites Delivering Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/watch-out-for-spoofed-zoom-skype-google.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/watch-out-for-spoofed-zoom-skype-google.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-07T06:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been leveraging fake websites advertising popular video conferencing software such as Google Meet, Skype, and Zoom to deliver a variety of malware targeting both Android and Windows users since December 2023.
“The threat actor is distributing Remote Access Trojans (RATs) including SpyNote RAT for Android platforms, and NjRAT and DCRat for Windows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Misconfigured YARN, Docker, Confluence, Redis Servers for Crypto Mining]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-yarn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploit-misconfigured-yarn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T16:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are targeting misconfigured and vulnerable servers running Apache Hadoop YARN, Docker, Atlassian Confluence, and Redis services as part of an emerging malware campaign designed to deliver a cryptocurrency miner and spawn a reverse shell for persistent remote access.
“The attackers leverage these tools to issue exploit code, taking advantage of common misconfigurations and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exit Scam: BlackCat Ransomware Group Vanishes After $22 Million Payout]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/exit-scam-blackcat-ransomware-group.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/exit-scam-blackcat-ransomware-group.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actors behind the BlackCat ransomware have shut down their darknet website and likely pulled an exit scam after uploading a bogus law enforcement seizure banner.
"ALPHV/BlackCat did not get seized. They are exit scamming their affiliates," security researcher Fabian Wosar said. "It is blatantly obvious when you check the source code of the new takedown notice."
"There]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[A New Way To Manage Your Web Exposure: The Reflectiz Product Explained]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/a-new-way-to-manage-your-web-exposure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/a-new-way-to-manage-your-web-exposure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T11:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An in-depth look into a proactive website security solution that continuously detects, prioritizes, and validates web threats, helping to mitigate security, privacy, and compliance risks. 
[Reflectiz shields websites from client-side attacks, supply chain risks, data breaches, privacy violations, and compliance issues]
You Can’t Protect What You Can’t See
Today’s websites are connected]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Find and Fix Risky Sharing in Google Drive]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-to-find-and-fix-risky-sharing-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-to-find-and-fix-risky-sharing-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T09:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Every Google Workspace administrator knows how quickly Google Drive becomes a messy sprawl of loosely shared confidential information. This isn't anyone's fault; it’s inevitable as your productivity suite is purposefully designed to enable real-time collaboration – both internally and externally. 
For Security & Risk Management teams, the untenable risk of any Google Drive footprint]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0189 : [SCADA] Vulnérabilité dans Moxa NPort W2150A/W2250A Series (06 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0189/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0189/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T09:00:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Moxa NPort W2150A/W2250A Series. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0188 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (06 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0188/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0188/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:59:27.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0187 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (06 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0187/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0187/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T08:40:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0186 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits VMware (06 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0186/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0186/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:41:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Cracks Down on Predatory Spyware Firm for Targeting Officials and Journalists]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-cracks-down-on-predatory-spyware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-cracks-down-on-predatory-spyware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Treasury’s Office of Foreign Assets Control (OFAC) sanctioned two individuals and five entities associated with the Intellexa Alliance for their role in “developing, operating, and distributing” commercial spyware designed to target government officials, journalists, and policy experts in the country.
“The proliferation of commercial spyware poses distinct and growing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[VMware Issues Security Patches for ESXi, Workstation, and Fusion Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/vmware-issues-security-patches-for-esxi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/vmware-issues-security-patches-for-esxi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[VMware has released patches to address four security flaws impacting ESXi, Workstation, and Fusion, including two critical flaws that could lead to code execution.
Tracked as CVE-2024-22252 and CVE-2024-22253, the vulnerabilities have been described as use-after-free bugs in the XHCI USB controller. They carry a CVSS score of 9.3 for Workstation and Fusion, and 8.4 for ESXi systems.
"A]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Alert: GhostSec and Stormous Launch Joint Ransomware Attacks in Over 15 Countries]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-ghostsec-and-stormous-launch.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/alert-ghostsec-and-stormous-launch.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cybercrime group called GhostSec has been linked to a Golang variant of a ransomware family called GhostLocker.
“TheGhostSec and Stormous ransomware groups are jointly conducting double extortion ransomware attacks on various business verticals in multiple countries,” Cisco Talos researcher Chetan Raghuprasad said in a report shared with The Hacker News.
“GhostLocker and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0185 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (06 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0185/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0185/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:07:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.
 D'après l'éditeur, les vulnérabilités …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New APT Group 'Lotus Bane' Behind Recent Attacks on Vietnam's Financial Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-apt-group-lotus-bane-behind-recent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-apt-group-lotus-bane-behind-recent.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T07:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A financial entity in Vietnam was the target of a previously undocumented threat actor called Lotus Bane that was first detected in March 2023.
Singapore-headquartered Group-IB described the hacking outfit as an advanced persistent threat group that's believed to have been active since at least 2022.
The exact specifics of the infection chain remain unknown as yet, but it involves the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urgent: Apple Issues Critical Updates for Actively Exploited Zero-Day Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/urgent-apple-issues-critical-updates.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/urgent-apple-issues-critical-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-06T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has released security updates to address several security flaws, including two vulnerabilities that it said have been actively exploited in the wild.
The shortcomings are listed below -

CVE-2024-23225 - A memory corruption issue in Kernel that an attacker with arbitrary kernel read and write capability can exploit to bypass kernel memory protections


CVE-2024-23296 - A memory]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit ConnectWise ScreenConnect Flaws to Deploy TODDLERSHARK Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploit-connectwise.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/hackers-exploit-connectwise.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T16:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors have exploited the recently disclosed security flaws in ConnectWise ScreenConnect to deploy a new malware called TODDLERSHARK.
According to a report shared by Kroll with The Hacker News, TODDLERSHARK overlaps with known Kimsuky malware such as BabyShark and ReconShark.
“The threat actor gained access to the victim workstation by exploiting the exposed setup wizard]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0184 : Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Security Event Manager (05 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0184/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0184/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T12:09:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Security Event Manger (SEM). Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[What is Exposure Management and How Does it Differ from ASM?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/what-is-exposure-management-and-how.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/what-is-exposure-management-and-how.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Startups and scales-ups are often cloud-first organizations and rarely have sprawling legacy on-prem environments. Likewise, knowing the agility and flexibility that cloud environments provide, the mid-market is predominantly running in a hybrid state, partly in the cloud but with some on-prem assets.
While there has been a bit of a backswing against the pricing and lock-in presented when using]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Using Novel DNS Hijacking Technique for Investment Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cybercriminals-using-novel-dns.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/cybercriminals-using-novel-dns.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new DNS threat actor dubbed Savvy Seahorse is leveraging sophisticated techniques to entice targets into fake investment platforms and steal funds.
“Savvy Seahorse is a DNS threat actor who convinces victims to create accounts on fake investment platforms, make deposits to a personal account, and then transfers those deposits to a bank in Russia,” Infoblox said in a report]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 225,000 Compromised ChatGPT Credentials Up for Sale on Dark Web Markets]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-225000-compromised-chatgpt.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-225000-compromised-chatgpt.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than 225,000 logs containing compromised OpenAI ChatGPT credentials were made available for sale on underground markets between January and October 2023, new findings from Group-IB show.
These credentials were found within information stealer logs associated with LummaC2, Raccoon, and RedLine stealer malware.
“The number of infected devices decreased slightly in mid- and late]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Warning: Thread Hijacking Attack Targets IT Networks, Stealing NTLM Hashes]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/warning-thread-hijacking-attack-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/warning-thread-hijacking-attack-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T10:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as TA577 has been observed using ZIP archive attachments in phishing emails with an aim to steal NT LAN Manager (NTLM) hashes.
The new attack chain “can be used for sensitive information gathering purposes and to enable follow-on activity,” enterprise security firm Proofpoint said in a Monday report.
At least two campaigns taking advantage of this]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0183 : Vulnérabilité dans Mozilla Thunderbird (05 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0183/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0183/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T08:44:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Mozilla. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0182 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits Squid (05 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0182/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0182/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T08:41:53.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Squid. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0181 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Android (05 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0181/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0181/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T08:00:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Android. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical JetBrains TeamCity On-Premises Flaws Could Lead to Server Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/critical-jetbrains-teamcity-on-premises.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/critical-jetbrains-teamcity-on-premises.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-05T03:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new pair of security vulnerabilities have been disclosed in JetBrains TeamCity On-Premises software that could be exploited by a threat actor to take control of affected systems.
The flaws, tracked as CVE-2024-27198 (CVSS score: 9.8) and CVE-2024-27199 (CVSS score: 7.3), have been addressed in version 2023.11.4. They impact all TeamCity On-Premises versions through 2023.11.3.
“The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How Cybercriminals are Exploiting India's UPI for Money Laundering Operations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-cybercriminals-are-exploiting.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/how-cybercriminals-are-exploiting.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T13:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals are using a network of hired money mules in India using an Android-based application to orchestrate a massive money laundering scheme.
The malicious application, called XHelper, is a "key tool for onboarding and managing these money mules," CloudSEK researchers Sparsh Kulshrestha, Abhishek Mathew, and Santripti Bhujel said in a report.
Details about the scam]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-ACT-011 : Bulletin d’actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-011 (04 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-011/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-011/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T12:55:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas …]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From 500 to 5000 Employees - Securing 3rd Party App-Usage in Mid-Market Companies]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/from-500-to-5000-employees-securing-3rd.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/from-500-to-5000-employees-securing-3rd.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T11:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A company’s lifecycle stage, size, and state have a significant impact on its security needs, policies, and priorities. This is particularly true for modern mid-market companies that are either experiencing or have experienced rapid growth. As requirements and tasks continue to accumulate and malicious actors remain active around the clock, budgets are often stagnant at best. Yet, it is crucial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Over 100 Malicious AI/ML Models Found on Hugging Face Platform]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-100-malicious-aiml-models-found-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/over-100-malicious-aiml-models-found-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T09:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 100 malicious artificial intelligence (AI)/machine learning (ML) models have been discovered in the Hugging Face platform.
These include instances where loading a pickle file leads to code execution, software supply chain security firm JFrog said.
"The model's payload grants the attacker a shell on the compromised machine, enabling them to gain full control over victims']]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Phobos Ransomware Aggressively Targeting U.S. Critical Infrastructure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/phobos-ransomware-aggressively.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/phobos-ransomware-aggressively.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-04T05:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. cybersecurity and intelligence agencies have warned of Phobos ransomware attacks targeting government and critical infrastructure entities, outlining the various tactics and techniques the threat actors have adopted to deploy the file-encrypting malware.
“Structured as a ransomware as a service (RaaS) model, Phobos ransomware actors have targeted entities including municipal and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Court Orders NSO Group to Hand Over Pegasus Spyware Code to WhatsApp]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-court-orders-nso-group-to-hand-over.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-court-orders-nso-group-to-hand-over.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T06:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A U.S. judge has ordered NSO Group to hand over its source code for Pegasus and other products to Meta as part of the social media giant's ongoing litigation against the Israeli spyware vendor.
The decision, which marks a major legal victory for Meta, which filed the lawsuit in October 2019 for using its infrastructure to distribute the spyware to approximately]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Charges Iranian Hacker, Offers $10 Million Reward for Capture]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-charges-iranian-hacker-offers-10.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/us-charges-iranian-hacker-offers-10.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-02T04:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Friday unsealed an indictment against an Iranian national for his alleged involvement in a multi-year cyber-enabled campaign designed to compromise U.S. governmental and private entities.
More than a dozen entities are said to have been targeted, including the U.S. Departments of the Treasury and State, defense contractors that support U.S. Department of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0180 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0180/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0180/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T13:41:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Phishing Kit Leverages SMS, Voice Calls to Target Cryptocurrency Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-phishing-kit-leverages-sms-voice.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-phishing-kit-leverages-sms-voice.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T13:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel phishing kit has been observed impersonating the login pages of well-known cryptocurrency services as part of an attack cluster designed to primarily target mobile devices.
“This kit enables attackers to build carbon copies of single sign-on (SSO) pages, then use a combination of email, SMS, and voice phishing to trick the target into sharing usernames, passwords, password reset URLs,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0179 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0179/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0179/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T13:24:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0178 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d’Ubuntu (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0178/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0178/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T13:05:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0177 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de RedHat (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0177/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0177/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T13:01:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de RedHat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une élévation de privilèges et une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[4 Instructive Postmortems on Data Downtime and Loss]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/4-instructive-postmortems-on-data.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/4-instructive-postmortems-on-data.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T11:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[More than a decade ago, the concept of the ‘blameless’ postmortem changed how tech companies recognize failures at scale.
John Allspaw, who coined the term during his tenure at Etsy, argued postmortems were all about controlling our natural reaction to an incident, which is to point fingers: “One option is to assume the single cause is incompetence and scream at engineers to make them]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New BIFROSE Linux Malware Variant Using Deceptive VMware Domain for Evasion]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-bifrose-linux-malware-variant-using.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/new-bifrose-linux-malware-variant-using.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T10:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new Linux variant of a remote access trojan (RAT) called BIFROSE (aka Bifrost) that uses a deceptive domain mimicking VMware.
"This latest version of Bifrost aims to bypass security measures and compromise targeted systems," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 researchers Anmol Maurya and Siddharth Sharma said.
BIFROSE is one of the long-standing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0176 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Mitel MiContact Center Business (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0176/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0176/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T08:27:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Mitel MiContact Center Business . Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0175 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (01 mars 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0175/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0175/"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T08:21:37.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Five Eyes Agencies Warn of Active Exploitation of Ivanti Gateway Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/five-eyes-agencies-warn-of-active.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/five-eyes-agencies-warn-of-active.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T06:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Five Eyes (FVEY) intelligence alliance has issued a new cybersecurity advisory warning of cyber threat actors exploiting known security flaws in Ivanti Connect Secure and Ivanti Policy Secure gateways, noting that the Integrity Checker Tool (ICT) can be deceived to provide a false sense of security.
"Ivanti ICT is not sufficient to detect compromise and that a cyber threat actor may be able]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Rolls Out Default Secret Scanning Push Protection for Public Repositories]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/github-rolls-out-default-secret.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/03/github-rolls-out-default-secret.html"/>
        <updated>2024-03-01T05:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub on Thursday announced that it’s enabling secret scanning push protection by default for all pushes to public repositories.
“This means that when a supported secret is detected in any push to a public repository, you will have the option to remove the secret from your commits or, if you deem the secret safe, bypass the block,” Eric Tooley and Courtney Claessens said.
Push protection&]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Silver SAML Attack Evades Golden SAML Defenses in Identity Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-silver-saml-attack-evades-golden.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-silver-saml-attack-evades-golden.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T15:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a new attack technique called Silver SAML that can be successful even in cases where mitigations have been applied against Golden SAML attacks.
Silver SAML “enables the exploitation of SAML to launch attacks from an identity provider like Entra ID against applications configured to use it for authentication, such as Salesforce,” Semperis]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GTPDOOR Linux Malware Targets Telecoms, Exploiting GPRS Roaming Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/gtpdoor-linux-malware-targets-telecoms.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/gtpdoor-linux-malware-targets-telecoms.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat hunters have discovered a new Linux malware called GTPDOOR that’s designed to be deployed in telecom networks that are adjacent to GPRS roaming exchanges (GRX)
The malware is novel in the fact that it leverages the GPRS Tunnelling Protocol (GTP) for command-and-control (C2) communications.
GPRS roaming allows subscribers to access their GPRS services while they are]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Prioritize Cybersecurity Spending: A Risk-Based Strategy for the Highest ROI]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-risk-based-approach-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/why-risk-based-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As an IT leader, staying on top of the latest cybersecurity developments is essential to keeping your organization safe. But with threats coming from all around — and hackers dreaming up new exploits every day — how do you create proactive, agile cybersecurity strategies? And what cybersecurity approach gives you the most bang for your buck, mitigating your risks and maximizing the value of your]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Hackers Exploited Windows Kernel Flaw as Zero-Day in Recent Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lazarus-hackers-exploited-windows.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lazarus-hackers-exploited-windows.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T11:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious Lazarus Group actors exploited a recently patched privilege escalation flaw in the Windows Kernel as a zero-day to obtain kernel-level access and disable security software on compromised hosts.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-21338 (CVSS score: 7.8), which can permit an attacker to gain SYSTEM privileges. It was resolved by Microsoft earlier this month as part]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0174 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Cisco NX-OS (29 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0174/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0174/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T10:33:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Cisco NX-OS. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0173 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (29 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0173/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0173/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T08:45:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Juniper Secure Analytics . Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Backdoor Targeting European Officials Linked to Indian Diplomatic Events]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-backdoor-targeting-european.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/new-backdoor-targeting-european.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T08:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat actor dubbed SPIKEDWINE has been observed targeting officials in European countries with Indian diplomatic missions using a new backdoor called WINELOADER.
The adversary, according to a report from Zscaler ThreatLabz, used a PDF file in emails that purported to come from the Ambassador of India, inviting diplomatic staff to a wine-tasting]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Lazarus Exploits Typos to Sneak PyPI Malware into Dev Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lazarus-exploits-typos-to-sneak-pypi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/lazarus-exploits-typos-to-sneak-pypi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T08:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The notorious North Korean state-backed hacking group Lazarus uploaded four packages to the Python Package Index (PyPI) repository with the goal of infecting developer systems with malware.
The packages, now taken down, are pycryptoenv, pycryptoconf, quasarlib, and swapmempool. They have been collectively downloaded 3,269 times, with pycryptoconf accounting for the most]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploiting Ivanti VPN Flaws to Deploy New Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-exploiting-ivanti-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/chinese-hackers-exploiting-ivanti-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T05:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[At least two different suspected China-linked cyber espionage clusters, tracked as UNC5325 and UNC3886, have been attributed to the exploitation of security flaws in Ivanti Connect Secure VPN appliances.
UNC5325 abused CVE-2024-21893 to deliver a wide range of new malware called LITTLELAMB.WOOLTEA, PITSTOP, PITDOG, PITJET, and PITHOOK, as well as maintain persistent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[President Biden Blocks Mass Transfer of Personal Data to High-Risk Nations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/president-biden-blocks-mass-transfer-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/president-biden-blocks-mass-transfer-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-29T05:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. President Joe Biden has issued an Executive Order that prohibits the mass transfer of citizens' personal data to countries of concern.
The Executive Order also "provides safeguards around other activities that can give those countries access to Americans' sensitive data," the White House said in a statement.
This includes sensitive information such as genomic data, biometric data,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iran-Linked UNC1549 Hackers Target Middle East Aerospace & Defense Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iran-linked-unc1549-hackers-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/iran-linked-unc1549-hackers-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T15:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Iran-nexus threat actor known as UNC1549 has been attributed with medium confidence to a new set of attacks targeting aerospace, aviation, and defense industries in the Middle East, including Israel and the U.A.E.
Other targets of the cyber espionage activity likely include Turkey, India, and Albania, Google-owned Mandiant said in a new analysis.
UNC1549 is said to overlap with]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0172 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Zimbra  Collaboration (28 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0172/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0172/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T13:46:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Zimbra Collaboration. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Warns U.S. Healthcare Sector of Targeted BlackCat Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fbi-warns-us-healthcare-sector-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/fbi-warns-us-healthcare-sector-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T13:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government is warning about the resurgence of BlackCat (aka ALPHV) ransomware attacks targeting the healthcare sector as recently as this month.
"Since mid-December 2023, of the nearly 70 leaked victims, the healthcare sector has been the most commonly victimized," the government said in an updated advisory.
"This is likely in response to the ALPHV/BlackCat administrator's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Building Your Privacy-Compliant Customer Data Platform (CDP) with First-Party Data]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/building-your-privacy-compliant.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/building-your-privacy-compliant.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T12:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's digital era, data privacy isn't just a concern; it's a consumer demand. Businesses are grappling with the dual challenge of leveraging customer data for personalized experiences while navigating a maze of privacy regulations. The answer? A privacy-compliant Customer Data Platform (CDP).
Join us for a transformative webinar where we unveil Twilio Segment's state-of-the-art CDP.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Superusers Need Super Protection: How to Bridge Privileged Access Management and Identity Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/superusers-need-super-protection-how-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/superusers-need-super-protection-how-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T10:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Traditional perimeter-based security has become costly and ineffective. As a result, communications security between people, systems, and networks is more important than blocking access with firewalls. On top of that, most cybersecurity risks are caused by just a few superusers – typically one out of 200 users. There’s a company aiming to fix the gap between traditional PAM and IdM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0171 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Aruba ClearPass Policy Manager (28 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0171/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0171/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T09:10:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Aruba ClearPass Policy Manager. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0170 : Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (28 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0170/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0170/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T08:46:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CERTFR-2024-AVI-0169 : Vulnérabilité dans les produits VMware (28 février 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0169/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0169/"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T08:39:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits VMware. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TimbreStealer Malware Spreading via Tax-themed Phishing Scam Targets IT Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/timbrestealer-malware-spreading-via-tax.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/02/timbrestealer-malware-spreading-via-tax.html"/>
        <updated>2024-02-28T07:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mexican users have been targeted with tax-themed phishing lures at least since November 2023 to distribute a previously undocumented Windows malware called TimbreStealer.
Cisco Talos, which discovered the activity, described the authors as skilled and that the "threat actor has previously used similar tactics, techniques and procedures (TTPs) to distribute a banking trojan known]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>