<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <id>https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html</id>
    <title>Becycure News</title>
    <updated>2024-09-27T21:11:46.247Z</updated>
    <generator>osmosfeed 1.15.1</generator>
    <link rel="alternate" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/index.html"/>
    <link rel="self" href="https://matthieu-becycure.github.io/becycure-news/feed.atom"/>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software Releases Patches for 6 Flaws in WhatsUp Gold – Patch Now]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-releases-patches-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-releases-patches-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T15:44:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has released another round of updates to address six security flaws in WhatsUp Gold, including two critical vulnerabilities.
The issues, the company said, have been resolved in version 24.0.1 released on September 20, 2024. The company has yet to release any details about what the flaws are other than listing their CVE identifiers -

CVE-2024-46905 (CVSS score: 8.8)]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilités affectant OpenPrinting CUPS (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-012/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-012/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T13:20:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans OpenPrinting CUPS et dans le composant cups-browsed. Celui-ci permet notamment de découvrir automatiquement des imprimantes partagées sur le réseau. Au total, quatre vulnérabilités ont été identifiées. Elles permettent : de récupérer des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Linux CUPS Printing System Flaws Could Allow Remote Command Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-linux-cups-printing-system.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-linux-cups-printing-system.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T12:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new set of security vulnerabilities has been disclosed in the OpenPrinting Common Unix Printing System (CUPS) on Linux systems that could permit remote command execution under certain conditions.
"A remote unauthenticated attacker can silently replace existing printers' (or install new ones) IPP urls with a malicious one, resulting in arbitrary command execution (on the computer) when a print]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Plan and Prepare for Penetration Testing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-plan-and-prepare-for-penetration.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-plan-and-prepare-for-penetration.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As security technology and threat awareness among organizations improves so do the adversaries who are adopting and relying on new techniques to maximize speed and impact while evading detection.
Ransomware and malware continue to be the method of choice by big game hunting (BGH) cyber criminals, and the increased use of hands-on or “interactive intrusion” techniques is especially alarming.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Identifies Storm-0501 as Major Threat in Hybrid Cloud Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-identifies-storm-0501-as.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-identifies-storm-0501-as.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T11:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as Storm-0501 has targeted government, manufacturing, transportation, and law enforcement sectors in the U.S. to stage ransomware attacks.
The multi-stage attack campaign is designed to compromise hybrid cloud environments and perform lateral movement from on-premises to cloud environment, ultimately resulting in data exfiltration, credential theft, tampering, persistent]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Certifications: The Gateway to Career Advancement]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-certifications-gateway-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-certifications-gateway-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In today's fast-evolving digital landscape, cybersecurity has become a cornerstone of organizational resilience. As cyber threats grow increasingly sophisticated, the demand for skilled cybersecurity professionals has never been higher. Whether you're a seasoned cyber professional or just starting your journey, signing up for the GIAC Newsletter ensures you're always informed and equipped for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New HTML Smuggling Campaign Delivers DCRat Malware to Russian-Speaking Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-html-smuggling-campaign-delivers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-html-smuggling-campaign-delivers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Russian-speaking users have been targeted as part of a new campaign distributing a commodity trojan called DCRat (aka DarkCrystal RAT) by means of a technique known as HTML smuggling.
The development marks the first time the malware has been deployed using this method, a departure from previously observed delivery vectors such as compromised or fake websites, or phishing emails bearing PDF]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0823/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0823/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:22:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0822/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0822/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:21:57.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0821/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0821/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:21:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités IBM Cognos Transformer (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0820/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0820/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:15:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0819/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0819/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T08:01:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans PHP (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0818/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0818/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:54:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans PHP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Sanctions Two Crypto Exchanges for Facilitating Cybercrime and Money Laundering]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-sanctions-two-crypto-exchanges-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-sanctions-two-crypto-exchanges-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:47:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government on Thursday sanctioned two cryptocurrency exchanges and unsealed an indictment against a Russian national for his alleged involvement in the operation of several money laundering services that were offered to cybercriminals.
The virtual currency exchanges, Cryptex and PM2BTC, have been alleged to facilitate the laundering of cryptocurrencies possibly obtained through]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Grafana (27 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0817/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0817/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T07:38:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Grafana. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical NVIDIA Container Toolkit Vulnerability Could Grant Full Host Access to Attackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-nvidia-container-toolkit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-27T05:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the NVIDIA Container Toolkit that, if successfully exploited, could allow threat actors to break out of the confines of a container and gain full access to the underlying host.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-0132, carries a CVSS score of 9.0 out of a maximum of 10.0. It has been addressed in NVIDIA Container Toolkit version v1.16.2 and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Could Have Remotely Controlled Kia Cars Using Only License Plates]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-could-have-remotely-controlled.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-could-have-remotely-controlled.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T16:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a set of now patched vulnerabilities in Kia vehicles that, if successfully exploited, could have allowed remote control over key functions simply by using only a license plate.
"These attacks could be executed remotely on any hardware-equipped vehicle in about 30 seconds, regardless of whether it had an active Kia Connect subscription," security]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Overloaded with SIEM Alerts? Discover Effective Strategies in This Expert-Led Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/overloaded-with-siem-alerts-discover.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/overloaded-with-siem-alerts-discover.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine trying to find a needle in a haystack, but the haystack is on fire, and there are a million other needles you also need to find. That's what dealing with security alerts can feel like.
SIEM was supposed to make this easier, but somewhere along the way, it became part of the problem. Too many alerts, too much noise, and not enough time to actually stop threats.
It's time for a change.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[N. Korean Hackers Deploy New KLogEXE and FPSpy Malware in Targeted Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/n-korean-hackers-deploy-new-klogexe-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/n-korean-hackers-deploy-new-klogexe-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T12:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed leveraging two new malware strains dubbed KLogEXE and FPSpy.
The activity has been attributed to an adversary tracked as Kimsuky, which is also known as APT43, ARCHIPELAGO, Black Banshee, Emerald Sleet (formerly Thallium), Sparkling Pisces, Springtail, and Velvet Chollima.
"These samples enhance Sparkling Pisces' already extensive arsenal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Foxit (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0816/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0816/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T11:28:09.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Foxit. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[EPSS vs. CVSS: What’s the Best Approach to Vulnerability Prioritization?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/epss-vs-cvss-whats-best-approach-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/epss-vs-cvss-whats-best-approach-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Many businesses rely on the Common Vulnerability Scoring System (CVSS) to assess the severity of vulnerabilities for prioritization. While these scores provide some insight into the potential impact of a vulnerability, they don’t factor in real-world threat data, such as the likelihood of exploitation. With new vulnerabilities discovered daily, teams don’t have the time - or the budget - to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Watering Hole Attack on Kurdish Sites Distributing Malicious APKs and Spyware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/watering-hole-attack-on-kurdish-sites.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/watering-hole-attack-on-kurdish-sites.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T10:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[As many as 25 websites linked to the Kurdish minority have been compromised as part of a watering hole attack designed to harvest sensitive information for over a year and a half.
French cybersecurity firm Sekoia, which disclosed details of the campaign dubbed SilentSelfie, described the intrusion set as long-running, with first signs of infection detected as far back as December 2022.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Synology (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0815/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0815/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T08:02:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Synology. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0814/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0814/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T07:08:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (26 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0813/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0813/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T06:50:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de requêtes illégitimes par rebond (CSRF) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cloudflare Warns of India-Linked Hackers Targeting South and East Asian Entities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cloudflare-warns-of-india-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cloudflare-warns-of-india-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An advanced threat actor with an India nexus has been observed using multiple cloud service providers to facilitate credential harvesting, malware delivery, and command-and-control (C2).
Web infrastructure and security company Cloudflare is tracking the activity under the name SloppyLemming, which is also called Outrider Tiger and Fishing Elephant.
"Between late 2022 to present, SloppyLemming]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Infiltrate U.S. Internet Providers in Cyber Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-infiltrate-us-internet.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-infiltrate-us-internet.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-26T04:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nation-state threat actors backed by Beijing broke into a "handful" of U.S. internet service providers (ISPs) as part of a cyber espionage campaign orchestrated to glean sensitive information, The Wall Street Journal reported Wednesday.
The activity has been attributed to a threat actor that Microsoft tracks as Salt Typhoon, which is also known as FamousSparrow and GhostEmperor.
"Investigators]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google's Shift to Rust Programming Cuts Android Memory Vulnerabilities by 52%]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/googles-shift-to-rust-programming-cuts.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/googles-shift-to-rust-programming-cuts.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T17:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has revealed that its transition to memory-safe languages such as Rust as part of its secure-by-design approach has led to the percentage of memory-safe vulnerabilities discovered in Android dropping from 76% to 24% over a period of six years.
The tech giant said focusing on Safe Coding for new features not only reduces the overall security risk of a codebase, but also makes the switch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mozilla Faces Privacy Complaint for Enabling Tracking in Firefox Without User Consent]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mozilla-faces-privacy-complaint-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mozilla-faces-privacy-complaint-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Vienna-based privacy non-profit noyb (short for None Of Your Business) has filed a complaint with the Austrian data protection authority (DPA) against Firefox maker Mozilla for enabling a new feature called Privacy Preserving Attribution (PPA) without explicitly seeking users' consent.
"Contrary to its reassuring name, this technology allows Firefox to track user behavior on websites," noyb said]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Traefik (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0812/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0812/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T14:01:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Traefik. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Trend Micro (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0811/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0811/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T13:51:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Trend Micro. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity Researchers Warn of New Rust-Based Splinter Post-Exploitation Tool]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-researchers-warn-of-new.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybersecurity-researchers-warn-of-new.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T12:38:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have flagged the discovery of a new post-exploitation red team tool called Splinter in the wild.
Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 shared its findings after it discovered the program on several customers' systems.
"It has a standard set of features commonly found in penetration testing tools and its developer created it using the Rust programming language," Unit 42's Dominik]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Expert Tips on How to Spot a Phishing Link]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/expert-tips-on-how-to-spot-phishing-link.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/expert-tips-on-how-to-spot-phishing-link.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Phishing attacks are becoming more advanced and harder to detect, but there are still telltale signs that can help you spot them before it's too late. See these key indicators that security experts use to identify phishing links:1. Check Suspicious URLs 

Phishing URLs are often long, confusing, or filled with random characters. Attackers use these to disguise the link's true destination]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Agentic AI in SOCs: A Solution to SOAR's Unfulfilled Promises]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/agentic-ai-in-socs-solution-to-soars.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/agentic-ai-in-socs-solution-to-soars.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Security Orchestration, Automation, and Response (SOAR) was introduced with the promise of revolutionizing Security Operations Centers (SOCs) through automation, reducing manual workloads and enhancing efficiency. However, despite three generations of technology and 10 years of advancements, SOAR hasn’t fully delivered on its potential, leaving SOCs still grappling with many of the same]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[ChatGPT macOS Flaw Could've Enabled Long-Term Spyware via Memory Function]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chatgpt-macos-flaw-couldve-enabled-long.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chatgpt-macos-flaw-couldve-enabled-long.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched security vulnerability in OpenAI's ChatGPT app for macOS could have made it possible for attackers to plant long-term persistent spyware into the artificial intelligence (AI) tool's memory.
The technique, dubbed SpAIware, could be abused to facilitate "continuous data exfiltration of any information the user typed or responses received by ChatGPT, including any future chat sessions]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Xen (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0810/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0810/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:17:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Xen. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0809/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0809/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:10:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0808/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0808/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:05:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Nessus Network Monitor (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0807/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0807/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T09:02:21.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Nessus Network Monitor. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0806/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0806/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T08:20:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Nagios XI (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0805/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0805/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T07:25:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Nagios XI. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Transportation Companies Hit by Cyberattacks Using Lumma Stealer and NetSupport Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/transportation-companies-hit-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/transportation-companies-hit-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T07:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Transportation and logistics companies in North America are the target of a new phishing campaign that delivers a variety of information stealers and remote access trojans (RATs).
The activity cluster, per Proofpoint, makes use of compromised legitimate email accounts belonging to transportation and shipping companies so as to inject malicious content into existing email conversations.
As many]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Stormshield Network Security (25 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0804/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0804/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T06:57:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Stormshield. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CISA Flags Critical Ivanti vTM Vulnerability Amid Active Exploitation Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisa-flags-critical-ivanti-vtm.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisa-flags-critical-ivanti-vtm.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-25T06:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Cybersecurity and Infrastructure Security Agency (CISA) on Tuesday added a critical security flaw impacting Ivanti Virtual Traffic Manager (vTM) to its Known Exploited Vulnerabilities (KEV) catalog, based on evidence of active exploitation.
The vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-7593 (CVSS score: 9.8), which could be exploited by a remote unauthenticated attacker to bypass the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Necro Android Malware Found in Popular Camera and Browser Apps on Play Store]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/necro-android-malware-found-in-popular.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/necro-android-malware-found-in-popular.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T16:13:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Altered versions of legitimate Android apps associated with Spotify, WhatsApp, and Minecraft have been used to deliver a new version of a known malware loader called Necro.
Kaspersky said some of the malicious apps have also been found on the Google Play Store. They have been cumulatively downloaded 11 million times. They include -

Wuta Camera - Nice Shot Always (com.benqu.wuta) - 10+ million]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Proposes Ban on Connected Vehicles Using Chinese and Russian Tech]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-proposes-ban-on-connected-vehicles.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-proposes-ban-on-connected-vehicles.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T13:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Commerce (DoC) said it's proposing a ban on the import or sale of connected vehicles that integrate software and hardware made by foreign adversaries, particularly that of the People's Republic of China (PRC) and Russia.
"The proposed rule focuses on hardware and software integrated into the Vehicle Connectivity System (VCS) and software integrated into the Automated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discover Latest Ransomware Tactics and Zero Trust Strategies in This Expert Webinar]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discover-latest-ransomware-tactics-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discover-latest-ransomware-tactics-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ransomware is no longer just a threat; it's an entire industry. Cybercriminals are growing more sophisticated, and their tactics are evolving rapidly.
This persistent danger is a major concern for business leaders.
But there's good news: you don't have to be defenseless. What if you could gain a strategic edge?
Join our exclusive webinar, "Unpacking the 2024 Ransomware Landscape: Insights and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Kaspersky Exits U.S., Automatically Replaces Software With UltraAV, Raising Concerns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/kaspersky-exits-us-automatically.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/kaspersky-exits-us-automatically.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Antivirus vendor Kaspersky has formally begun pulling back its offerings in the U.S., migrating existing users to UltraAV, effective September 19, 2024, ahead of its formal exit at the end of the month.
"Kaspersky antivirus customers received a software update facilitating the transition to UltraAV," the company said in a post announcing the move on September 21.
"This update ensured that users]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans TheGreenBow VPN Client  (24 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0803/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0803/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:16:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans TheGreenBow VPN Client. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The SSPM Justification Kit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-sspm-justification-kit.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-sspm-justification-kit.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SaaS applications contain a wealth of sensitive data and are central to business operations. Despite this, far too many organizations rely on half measures and hope their SaaS stack will remain secure. Unfortunately, this approach is lacking and will leave security teams blind to threat prevention and detection, as well as open to regulatory violations, data leaks, and significant breaches.
If]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Octo2 Android Banking Trojan Emerges with Device Takeover Capabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-octo2-android-banking-trojan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-octo2-android-banking-trojan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered a new version of an Android banking trojan called Octo that comes with improved capabilities to conduct device takeover (DTO) and perform fraudulent transactions.
The new version has been codenamed Octo2 by the malware author, Dutch security firm ThreatFabric said in a report shared with The Hacker News, adding campaigns distributing the malware have]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exfiltration de données du secteur social - Retour d’expérience du CERT-FR (24 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-009/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-009/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T09:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[L’année 2023 et le début de l’année 2024 ont été marqués par de nombreux incidents ciblant des entités du secteur social gérant des données à caractère personnel . Compte tenu des impacts qu’ont eu ces exfiltrations de données, le CERT-FR propose un retour d’expérience sur la gestion de ces...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram Agrees to Share User Data With Authorities for Criminal Investigations]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/telegram-agrees-to-share-user-data-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/telegram-agrees-to-share-user-data-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-24T06:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In a major policy reversal, the popular messaging app Telegram has announced it will give users' IP addresses and phone numbers to authorities in response to valid legal requests in an attempt to rein in criminal activity on the platform.
"We've made it clear that the IP addresses and phone numbers of those who violate our rules can be disclosed to relevant authorities in response to valid legal]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-042 (23 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-042/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-042/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T14:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[THN Cybersecurity Recap: Last Week's Top Threats and Trends (September 16-22)]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/thn-cybersecurity-recap-last-weeks-top.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Hold on tight, folks, because last week's cybersecurity landscape was a rollercoaster! We witnessed everything from North Korean hackers dangling "dream jobs" to expose a new malware, to a surprising twist in the Apple vs. NSO Group saga. Even the seemingly mundane world of domain names and cloud configurations had its share of drama. Let's dive into the details and see what lessons we can glean]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why 'Never Expire' Passwords Can Be a Risky Decision]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-never-expire-passwords-can-be-risky.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-never-expire-passwords-can-be-risky.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Password resets can be frustrating for end users. Nobody likes being interrupted by the ‘time to change your password’ notification – and they like it even less when the new passwords they create are rejected by their organization’s password policy. IT teams share the pain, with resetting passwords via service desk tickets and support calls being an everyday burden. Despite this, it’s commonly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Flaw in Microchip ASF Exposes IoT Devices to Remote Code Execution Risk]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaw-in-microchip-asf-exposes.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-flaw-in-microchip-asf-exposes.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T09:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A critical security flaw has been disclosed in the Microchip Advanced Software Framework (ASF) that, if successfully exploited, could lead to remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-7490, carries a CVSS score of 9.5 out of a maximum of 10.0. It has been described as a stack-based overflow vulnerability in ASF's implementation of the tinydhcp server stemming from a lack of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Discord Introduces DAVE Protocol for End-to-End Encryption in Audio and Video Calls]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discord-introduces-dave-protocol-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/discord-introduces-dave-protocol-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T09:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Popular social messaging platform Discord has announced that it's rolling out a new custom end-to-end encrypted (E2EE) protocol to secure audio and video calls.
The protocol has been dubbed DAVE, short for Discord's audio and video end-to-end encryption ("E2EE A/V").
As part of the change introduced last week, voice and video in DMs, Group DMs, voice channels, and Go Live streams are expected to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Moxa (23 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0802/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0802/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T07:01:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Moxa. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits ESET (23 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0801/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0801/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T06:51:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits ESET. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PondRAT Malware Hidden in Python Packages Targets Software Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-pondrat-malware-hidden-in-python.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-pondrat-malware-hidden-in-python.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T06:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed using poisoned Python packages as a way to deliver a new malware called PondRAT as part of an ongoing campaign.
PondRAT, according to new findings from Palo Alto Networks Unit 42, is assessed to be a lighter version of POOLRAT (aka SIMPLESEA), a known macOS backdoor that has been previously attributed to the Lazarus Group and deployed in]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploit GeoServer Flaw to Target APAC Nations with EAGLEDOOR Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-exploit-geoserver-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-exploit-geoserver-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-23T04:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A suspected advanced persistent threat (APT) originating from China targeted a government organization in Taiwan, and possibly other countries in the Asia-Pacific (APAC) region, by exploiting a recently patched critical security flaw impacting OSGeo GeoServer GeoTools.
The intrusion activity, which was detected by Trend Micro in July 2024, has been attributed to a threat actor dubbed Earth Baxia]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivist Group Twelve Targets Russian Entities with Destructive Cyber Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivist-group-twelve-targets-russian.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivist-group-twelve-targets-russian.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T14:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacktivist group known as Twelve has been observed using an arsenal of publicly available tools to conduct destructive cyber attacks against Russian targets.
"Rather than demand a ransom for decrypting data, Twelve prefers to encrypt victims' data and then destroy their infrastructure with a wiper to prevent recovery," Kaspersky said in a Friday analysis.
"The approach is indicative of a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[LinkedIn Halts AI Data Processing in UK Amid Privacy Concerns Raised by ICO]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/linkedin-halts-ai-data-processing-in-uk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/linkedin-halts-ai-data-processing-in-uk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T13:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.K. Information Commissioner's Office (ICO) has confirmed that professional social networking platform LinkedIn has suspended processing users' data in the country to train its artificial intelligence (AI) models.
"We are pleased that LinkedIn has reflected on the concerns we raised about its approach to training generative AI models with information relating to its U.K. users," Stephen]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine Bans Telegram Use for Government and Military Personnel]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ukraine-bans-telegram-use-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ukraine-bans-telegram-use-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-21T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ukraine has restricted the use of the Telegram messaging app by government officials, military personnel, and other defense and critical infrastructure workers, citing national security concerns.
The ban was announced by the National Coordination Centre for Cybersecurity (NCCC) in a post shared on Facebook.
"I have always advocated and advocate for freedom of speech, but the issue of Telegram is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Europol Shuts Down Major Phishing Scheme Targeting Mobile Phone Credentials]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/europol-shuts-down-major-phishing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/europol-shuts-down-major-phishing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T12:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Law enforcement authorities have announced the takedown of an international criminal network that leveraged a phishing platform to unlock stolen or lost mobile phones.
The phishing-as-a-service (PhaaS) platform, called iServer, is estimated to have claimed more than 483,000 victims globally, led by Chile (77,000), Colombia (70,000), Ecuador (42,000), Peru (41,500), Spain (30,000), and Argentina]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0800/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0800/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:44:32.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0799/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0799/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:44:02.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0798/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0798/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:40:42.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0797/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0797/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:30:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Passwordless AND Keyless: The Future of (Privileged) Access Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/passwordless-and-keyless-future-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/passwordless-and-keyless-future-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In IT environments, some secrets are managed well and some fly under the radar. Here’s a quick checklist of what kinds of secrets companies typically manage, including one type they should manage:

Passwords [x]
TLS certificates [x]
Accounts [x]
SSH keys ???

The secrets listed above are typically secured with privileged access management (PAM) solutions or similar. Yet, most traditional PAM]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian APT UNC1860 Linked to MOIS Facilitates Cyber Intrusions in Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/iranian-apt-unc1860-linked-to-mois.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/iranian-apt-unc1860-linked-to-mois.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T10:11:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[An Iranian advanced persistent threat (APT) threat actor likely affiliated with the Ministry of Intelligence and Security (MOIS) is now acting as an initial access facilitator that provides remote access to target networks.
Google-owned Mandiant is tracking the activity cluster under the moniker UNC1860, which it said shares similarities with intrusion sets tracked by Microsoft, Cisco Talos, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0796/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0796/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T09:16:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Ivanti Cloud Service Appliance (CSA). Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité. Ivanti déclare que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-8963 est activement exploitée dans le cadre d'attaques ciblées, en combinaison avec la...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Microsoft (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0795/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0795/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T09:11:48.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Microsoft. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0793/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0793/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T09:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Microsoft Office (20 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0794/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0794/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T09:11:47.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Microsoft Office. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Users Can Now Sync Passkeys Across Devices with New Google PIN Feature]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chrome-users-can-now-sync-passkeys.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chrome-users-can-now-sync-passkeys.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T05:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google on Thursday unveiled a Password Manager PIN to let Chrome web users sync their passkeys across Windows, macOS, Linux, ChromeOS, and Android devices.
"This PIN adds an additional layer of security to ensure your passkeys are end-to-end encrypted and can't be accessed by anyone, not even Google," Chrome product manager Chirag Desai said.
The PIN is a six-digit code by default, although it's]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Ivanti Cloud Appliance Vulnerability Exploited in Active Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-ivanti-cloud-appliance.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-ivanti-cloud-appliance.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-20T04:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has revealed that a critical security flaw impacting Cloud Service Appliance (CSA) has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The new vulnerability, assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-8963, carries a CVSS score of 9.4 out of a maximum of 10.0. It was "incidentally addressed" by the company as part of CSA 4.6 Patch 519 and CSA 5.0.
"Path Traversal in the Ivanti CSA before 4.6 Patch]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wherever There's Ransomware, There's Service Account Compromise. Are You Protected?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wherever-theres-ransomware-theres.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wherever-theres-ransomware-theres.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T17:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Until just a couple of years ago, only a handful of IAM pros knew what service accounts are. In the last years, these silent Non-Human-Identities (NHI) accounts have become one of the most targeted and compromised attack surfaces. Assessments report that compromised service accounts play a key role in lateral movement in over 70% of ransomware attacks. However, there’s an alarming disproportion]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Exploit Default Credentials in FOUNDATION Software to Breach Construction Firms]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-exploit-default-credentials-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-exploit-default-credentials-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T15:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have been observed targeting the construction sector by infiltrating the FOUNDATION Accounting Software, according to new findings from Huntress.
"Attackers have been observed brute-forcing the software at scale, and gaining access simply by using the product’s default credentials," the cybersecurity company said.
Targets of the emerging threat include plumbing, HVAC (heating,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Brazilian-Linked SambaSpy Malware Targets Italian Users via Phishing Emails]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-brazilian-linked-sambaspy-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-brazilian-linked-sambaspy-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T14:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented malware called SambaSpy is exclusively targeting users in Italy via a phishing campaign orchestrated by a suspected Brazilian Portuguese-speaking threat actor.
"Threat actors usually try to cast a wide net to maximize their profits, but these attackers are focused on just one country," Kaspersky said in a new analysis. "It's likely that the attackers are testing the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New TeamTNT Cryptojacking Campaign Targets CentOS Servers with Rootkit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-teamtnt-cryptojacking-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-teamtnt-cryptojacking-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T13:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The cryptojacking operation known as TeamTNT has likely resurfaced as part of a new campaign targeting Virtual Private Server (VPS) infrastructures based on the CentOS operating system.
"The initial access was accomplished via a Secure Shell (SSH) brute force attack on the victim's assets, during which the threat actor uploaded a malicious script," Group-IB researchers Vito Alfano and Nam Le]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Healthcare's Diagnosis is Critical: The Cure is Cybersecurity Hygiene]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/healthcares-diagnosis-is-critical-cure.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/healthcares-diagnosis-is-critical-cure.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity in healthcare has never been more urgent. As the most vulnerable industry and largest target for cybercriminals, healthcare is facing an increasing wave of cyberattacks. When a hospital's systems are held hostage by ransomware, it’s not just data at risk — it’s the care of patients who depend on life-saving treatments. Imagine an attack that forces emergency care to halt, surgeries]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Warns of New INC Ransomware Targeting U.S. Healthcare Sector]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-warns-of-new-inc-ransomware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-warns-of-new-inc-ransomware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T10:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft has revealed that a financially motivated threat actor has been observed using a ransomware strain called INC for the first time to target the healthcare sector in the U.S.
The tech giant's threat intelligence team is tracking the activity under the name Vanilla Tempest (formerly DEV-0832).
"Vanilla Tempest receives hand-offs from GootLoader infections by the threat actor Storm-0494,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab Patches Critical SAML Authentication Bypass Flaw in CE and EE Editions]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/gitlab-patches-critical-saml.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/gitlab-patches-critical-saml.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-19T05:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab has released patches to address a critical flaw impacting Community Edition (CE) and Enterprise Edition (EE) that could result in an authentication bypass.
The vulnerability is rooted in the ruby-saml library (CVE-2024-45409, CVSS score: 10.0), which could allow an attacker to log in as an arbitrary user within the vulnerable system. It was addressed by the maintainers last week.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New "Raptor Train" IoT Botnet Compromises Over 200,000 Devices Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-raptor-train-iot-botnet-compromises.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-raptor-train-iot-botnet-compromises.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T16:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a never-before-seen botnet comprising an army of small office/home office (SOHO) and IoT devices that are likely operated by a Chinese nation-state threat actor called Flax Typhoon (aka Ethereal Panda or RedJuliett).
The sophisticated botnet, dubbed Raptor Train by Lumen's Black Lotus Labs, is believed to have been operational since at least May 2020,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Engineer Charged in U.S. for Years-Long Cyber Espionage Targeting NASA and Military]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-engineer-charged-in-us-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-engineer-charged-in-us-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T14:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A Chinese national has been indicted in the U.S. on charges of conducting a "multi-year" spear-phishing campaign to obtain unauthorized access to computer software and source code created by the National Aeronautics and Space Administration (NASA), research universities, and private companies.
Song Wu, 39, has been charged with 14 counts of wire fraud and 14 counts of aggravated identity theft.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Pay A Pentester?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-pay-pentester.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-pay-pentester.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The evolution of software always catches us by surprise. I remember betting against the IBM computer Deep Blue during its chess match against the grandmaster Garry Kasparov in 1997, only to be stunned when the machine claimed victory. Fast forward to today, would we have imagined just three years ago that a chatbot could write essays, handle customer support calls, and even craft commercial]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans VMware vCenter Server (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0792/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0792/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T10:01:03.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits VMware. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans GitLab (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0791/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0791/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:55:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans GitLab. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0790/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0790/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:52:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Mozilla Firefox pour Android (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0789/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0789/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:50:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Mozilla Firefox pour Android. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Atlassian (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0788/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0788/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:43:49.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Atlassian. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans LibreOffice (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0787/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0787/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:41:44.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans LibreOffice. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Energy and Aerospace Industries with New MISTPEN Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-target-energy-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-target-energy-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A North Korea-linked cyber-espionage group has been observed leveraging job-themed phishing lures to target prospective victims in energy and aerospace verticals and infect them with a previously undocumented backdoor dubbed MISTPEN.
The activity cluster is being tracked by Google-owned Mandiant under the moniker UNC2970, which it said overlaps with a threat group known as TEMP.Hermit, which is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking (18 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0786/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0786/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:04:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits HPE Aruba Networking. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chrome Introduces One-Time Permissions and Enhanced Safety Check for Safer Browsing]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chrome-introduces-one-time-permissions.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chrome-introduces-one-time-permissions.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T09:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it's rolling out a new set of features to its Chrome browser that gives users more control over their data when surfing the internet and protects against online threats.
"With the newest version of Chrome, you can take advantage of our upgraded Safety Check, opt out of unwanted website notifications more easily and grant select permissions to a site for one time only,"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GSMA Plans End-to-End Encryption for Cross-Platform RCS Messaging]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/gsma-plans-end-to-end-encryption-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/gsma-plans-end-to-end-encryption-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T06:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The GSM Association, the governing body that oversees the development of the Rich Communications Services (RCS) protocol, on Tuesday, said it's working towards implementing end-to-end encryption (E2EE) to secure messages sent between the Android and iOS ecosystems.
"The next major milestone is for the RCS Universal Profile to add important user protections such as interoperable end-to-end]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Patch Issued for Critical VMware vCenter Flaw Allowing Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/patch-issued-for-critical-vmware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/patch-issued-for-critical-vmware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-18T05:08:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Broadcom on Tuesday released updates to address a critical security flaw impacting VMware vCenter Server that could pave the way for remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-38812 (CVSS score: 9.8), has been described as a heap-overflow vulnerability in the DCE/RPC protocol.
"A malicious actor with network access to vCenter Server may trigger this vulnerability by sending a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Chrome Switches to ML-KEM for Post-Quantum Cryptography Defense]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-chrome-switches-to-ml-kem-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-chrome-switches-to-ml-kem-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T12:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has announced that it will be switching from KYBER to ML-KEM in its Chrome web browser as part of its ongoing efforts to defend against the risk posed by cryptographically relevant quantum computers (CRQCs).
"Chrome will offer a key share prediction for hybrid ML-KEM (codepoint 0x11EC)," David Adrian, David Benjamin, Bob Beck, and Devon O'Brien of the Chrome Team said. "The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Treasury Sanctions Executives Linked to Intellexa Predator Spyware Operation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-treasury-sanctions-executives-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-treasury-sanctions-executives-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T12:06:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Treasury has imposed fresh sanctions against five executives and one entity with ties to the Intellexa Consortium for their role in the development, operation, and distribution of a commercial spyware called Predator.
"The United States will not tolerate the reckless propagation of disruptive technologies that threatens our national security and undermines the privacy and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Meta to Train AI Models Using Public U.K. Facebook and Instagram Posts]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/meta-to-train-ai-models-using-public-uk.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/meta-to-train-ai-models-using-public-uk.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T11:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Meta has announced that it will begin training its artificial intelligence (AI) systems using public content shared by adult users across Facebook and Instagram in the U.K. in the coming months.
"This means that our generative AI models will reflect British culture, history, and idiom, and that UK companies and institutions will be able to utilize the latest technology," the social media]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How to Investigate ChatGPT activity in Google Workspace]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-investigate-chatgpt-activity-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/how-to-investigate-chatgpt-activity-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T11:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Since launching ChatGPT in 2022, OpenAI has defied expectations with a steady stream of product announcements and enhancements. One such announcement came on May 16, 2024, and for most consumers, it probably felt innocuous. Titled “Improvements to data analysis in ChatGPT,” the post outlines how users can add files directly from Google Drive and Microsoft OneDrive. It’s worth mentioning]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Apple (17 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0785/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0785/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T09:17:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Apple. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Ivanti Cloud Service Appliance (17 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0784/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0784/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T07:34:07.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Ivanti Cloud Service Appliance (CSA). Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance. Ivanti déclare que la vulnérabilité CVE-2024-8190 est activement exploitée dans le cadre d'attaques ciblées.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Binance Warns of Rising Clipper Malware Attacks Targeting Cryptocurrency Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/binance-warns-of-rising-clipper-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/binance-warns-of-rising-clipper-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T07:18:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency exchange Binance is warning of an "ongoing" global threat that's targeting cryptocurrency users with clipper malware with the goal of facilitating financial fraud.
Clipper malware, also called ClipBankers, is a type of malware that Microsoft calls cryware, which comes with capabilities to monitor a victim's clipboard activity and steal sensitive data a user copies, including]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds Issues Patch for Critical ARM Vulnerability Enabling RCE Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/solarwinds-issues-patch-for-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/solarwinds-issues-patch-for-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-17T04:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SolarWinds has released fixes to address two security flaws in its Access Rights Manager (ARM) software, including a critical vulnerability that could result in remote code execution.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-28991, is rated 9.0 out of a maximum of 10.0 on the CVSS scoring system. It has been described as an instance of deserialization of untrusted data. 
"SolarWinds Access Rights]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Fixes GCP Composer Flaw That Could've Led to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-fixes-gcp-composer-flaw-that.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-fixes-gcp-composer-flaw-that.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T13:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A now-patched critical security flaw impacting Google Cloud Platform (GCP) Composer could have been exploited to achieve remote code execution on cloud servers by means of a supply chain attack technique called dependency confusion.
The vulnerability has been codenamed CloudImposer by Tenable Research.
"The vulnerability could have allowed an attacker to hijack an internal software dependency]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-041 (16 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-041/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-041/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T12:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Cryptocurrency Users on LinkedIn with RustDoor Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-target.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-target.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T12:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers are continuing to warn about North Korean threat actors' attempts to target prospective victims on LinkedIn to deliver malware called RustDoor.
The latest advisory comes from Jamf Threat Labs, which said it spotted an attack attempt in which a user was contacted on the professional social network by claiming to be a recruiter for a legitimate decentralized]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[From Breach to Recovery: Designing an Identity-Focused Incident Response Playbook]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/from-breach-to-recovery-designing.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/from-breach-to-recovery-designing.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T11:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine this... You arrive at work to a chaotic scene. Systems are down, panic is in the air. The culprit? Not a rogue virus, but a compromised identity. The attacker is inside your walls, masquerading as a trusted user. This isn't a horror movie, it's the new reality of cybercrime. The question is, are you prepared?
Traditional incident response plans are like old maps in a new world. They]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Master Your PCI DSS v4 Compliance with Innovative Smart Approvals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/master-your-pci-dss-v4-compliance-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/master-your-pci-dss-v4-compliance-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The PCI DSS landscape is evolving rapidly. With the Q1 2025 deadline looming ever larger, businesses are scrambling to meet the stringent new requirements of PCI DSS v4.0. Two sections in particular, 6.4.3 and 11.6.1, are troublesome as they demand that organizations rigorously monitor and manage payment page scripts and use a robust change detection mechanism. With the deadline fast approaching]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MISP (16 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0783/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0783/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T08:45:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MISP. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SolarWinds Access Rights Manager (16 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0782/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0782/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T08:45:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans SolarWinds Access Rights Manager. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Juniper Networks (16 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0781/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0781/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T08:45:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Drops Spyware Case Against NSO Group, Citing Risk of Threat Intelligence Exposure]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apple-drops-spyware-case-against-nso.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apple-drops-spyware-case-against-nso.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T07:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Apple has filed a motion to "voluntarily" dismiss its lawsuit against commercial spyware vendor NSO Group, citing a shifting risk landscape that could lead to exposure of critical "threat intelligence" information.
The development was first reported by The Washington Post on Friday.
The iPhone maker said its efforts, coupled with those of others in the industry and national governments to tackle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cybercriminals Exploit HTTP Headers for Credential Theft via Large-Scale Phishing Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybercriminals-exploit-http-headers-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cybercriminals-exploit-http-headers-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-16T04:23:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have warned of ongoing phishing campaigns that abuse refresh entries in HTTP headers to deliver spoofed email login pages that are designed to harvest users' credentials.
"Unlike other phishing webpage distribution behavior through HTML content, these attacks use the response header sent by a server, which occurs before the processing of the HTML content," Palo Alto]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Warns of Active Exploitation of Newly Patched Cloud Appliance Vulnerability]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ivanti-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ivanti-warns-of-active-exploitation-of.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-14T04:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has revealed that a newly patched security flaw in its Cloud Service Appliance (CSA) has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The high-severity vulnerability in question is CVE-2024-8190 (CVSS score: 7.2), which allows remote code execution under certain circumstances.
"An OS command injection vulnerability in Ivanti Cloud Services Appliance versions 4.6 Patch 518 and before allows]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apple Vision Pro Vulnerability Exposed Virtual Keyboard Inputs to Attackers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apple-vision-pro-vulnerability-exposed.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apple-vision-pro-vulnerability-exposed.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Details have emerged about a now-patched security flaw impacting Apple's Vision Pro mixed reality headset that, if successfully exploited, could allow malicious attackers to infer data entered on the device's virtual keyboard.
The attack, dubbed GAZEploit, has been assigned the CVE identifier CVE-2024-40865.
"A novel attack that can infer eye-related biometrics from the avatar image to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[17-Year-Old Arrested in Connection with Cyber Attack Affecting Transport for London]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/17-year-old-arrested-in-connection-with.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/17-year-old-arrested-in-connection-with.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[British authorities on Thursday announced the arrest of a 17-year-old male in connection with a cyber attack affecting Transport for London (TfL).
"The 17-year-old male was detained on suspicion of Computer Misuse Act offenses in relation to the attack, which was launched on TfL on 1 September," the U.K. National Crime Agency (NCA) said.
The teenager, who's from Walsall, is said to have been]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0780/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0780/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T12:04:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0779/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0779/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:58:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0778/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0778/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:30:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0777/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0777/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:27:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Say Goodbye to Phishing: Must-Haves to Eliminate Credential Theft]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/say-goodbye-to-phishing-must-haves-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/say-goodbye-to-phishing-must-haves-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Even as cyber threats become increasingly sophisticated, the number one attack vector for unauthorized access remains phished credentials (Verizon DBIR, 2024). Solving this problem resolves over 80% of your corporate risk, and a solution is possible. 
However, most tools available on the market today cannot offer a complete defense against this attack vector because they were architected to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TrickMo Android Trojan Exploits Accessibility Services for On-Device Banking Fraud]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/trickmo-android-trojan-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/trickmo-android-trojan-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new variant of an Android banking trojan called TrickMo that comes packed with new capabilities to evade analysis and display fake login screens to capture victims' banking credentials.
"The mechanisms include using malformed ZIP files in combination with JSONPacker," Cleafy security researchers Michele Roviello and Alessandro Strino said. "In addition,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress WhatsUp Gold Exploited Just Hours After PoC Release for Critical Flaw]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-whatsup-gold-exploited-just.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-whatsup-gold-exploited-just.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T11:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious actors are likely leveraging publicly available proof-of-concept (PoC) exploits for recently disclosed security flaws in Progress Software WhatsUp Gold to conduct opportunistic attacks.
The activity is said to have commenced on August 30, 2024, a mere five hours after a PoC was released for CVE-2024-6670 (CVSS score: 9.8) by security researcher Sina Kheirkhah of the Summoning Team, who]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Spring Framework (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0776/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0776/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Spring Framework. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (13 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0775/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0775/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T07:33:05.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Linux Malware Campaign Exploits Oracle Weblogic to Mine Cryptocurrency]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-linux-malware-campaign-exploits.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-linux-malware-campaign-exploits.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-13T05:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new malware campaign targeting Linux environments to conduct illicit cryptocurrency mining.
The activity, which specifically singles out the Oracle Weblogic server, is designed to deliver malware dubbed Hadooken, according to cloud security firm Aqua.
"When Hadooken is executed, it drops a Tsunami malware and deploys a crypto miner," security researcher]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android Malware 'Ajina.Banker' Steals Financial Data and Bypasses 2FA via Telegram]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-android-malware-ajinabanker-steals.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-android-malware-ajinabanker-steals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T16:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Bank customers in the Central Asia region have been targeted by a new strain of Android malware codenamed Ajina.Banker since at least November 2024 with the goal of harvesting financial information and intercepting two-factor authentication (2FA) messages.
Singapore-headquartered Group-IB, which discovered the threat in May 2024, said the malware is propagated via a network of Telegram channels]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Urgent: GitLab Patches Critical Flaw Allowing Unauthorized Pipeline Job Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/urgent-gitlab-patches-critical-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/urgent-gitlab-patches-critical-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GitLab on Wednesday released security updates to address 17 security vulnerabilities, including a critical flaw that allows an attacker to run pipeline jobs as an arbitrary user.
The issue, tracked as CVE-2024-6678, carries a CVSS score of 9.9 out of a maximum of 10.0
"An issue was discovered in GitLab CE/EE affecting all versions starting from 8.14 prior to 17.1.7, starting from 17.2 prior to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Beware: New Vo1d Malware Infects 1.3 Million Android TV Boxes Worldwide]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/beware-new-vo1d-malware-infects-13.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/beware-new-vo1d-malware-infects-13.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T13:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Nearly 1.3 million Android-based TV boxes running outdated versions of the operating system and belonging to users spanning 197 countries have been infected by a new malware dubbed Vo1d (aka Void).
"It is a backdoor that puts its components in the system storage area and, when commanded by attackers, is capable of secretly downloading and installing third-party software," Russian antivirus]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Exposed Selenium Grid Servers Targeted for Crypto Mining and Proxyjacking]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/exposed-selenium-grid-servers-targeted.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/exposed-selenium-grid-servers-targeted.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:56:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Internet-exposed Selenium Grid instances are being targeted by bad actors for illicit cryptocurrency mining and proxyjacking campaigns.
"Selenium Grid is a server that facilitates running test cases in parallel across different browsers and versions," Cado Security researchers Tara Gould and Nate Bill said in an analysis published today.
"However, Selenium Grid's default configuration lacks]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Juniper Networks (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0774/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0774/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:42:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Juniper Networks. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Edge (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0773/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0773/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T12:39:43.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Edge. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Top 3 Threat Report Insights for Q2 2024]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/top-3-threat-report-insights-for-q2-2024.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/top-3-threat-report-insights-for-q2-2024.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:51:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cato CTRL (Cyber Threats Research Lab) has released its Q2 2024 Cato CTRL SASE Threat Report. The report highlights critical findings based on the analysis of a staggering 1.38 trillion network flows from more than 2,500 of Cato’s global customers, between April and June 2024.
Key Insights from the Q2 2024 Cato CTRL SASE Threat Report
The report is packed with unique insights that are based on]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Cyber Group OilRig Targets Iraqi Government in Sophisticated Malware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/iranian-cyber-group-oilrig-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/iranian-cyber-group-oilrig-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:49:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Iraqi government networks have emerged as the target of an "elaborate" cyber attack campaign orchestrated by an Iran state-sponsored threat actor called OilRig.
The attacks singled out Iraqi organizations such as the Prime Minister's Office and the Ministry of Foreign Affairs, cybersecurity company Check Point said in a new analysis.
OilRig, also called APT34, Crambus, Cobalt Gypsy, GreenBug,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ireland's Watchdog Launches Inquiry into Google's AI Data Practices in Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/irelands-watchdog-launches-inquiry-into.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/irelands-watchdog-launches-inquiry-into.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T10:32:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Irish Data Protection Commission (DPC) has announced that it has commenced a "Cross-Border statutory inquiry" into Google's foundational artificial intelligence (AI) model to determine whether the tech giant has adhered to data protection regulations in the region when processing the personal data of European users.
"The statutory inquiry concerns the question of whether Google has complied]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0772/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0772/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T08:44:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Tenable (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0771/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0771/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T07:34:24.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Tenable. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Palo Alto Networks (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0770/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0770/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T07:14:50.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Palo Alto Networks. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans GitLab (12 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0769/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0769/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T06:59:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans GitLab. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress Mandates Two-Factor Authentication for Plugin and Theme Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wordpress-mandates-two-factor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wordpress-mandates-two-factor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-12T04:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[WordPress.org has announced a new account security measure that will require accounts with capabilities to update plugins and themes to activate two-factor authentication (2FA) mandatorily.
The enforcement is expected to come into effect starting October 1, 2024.
"Accounts with commit access can push updates and changes to plugins and themes used by millions of WordPress sites worldwide," the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Quad7 Botnet Expands to Target SOHO Routers and VPN Appliances]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/quad7-botnet-expands-to-target-soho.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/quad7-botnet-expands-to-target-soho.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T16:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The operators of the mysterious Quad7 botnet are actively evolving by compromising several brands of SOHO routers and VPN appliances by leveraging a combination of both known and unknown security flaws.
Targets include devices from TP-LINK, Zyxel, Asus, Axentra, D-Link, and NETGEAR, according to a new report by French cybersecurity company Sekoia.
"The Quad7 botnet operators appear to be]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[DragonRank Black Hat SEO Campaign Targeting IIS Servers Across Asia and Europe]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/dragonrank-black-hat-seo-campaign.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/dragonrank-black-hat-seo-campaign.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T15:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A "simplified Chinese-speaking actor" has been linked to a new campaign that has targeted multiple countries in Asia and Europe with the end goal of performing search engine optimization (SEO) rank manipulation.
The black hat SEO cluster has been codenamed DragonRank by Cisco Talos, with victimology footprint scattered across Thailand, India, Korea, Belgium, the Netherlands, and China.
"]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Singapore Police Arrest Six Hackers Linked to Global Cybercrime Syndicate]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/singapore-police-arrest-six-for-alleged.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/singapore-police-arrest-six-for-alleged.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T12:07:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Singapore Police Force (SPF) has announced the arrest of five Chinese nationals and one Singaporean man for their alleged involvement in illicit cyber activities in the country.
The development comes after a group of about 160 law enforcement officials conducted a series of raids on September 9, 2024, simultaneously at several locations.
The six men, aged between 32 and 42, are suspected of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Intel (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0768/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0768/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T11:22:52.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Intel. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Why Is It So Challenging to Go Passwordless?]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-is-it-so-challenging-to-go.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/why-is-it-so-challenging-to-go.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T10:41:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Imagine a world where you never have to remember another password. Seems like a dream come true for both end users and IT teams, right? But as the old saying goes, "If it sounds too good to be true, it probably is." 
If your organization is like many, you may be contemplating a move to passwordless authentication. But the reality is that a passwordless security approach comes with its own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Developers Beware: Lazarus Group Uses Fake Coding Tests to Spread Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/developers-beware-lazarus-group-uses.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/developers-beware-lazarus-group-uses.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T09:46:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a new set of malicious Python packages that target software developers under the guise of coding assessments.
"The new samples were tracked to GitHub projects that have been linked to previous, targeted attacks in which developers are lured using fake job interviews," ReversingLabs researcher Karlo Zanki said.
The activity has been assessed to be part of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Ivanti Endpoint Manager (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0767/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0767/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T09:22:46.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Se référer au bulletin de sécurité de l'éditeur pour l'obtention des correctifs (cf. section Documentation).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0766/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0766/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T09:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans MongoDB Server (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0765/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0765/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T09:05:04.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans MongoDB Server. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Adobe (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0764/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0764/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T08:49:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Adobe. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Fortinet (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0763/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0763/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T08:16:01.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Fortinet. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Citrix (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0762/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0762/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T07:58:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Citrix. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Microsoft (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0761/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0761/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T07:37:13.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Microsoft. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Windows (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0759/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0759/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T07:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Windows. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et un déni de service à distance. Microsoft indique que les vulnérabilités...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Azure (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0760/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0760/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T07:37:12.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Azure. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance et une élévation de privilèges.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Microsoft Office (11 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0758/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0758/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T07:37:10.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Microsoft Office. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données. Microsoft indique que la vulnérabilité...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft Issues Patches for 79 Flaws, Including 3 Actively Exploited Windows Flaws]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-issues-patches-for-79-flaws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/microsoft-issues-patches-for-79-flaws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:53:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Microsoft on Tuesday disclosed that three new security flaws impacting the Windows platform have come under active exploitation as part of its Patch Tuesday update for September 2024.
The monthly security release addresses a total of 79 vulnerabilities, of which seven are rated Critical, 71 are rated Important, and one is rated Moderate in severity. This is aside from 26 flaws that the tech]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti Releases Urgent Security Updates for Endpoint Manager Vulnerabilities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ivanti-releases-urgent-security-updates.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ivanti-releases-urgent-security-updates.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-11T06:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ivanti has released software updates to address multiple security flaws impacting Endpoint Manager (EPM), including 10 critical vulnerabilities that could result in remote code execution.
A brief description of the issues is as follows -

CVE-2024-29847 (CVSS score: 10.0) - A deserialization of untrusted data vulnerability that allows a remote unauthenticated attacker to achieve code execution.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[CosmicBeetle Deploys Custom ScRansom Ransomware, Partnering with RansomHub]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cosmicbeetle-deploys-custom-scransom.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cosmicbeetle-deploys-custom-scransom.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T15:48:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor known as CosmicBeetle has debuted a new custom ransomware strain called ScRansom in attacks targeting small- and medium-sized businesses (SMBs) in Europe, Asia, Africa, and South America, while also likely working as an affiliate for RansomHub.
"CosmicBeetle replaced its previously deployed ransomware, Scarab, with ScRansom, which is continually improved," ESET researcher Jakub]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans SonicWall (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-011/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/alerte/CERTFR-2024-ALE-011/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T12:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le 22 août 2024, Sonicwall a publié un correctif concernant la vulnérabilité critique CVE-2024-40766 affectant les pare-feux Sonicwall génération 5, 6 et 7. Cette vulnérabilité, de type contrôle d'accès défaillant, permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Siemens (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0757/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0757/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:56:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Siemens. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moodle (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0756/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0756/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:53:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moodle. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Experts Identify 3 Chinese-Linked Clusters Behind Cyberattacks in Southeast Asia]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/experts-identify-3-chinese-linked.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/experts-identify-3-chinese-linked.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A trio of threat activity clusters linked to China has been observed compromising more government organizations in Southeast Asia as part of a renewed state-sponsored operation codenamed Crimson Palace, indicating an expansion in the scope of the espionage effort.
Cybersecurity firm Sophos, which has been monitoring the cyber offensive, said it comprises three intrusion sets tracked as Cluster]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Shining a Light on Shadow Apps: The Invisible Gateway to SaaS Data Breaches]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/shining-light-on-shadow-apps-invisible.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/shining-light-on-shadow-apps-invisible.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T11:21:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Shadow apps, a segment of Shadow IT, are SaaS applications purchased without the knowledge of the security team. While these applications may be legitimate, they operate within the blind spots of the corporate security team and expose the company to attackers. 
Shadow apps may include instances of software that the company is already using. For example, a dev team may onboard their own]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New PIXHELL Attack Exploits Screen Noise to Exfiltrates Data from Air-Gapped Computers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-pixhell-attack-exploits-screen.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-pixhell-attack-exploits-screen.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T10:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new side-channel attack dubbed PIXHELL could be abused to target air-gapped computers by breaching the "audio gap" and exfiltrating sensitive information by taking advantage of the noise generated by the pixels on the screen.
"Malware in the air-gap and audio-gap computers generates crafted pixel patterns that produce noise in the frequency range of 0 - 22 kHz," Dr. Mordechai Guri, the head of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Mustang Panda Deploys Advanced Malware to Spy on Asia-Pacific Governments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mustang-panda-deploys-advanced-malware.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/mustang-panda-deploys-advanced-malware.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T09:57:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The threat actor tracked as Mustang Panda has refined its malware arsenal to include new tools in order to facilitate data exfiltration and the deployment of next-stage payloads, according to new findings from Trend Micro.
The cybersecurity firm, which is monitoring the activity cluster under the name Earth Preta, said it observed "the propagation of PUBLOAD via a variant of the worm HIUPAN."]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synology SRM (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0755/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0755/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T09:41:18.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synology SRM. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits SAP (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0754/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0754/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T09:39:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SAP. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à la confidentialité des données, une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits OwnCloud (10 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0753/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0753/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-10T08:25:06.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits OwnCloud. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une atteinte à l'intégrité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New RAMBO Attack Uses RAM Radio Signals to Steal Data from Air-Gapped Networks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rambo-attack-uses-ram-radio-signals.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rambo-attack-uses-ram-radio-signals.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T17:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A novel side-channel attack has been found to leverage radio signals emanated by a device's random access memory (RAM) as a data exfiltration mechanism, posing a threat to air-gapped networks.
The technique has been codenamed RAMBO by Dr. Mordechai Guri, the head of the Offensive Cyber Research Lab in the Department of Software and Information Systems Engineering at the Ben Gurion University of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[One More Tool Will Do It? Reflecting on the CrowdStrike Fallout]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/one-more-tool-will-do-it-reflecting-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/one-more-tool-will-do-it-reflecting-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T12:34:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The proliferation of cybersecurity tools has created an illusion of security. Organizations often believe that by deploying a firewall, antivirus software, intrusion detection systems, identity threat detection and response, and other tools, they are adequately protected. However, this approach not only fails to address the fundamental issue of the attack surface but also introduces dangerous]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Blind Eagle Targets Colombian Insurance Sector with Customized Quasar RAT]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/blind-eagle-targets-colombian-insurance.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/blind-eagle-targets-colombian-insurance.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T12:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Colombian insurance sector is the target of a threat actor tracked as Blind Eagle with the end goal of delivering a customized version of a known commodity remote access trojan (RAT) known as Quasar RAT since June 2024.
"Attacks have originated with phishing emails impersonating the Colombian tax authority," Zscaler ThreatLabz researcher Gaetano Pellegrino said in a new analysis published]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese Hackers Exploit Visual Studio Code in Southeast Asian Cyberattacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-exploit-visual-studio.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-hackers-exploit-visual-studio.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T12:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The China-linked advanced persistent threat (APT) group known as Mustang Panda has been observed weaponizing Visual Studio Code software as part of espionage operations targeting government entities in Southeast Asia.
"This threat actor used Visual Studio Code's embedded reverse shell feature to gain a foothold in target networks," Palo Alto Networks Unit 42 researcher Tom Fakterman said in a]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: How to Protect Your Company from GenAI Data Leakage Without Losing It’s Productivity Benefits]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-how-to-protect-your-company.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-how-to-protect-your-company.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T11:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[GenAI has become a table stakes tool for employees, due to the productivity gains and innovative capabilities it offers. Developers use it to write code, finance teams use it to analyze reports, and sales teams create customer emails and assets. Yet, these capabilities are exactly the ones that introduce serious security risks.
Register to our upcoming webinar to learn how to prevent GenAI data]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Wing Security SaaS Pulse: Continuous Security & Actionable Insights — For Free]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wing-security-saas-pulse-continuous.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/wing-security-saas-pulse-continuous.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T10:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Designed to be more than a one-time assessment— Wing Security’s SaaS Pulse provides organizations with actionable insights and continuous oversight into their SaaS security posture—and it’s free!
Introducing SaaS Pulse: Free Continuous SaaS Risk Management 
Just like waiting for a medical issue to become critical before seeing a doctor, organizations can’t afford to overlook the constantly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Qnap (09 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0752/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0752/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T09:38:58.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Qnap. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software Issues Patch for Vulnerability in LoadMaster and MT Hypervisor]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-issues-patch-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/progress-software-issues-patch-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T09:24:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Progress Software has released security updates for a maximum-severity flaw in LoadMaster and Multi-Tenant (MT) hypervisor that could result in the execution of arbitrary operating system commands.
Tracked as CVE-2024-7591 (CVSS score: 10.0), the vulnerability has been described as an improper input validation bug that results in OS command injection.
"It is possible for unauthenticated, remote]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Android SpyAgent Malware Uses OCR to Steal Crypto Wallet Recovery Keys]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-android-spyagent-malware-uses-ocr.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-android-spyagent-malware-uses-ocr.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T08:50:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Android device users in South Korea have emerged as a target of a new mobile malware campaign that delivers a new type of threat dubbed SpyAgent.
The malware "targets mnemonic keys by scanning for images on your device that might contain them," McAfee Labs researcher SangRyol Ryu said in an analysis, adding the targeting footprint has broadened in scope to include the U.K.
The campaign makes use]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (09 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0751/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0751/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T08:07:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-040 (09 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-040/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-040/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T07:27:45.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[TIDRONE Espionage Group Targets Taiwan Drone Makers in Cyber Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/tidrone-espionage-group-targets-taiwan.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/tidrone-espionage-group-targets-taiwan.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T05:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A previously undocumented threat actor with likely ties to Chinese-speaking groups has predominantly singled out drone manufacturers in Taiwan as part of a cyber attack campaign that commenced in 2024.
Trend Micro is tracking the adversary under the moniker TIDRONE, stating the activity is espionage-driven given the focus on military-related industry chains.
The exact initial access vector used]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Offers $10 Million for Info on Russian Cadet Blizzard Hackers Behind Major Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-offers-10-million-for-info-on.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-offers-10-million-for-info-on.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-09T04:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. government and a coalition of international partners have officially attributed a Russian hacking group tracked as Cadet Blizzard to the General Staff Main Intelligence Directorate (GRU) 161st Specialist Training Center (Unit 29155).
"These cyber actors are responsible for computer network operations against global targets for the purposes of espionage, sabotage, and reputational harm]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Threat Actors Deploy COVERTCATCH Malware via LinkedIn Job Scams]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-threat-actors-deploy.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-threat-actors-deploy.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T07:28:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors affiliated with North Korea have been observed leveraging LinkedIn as a way to target developers as part of a fake job recruiting operation.

These attacks employ coding tests as a common initial infection vector, Google-owned Mandiant said in a new report about threats faced by the Web3 sector.

"After an initial chat conversation, the attacker sent a ZIP file that contained]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[FBI Cracks Down on Dark Web Marketplace Managed by Russian and Kazakh Nationals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/fbi-cracks-down-on-dark-web-marketplace.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/fbi-cracks-down-on-dark-web-marketplace.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-07T07:10:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Two men have been indicted in the U.S. for their alleged involvement in managing a dark web marketplace called WWH Club that specializes in the sale of sensitive personal and financial information.
Alex Khodyrev, a 35-year-old Kazakhstan national, and Pavel Kublitskii, a 37-year-old Russian national, have been charged with conspiracy to commit access device fraud and conspiracy to commit wire]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall Urges Users to Patch Critical Firewall Flaw Amid Possible Exploitation]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/sonicwall-urges-users-to-patch-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/sonicwall-urges-users-to-patch-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[SonicWall has revealed that a recently patched critical security flaw impacting SonicOS may have come under active exploitation, making it essential that users apply the patches as soon as possible.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-40766, carries a CVSS score of 9.3 out of a maximum of 10.
"An improper access control vulnerability has been identified in the SonicWall SonicOS management]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GeoServer Vulnerability Targeted by Hackers to Deliver Backdoors and Botnet Malware]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/geoserver-vulnerability-targeted-by.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/geoserver-vulnerability-targeted-by.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:14:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently disclosed security flaw in OSGeo GeoServer GeoTools has been exploited as part of multiple campaigns to deliver cryptocurrency miners, botnet malware such as Condi and JenX, and a known backdoor called SideWalk.
The security vulnerability is a critical remote code execution bug (CVE-2024-36401, CVSS score: 9.8) that could allow malicious actors to take over susceptible instances.
In]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[GitHub Actions Vulnerable to Typosquatting, Exposing Developers to Hidden Malicious Code]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/github-actions-vulnerable-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/github-actions-vulnerable-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T15:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors have long leveraged typosquatting as a means to trick unsuspecting users into visiting malicious websites or downloading booby-trapped software and packages.

These attacks typically involve registering domains or packages with names slightly altered from their legitimate counterparts (e.g., goog1e.com vs. google.com).

Adversaries targeting open-source repositories across]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0750/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0750/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:23:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0749/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0749/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T13:18:31.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0748/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0748/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:17:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0747/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0747/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T11:15:41.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans le noyau Linux de SUSE. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The State of the Virtual CISO Report: MSP/MSSP Security Strategies for 2025]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-state-of-virtual-ciso-report.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The 2024 State of the vCISO Report continues Cynomi’s tradition of examining the growing popularity of virtual Chief Information Security Officer (vCISO) services. According to the independent survey, the demand for these services is increasing, with both providers and clients reaping the rewards. The upward trend is set to continue, with even faster growth expected in the future. However,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Critical Security Flaw Found in LiteSpeed Cache Plugin for WordPress]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-security-flaw-found-in.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/critical-security-flaw-found-in.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have discovered yet another critical security flaw in the LiteSpeed Cache plugin for WordPress that could allow unauthenticated users to take control of arbitrary accounts.
The vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-44000 (CVSS score: 7.5), impacts versions before and including 6.4.1. It has been addressed in version 6.5.0.1. 
"The plugin suffers from an]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Elastic Kibana (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0746/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0746/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T06:10:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Elastic Kibana. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits Asterisk (06 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0745/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0745/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:59:20.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans les produits Asterisk. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Apache OFBiz Update Fixes High-Severity Flaw Leading to Remote Code Execution]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apache-ofbiz-update-fixes-high-severity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/apache-ofbiz-update-fixes-high-severity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T05:22:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new security flaw has been addressed in the Apache OFBiz open-source enterprise resource planning (ERP) system that, if successfully exploited, could lead to unauthenticated remote code execution on Linux and Windows.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-45195 (CVSS score: 7.5), affects all versions of the software before 18.12.16.


"An attacker with no valid]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Pavel Durov Criticizes Outdated Laws After Arrest Over Telegram Criminal Activity]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/paul-durov-criticizes-outdated-laws.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/paul-durov-criticizes-outdated-laws.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-06T04:02:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Telegram CEO Pavel Durov has broken his silence nearly two weeks after his arrest in France, stating the charges are misguided.
"If a country is unhappy with an internet service, the established practice is to start a legal action against the service itself," Durov said in a 600-word statement on his Telegram account.
"Using laws from the pre-smartphone era to charge a CEO with crimes committed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-Speaking Hacker Group Targets Human Rights Studies in Middle East]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-speaking-hacker-group-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/chinese-speaking-hacker-group-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Unnamed government entities in the Middle East and Malaysia are the target of a persistent cyber campaign orchestrated by a threat actor known as Tropic Trooper since June 2023.
"Sighting this group's [Tactics, Techniques, and Procedures] in critical governmental entities in the Middle East, particularly those related to human rights studies, marks a new strategic move for them," Kaspersky]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam Releases Security Updates to Fix 18 Flaws, Including 5 Critical Issues]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/veeam-releases-security-updates-to-fix.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/veeam-releases-security-updates-to-fix.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T16:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Veeam has shipped security updates to address a total of 18 security flaws impacting its software products, including five critical vulnerabilities that could result in remote code execution.
The list of shortcomings is below -

CVE-2024-40711 (CVSS score: 9.8) - A vulnerability in Veeam Backup & Replication that allows unauthenticated remote code execution.


CVE-2024-42024 (CVSS score: 9.1]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans ClamAV (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0744/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0744/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T12:16:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans ClamAV. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une atteinte à l'intégrité des données et un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Seizes 32 Pro-Russian Propaganda Domains in Major Disinformation Crackdown]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-seizes-32-pro-russian-propaganda.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/us-seizes-32-pro-russian-propaganda.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T12:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The U.S. Department of Justice (DoJ) on Wednesday announced the seizure of 32 internet domains used by a pro-Russian propaganda operation called Doppelganger as part of a sweeping set of actions.
Accusing the Russian government-directed foreign malign influence campaign of violating U.S. money laundering and criminal trademark laws, the agency called out companies Social Design Agency (SDA),]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Centreon Web (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0743/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0743/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:30:29.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Centreon web. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[NIST Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) and CTEM – Better Together]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/nist-cybersecurity-framework-csf-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/nist-cybersecurity-framework-csf-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T09:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[It’s been a decade since the National Institute of Standards and Technology (NIST) introduced its Cybersecurity Framework (CSF) 1.0. Created following a 2013 Executive Order, NIST was tasked with designing a voluntary cybersecurity framework that would help organizations manage cyber risk, providing guidance based on established standards and best practices. While this version was originally]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malware Attackers Using MacroPack to Deliver Havoc, Brute Ratel, and PhantomCore]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malware-attackers-using-macropack-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malware-attackers-using-macropack-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:45:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are likely employing a tool designated for red teaming exercises to serve malware, according to new findings from Cisco Talos.

The program in question is a payload generation framework called MacroPack, which is used to generate Office documents, Visual Basic scripts, Windows shortcuts, and other formats for penetration testing and social engineering assessments. It was developed]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0742/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0742/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:41:14.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Synacor Zimbra Collaboration. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Juniper Secure Analytics (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0741/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0741/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T07:26:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Juniper Secure Analytics. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un déni de service à distance et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Veeam (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0740/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0740/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T06:54:28.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Veeam. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Cisco (05 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0739/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0739/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T06:36:40.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Cisco. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cross-Platform Malware KTLVdoor Discovered in Attack on Chinese Trading Firm]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-cross-platform-malware-ktlvdoor.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-cross-platform-malware-ktlvdoor.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T05:03:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Chinese-speaking threat actor known as Earth Lusca has been observed using a new backdoor dubbed KTLVdoor as part of a cyber attack targeting an unnamed trading company based in China.

The previously unreported malware is written in Golang, and thus is a cross-platform weapon capable of targeting both Microsoft Windows and Linux systems.

"KTLVdoor is a highly obfuscated malware that]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco Fixes Two Critical Flaws in Smart Licensing Utility to Prevent Remote Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisco-fixes-two-critical-flaws-in-smart.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/cisco-fixes-two-critical-flaws-in-smart.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-05T04:40:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cisco has released security updates for two critical security flaws impacting its Smart Licensing Utility that could allow unauthenticated, remote attackers to elevate their privileges or access sensitive information.
A brief description of the two vulnerabilities is below -

CVE-2024-20439 (CVSS score: 9.8) - The presence of an undocumented static user credential for an administrative account]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Targets Job Seekers with Fake FreeConference App]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-targets-job.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/north-korean-hackers-targets-job.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T15:52:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean threat actors have leveraged a fake Windows video conferencing application impersonating FreeConference.com to backdoor developer systems as part of an ongoing financially-driven campaign dubbed Contagious Interview.
The new attack wave, spotted by Singaporean company Group-IB in mid-August 2024, is yet another indication that the activity is also leveraging native installers for]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Google Confirms CVE-2024-32896 Exploited in the Wild, Releases Android Security Patch]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-confirms-cve-2024-32896.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/google-confirms-cve-2024-32896.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Google has released its monthly security updates for the Android operating system to address a known security flaw that it said has come under active exploitation in the wild.
The high-severity vulnerability, tracked as CVE-2024-32896 (CVSS score: 7.8), relates to a case of privilege escalation in the Android Framework component.
According to the description of the bug in the NIST National]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Hijack 22,000 Removed PyPI Packages, Spreading Malicious Code to Developers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-hijack-22000-removed-pypi.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-hijack-22000-removed-pypi.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T13:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new supply chain attack technique targeting the Python Package Index (PyPI) registry has been exploited in the wild in an attempt to infiltrate downstream organizations.
It has been codenamed Revival Hijack by software supply chain security firm JFrog, which said the attack method could be used to hijack 22,000 existing PyPI packages and result in "hundreds of thousands" of malicious package]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0738/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0738/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T12:10:36.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans Synacor Zimbra Desktop. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Moxa OnCell 3120-LTE-1 Series (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0737/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0737/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T12:02:16.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Moxa OnCell 3120-LTE-1 Series. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel Patches Critical OS Command Injection Flaw in Access Points and Routers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/zyxel-patches-critical-os-command.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/zyxel-patches-critical-os-command.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T11:27:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Zyxel has released software updates to address a critical security flaw impacting certain access point (AP) and security router versions that could result in the execution of unauthorized commands.

Tracked as CVE-2024-7261 (CVSS score: 9.8), the vulnerability has been described as a case of operating system (OS) command injection.

"The improper neutralization of special elements in the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[The New Effective Way to Prevent Account Takeovers]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-new-effective-way-to-prevent.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/the-new-effective-way-to-prevent.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T10:54:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Account takeover attacks have emerged as one of the most persistent and damaging threats to cloud-based SaaS environments. Yet despite significant investments in traditional security measures, many organizations continue to struggle with preventing these attacks. A new report, "Why Account Takeover Attacks Still Succeed, and Why the Browser is Your Secret Weapon in Stopping Them" argues that the]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Clearview AI Faces €30.5M Fine for Building Illegal Facial Recognition Database]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/clearview-ai-faces-305m-fine-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/clearview-ai-faces-305m-fine-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T08:43:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The Dutch Data Protection Authority (Dutch DPA) has imposed a fine of €30.5 million ($33.7 million) against facial recognition firm Clearview AI for violating the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) in the European Union (E.U.) by building an "illegal database with billions of photos of faces," including those of Dutch citizens.
"Facial recognition is a highly intrusive technology that you]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans OpenSSL (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0736/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0736/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T07:27:25.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans OpenSSL. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Mozilla (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0735/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0735/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T07:18:08.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Mozilla. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, un contournement de la politique de sécurité et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans CPython (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0734/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0734/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T06:07:54.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans CPython. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits Google (04 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0733/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0733/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T06:00:22.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Google. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire à distance, une élévation de privilèges et une atteinte à la confidentialité des données.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hackers Use Fake GlobalProtect VPN Software in New WikiLoader Malware Attack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-use-fake-globalprotect-vpn.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hackers-use-fake-globalprotect-vpn.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-04T05:31:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A new malware campaign is spoofing Palo Alto Networks' GlobalProtect VPN software to deliver a variant of the WikiLoader (aka WailingCrab) loader by means of a search engine optimization (SEO) campaign.

The malvertising activity, observed in June 2024, is a departure from previously observed tactics wherein the malware has been propagated via traditional phishing emails, Unit 42 researchers]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hacktivists Exploits WinRAR Vulnerability in Attacks Against Russia and Belarus]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivists-exploits-winrar.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/hacktivists-exploits-winrar.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T13:29:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A hacktivist group known as Head Mare has been linked to cyber attacks that exclusively target organizations located in Russia and Belarus.
"Head Mare uses more up-to-date methods for obtaining initial access," Kaspersky said in a Monday analysis of the group's tactics and tools.
"For instance, the attackers took advantage of the relatively recent CVE-2023-38831 vulnerability in WinRAR, which]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Rust-Based Ransomware Cicada3301 Targets Windows and Linux Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rust-based-ransomware-cicada3301.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-rust-based-ransomware-cicada3301.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T13:16:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unpacked the inner workings of a new ransomware variant called Cicada3301 that shares similarities with the now-defunct BlackCat (aka ALPHV) operation.
"It appears that Cicada3301 ransomware primarily targets small to medium-sized businesses (SMBs), likely through opportunistic attacks that exploit vulnerabilities as the initial access vector," cybersecurity]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vulnérabilité dans les produits VMware (03 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0732/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0732/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T11:11:23.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Une vulnérabilité a été découverte dans VMware Fusion. Elle permet à un attaquant de provoquer une exécution de code arbitraire.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Rocinante Trojan Poses as Banking Apps to Steal Sensitive Data from Brazilian Android Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/rocinante-trojan-poses-as-banking-apps.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/rocinante-trojan-poses-as-banking-apps.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T09:37:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Mobile users in Brazil are the target of a new malware campaign that delivers a new Android banking trojan named Rocinante.

"This malware family is capable of performing keylogging using the Accessibility Service, and is also able to steal PII from its victims using phishing screens posing as different banks," Dutch security company ThreatFabric said.

"Finally, it can use all this exfiltrated]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Secrets Exposed: Why Your CISO Should Worry About Slack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/secrets-exposed-why-your-ciso-should.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/secrets-exposed-why-your-ciso-should.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T07:30:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[In the digital realm, secrets (API keys, private keys, username and password combos, etc.) are the keys to the kingdom. But what if those keys were accidentally left out in the open in the very tools we use to collaborate every day?
A Single Secret Can Wreak Havoc
Imagine this: It's a typical Tuesday in June 2024. Your dev team is knee-deep in sprints, Jira tickets are flying, and Slack is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans Google Chrome (03 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0731/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0731/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T06:05:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans Google Chrome. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Flaws in Microsoft macOS Apps Could Allow Hackers to Gain Unrestricted Access]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-flaws-in-microsoft-macos-apps-could.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/new-flaws-in-microsoft-macos-apps-could.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T04:01:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Eight vulnerabilities have been uncovered in Microsoft applications for macOS that an adversary could exploit to gain elevated privileges or access sensitive data by circumventing the operating system's permissions-based model, which revolves around the Transparency, Consent, and Control (TCC) framework.
"If successful, the adversary could gain any privileges already granted to the affected]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Ex-Engineer Charged in Missouri for Failed $750,000 Bitcoin Extortion Attempt]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ex-engineer-charged-in-missouri-for.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ex-engineer-charged-in-missouri-for.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-03T01:58:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A 57-year-old man from the U.S. state of Missouri has been arrested in connection with a failed data extortion campaign that targeted his former employer.
Daniel Rhyne of Kansas City, Missouri, has been charged with one count of extortion in relation to a threat to cause damage to a protected computer, one count of intentional damage to a protected computer, and one count of wire fraud.
He was]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Organismes de recherche et think tanks - État de la menace informatique (02 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-008/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/cti/CERTFR-2024-CTI-008/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T15:18:38.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Le secteur de la recherche et des *think tanks* couvre un périmètre large et hétéroclite. Celui-ci comprend des entités publiques et privées de toute nature, dont certaines peuvent être des fondations, des organisations internationales ou des associations. Ces entités sont ciblées par un vaste...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[RansomHub Ransomware Group Targets 210 Victims Across Critical Sectors]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ransomhub-ransomware-group-targets-210.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/ransomhub-ransomware-group-targets-210.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T13:33:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors linked to the RansomHub ransomware group encrypted and exfiltrated data from at least 210 victims since its inception in February 2024, the U.S. government said.
The victims span various sectors, including water and wastewater, information technology, government services and facilities, healthcare and public health, emergency services, food and agriculture, financial services,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Bulletin d'actualité CERTFR-2024-ACT-039 (02 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-039/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/actualite/CERTFR-2024-ACT-039/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T12:27:51.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Ce bulletin d’actualité du CERT-FR revient sur les vulnérabilités significatives de la semaine passée pour souligner leurs criticités. Il ne remplace pas l’analyse de l’ensemble des avis et alertes publiés par le CERT-FR dans le cadre d’une analyse de risques pour prioriser l’application des...]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans MISP (02 septembre 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0730/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0730/"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T11:36:26.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans MISP. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS) et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Webinar: Learn to Boost Cybersecurity with AI-Powered Vulnerability Management]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-learn-to-boost-cybersecurity.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/webinar-learn-to-boost-cybersecurity.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T08:55:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The world of cybersecurity is in a constant state of flux. New vulnerabilities emerge daily, and attackers are becoming more sophisticated.
In this high-stakes game, security leaders need every advantage they can get. That's where Artificial Intelligence (AI) comes in. AI isn't just a buzzword; it's a game-changer for vulnerability management.
AI is poised to revolutionize vulnerability]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Next-Generation Attacks, Same Targets - How to Protect Your Users' Identities]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/next-generation-attacks-same-targets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/next-generation-attacks-same-targets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T07:00:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The FBI and CISA Issue Joint Advisory on New Threats and How to Stop Ransomware
Note: on August 29, the FBI and CISA issued a joint advisory as part of their ongoing #StopRansomware effort to help organizations protect against ransomware. The latest advisory, AA24-242A, describes a new cybercriminal group and its attack methods. It also details three important actions to take today to mitigate]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Malicious npm Packages Mimicking 'noblox.js' Compromise Roblox Developers’ Systems]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malicious-npm-packages-mimicking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/09/malicious-npm-packages-mimicking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-09-02T03:36:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Roblox developers are the target of a persistent campaign that seeks to compromise systems through bogus npm packages, once again underscoring how threat actors continue to exploit the trust in the open-source ecosystem to deliver malware.
"By mimicking the popular 'noblox.js' library, attackers have published dozens of packages designed to steal sensitive data and compromise systems," Checkmarx]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Deploy FudModule Rootkit via Chrome Zero-Day Exploit]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-fudmodule.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-deploy-fudmodule.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-31T15:35:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A recently patched security flaw in Google Chrome and other Chromium web browsers was exploited as a zero-day by North Korean actors in a campaign designed to deliver the FudModule rootkit.
The development is indicative of the persistent efforts made by the nation-state adversary, which had made a habit of incorporating rafts of Windows zero-day exploits into its arsenal in recent months.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Cyberattackers Exploit Google Sheets for Malware Control in Global Espionage Campaign]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cyberattackers-exploit-google-sheets.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/cyberattackers-exploit-google-sheets.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T13:04:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have uncovered a novel malware campaign that leverages Google Sheets as a command-and-control (C2) mechanism.
The activity, detected by Proofpoint starting August 5, 2024, impersonates tax authorities from governments in Europe, Asia, and the U.S., with the goal of targeting over 70 organizations worldwide by means of a bespoke tool called Voldemort that's equipped to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de SUSE (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0729/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0729/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:55:33.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits SUSE. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer une élévation de privilèges, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux de Red Hat (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0728/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0728/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:54:59.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Red Hat. Elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance et un problème de sécurité non spécifié par l'éditeur.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans le noyau Linux d'Ubuntu (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0727/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0727/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:47:11.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits Ubuntu. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et un contournement de la politique de sécurité.]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Multiples vulnérabilités dans les produits IBM (30 août 2024)]]></title>
        <id>https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0726/</id>
        <link href="https://www.cert.ssi.gouv.fr/avis/CERTFR-2024-AVI-0726/"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:41:19.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[De multiples vulnérabilités ont été découvertes dans les produits IBM. Certaines d'entre elles permettent à un attaquant de provoquer un déni de service à distance, une atteinte à la confidentialité des données et une injection de code indirecte à distance (XSS).]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>CERT-FR</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Iranian Hackers Set Up New Network to Target U.S. Political Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-hackers-set-up-new-network-to.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/iranian-hackers-set-up-new-network-to.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T11:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have unearthed new network infrastructure set up by Iranian threat actors to support activities linked to the recent targeting of U.S. political campaigns.
Recorded Future's Insikt Group has linked the infrastructure to a threat it tracks as GreenCharlie, an Iran-nexus cyber threat group that overlaps with APT42, Charming Kitten, Damselfly, Mint Sandstorm (formerly]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Malware Masquerades as Palo Alto VPN Targeting Middle East Users]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-masquerades-as-palo-alto.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-malware-masquerades-as-palo-alto.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T10:20:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have disclosed a new campaign that potentially targets users in the Middle East through malware that disguises itself as Palo Alto Networks GlobalProtect virtual private network (VPN) tool.

"The malware can execute remote PowerShell commands, download and exfiltrate files, encrypt communications, and bypass sandbox solutions, representing a significant threat to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Breaking Down AD CS Vulnerabilities: Insights for InfoSec Professionals]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/breaking-down-ad-cs-vulnerabilities.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/breaking-down-ad-cs-vulnerabilities.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T09:39:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[The most dangerous vulnerability you’ve never heard of.
In the world of cybersecurity, vulnerabilities are discovered so often, and at such a high rate, that it can be very difficult to keep up with. Some vulnerabilities will start ringing alarm bells within your security tooling, while others are far more nuanced, but still pose an equally dangerous threat. Today, we want to discuss one of]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[North Korean Hackers Target Developers with Malicious npm Packages]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-target-developers.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/north-korean-hackers-target-developers.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:25:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors with ties to North Korea have been observed publishing a set of malicious packages to the npm registry, indicating "coordinated and relentless" efforts to target developers with malware and steal cryptocurrency assets.
The latest wave, which was observed between August 12 and 27, 2024, involved packages named temp-etherscan-api, ethersscan-api, telegram-con, helmet-validate, and]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[SANS Institute Unveils Critical Infrastructure Strategy Guide for 2024: A Call to Action for Securing ICS/OT Environments]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sans-institute-unveils-critical.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/sans-institute-unveils-critical.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:19:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A comprehensive guide authored by Dean Parsons emphasizes the growing need for specialized ICS security measures in the face of rising cyber threats.
With a staggering 50% increase in ransomware attacks targeting industrial control systems (ICS) in 2023, the SANS Institute is taking decisive action by announcing the release of its essential new strategy guide, "ICS Is the Business: Why Securing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[New Cyberattack Targets Chinese-Speaking Businesses with Cobalt Strike Payloads]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyberattack-targets-chinese.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/new-cyberattack-targets-chinese.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:17:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Chinese-speaking users are the target of a "highly organized and sophisticated attack" campaign that is likely leveraging phishing emails to infect Windows systems with Cobalt Strike payloads.
"The attackers managed to move laterally, establish persistence and remain undetected within the systems for more than two weeks," Securonix researchers Den Iuzvyk and Tim Peck said in a new report.
The]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Atlassian Confluence Vulnerability Exploited in Crypto Mining Campaigns]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/atlassian-confluence-vulnerability.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/atlassian-confluence-vulnerability.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-30T06:12:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Threat actors are actively exploiting a now-patched, critical security flaw impacting the Atlassian Confluence Data Center and Confluence Server to conduct illicit cryptocurrency mining on susceptible instances.
"The attacks involve threat actors that employ methods such as the deployment of shell scripts and XMRig miners, targeting of SSH endpoints, killing competing crypto mining processes,]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Vietnamese Human Rights Group Targeted in Multi-Year Cyberattack by APT32]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/vietnamese-human-rights-group-targeted.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/vietnamese-human-rights-group-targeted.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T16:15:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A non-profit supporting Vietnamese human rights has been the target of a multi-year campaign designed to deliver a variety of malware on compromised hosts.
Cybersecurity company Huntress attributed the activity to a threat cluster known as APT32, a Vietnamese-aligned hacking crew that's also known as APT-C-00, Canvas Cyclone (formerly Bismuth), Cobalt Kitty, and OceanLotus. The intrusion is]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Exploit Safari and Chrome Flaws in High-Profile Cyberattack]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-exploit-safari-and.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/russian-hackers-exploit-safari-and.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T15:59:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Cybersecurity researchers have flagged multiple in-the-wild exploit campaigns that leveraged now-patched flaws in Apple Safari and Google Chrome browsers to infect mobile users with information-stealing malware.
"These campaigns delivered n-day exploits for which patches were available, but would still be effective against unpatched devices," Google Threat Analysis Group (TAG) researcher Clement]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. Agencies Warn of Iranian Hacking Group's Ongoing Ransomware Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-agencies-warn-of-iranian-hacking.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/us-agencies-warn-of-iranian-hacking.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:42:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[U.S. cybersecurity and intelligence agencies have called out an Iranian hacking group for breaching multiple organizations across the country and coordinating with affiliates to deliver ransomware.
The activity has been linked to a threat actor dubbed Pioneer Kitten, which is also known as Fox Kitten, Lemon Sandstorm (formerly Rubidium), Parisite, and UNC757, which it described as connected to]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[How AitM Phishing Attacks Bypass MFA and EDR—and How to Fight Back]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-stop-aitm-phishing-attack.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/how-to-stop-aitm-phishing-attack.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:26:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[Attackers are increasingly using new phishing toolkits (open-source, commercial, and criminal) to execute adversary-in-the-middle (AitM) attacks.
AitM enables attackers to not just harvest credentials but steal live sessions, allowing them to bypass traditional phishing prevention controls such as MFA, EDR, and email content filtering.
In this article, we’re going to look at what AitM phishing]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
    <entry>
        <title type="html"><![CDATA[Unpatched AVTECH IP Camera Flaw Exploited by Hackers for Botnet Attacks]]></title>
        <id>https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpatched-avtech-ip-camera-flaw.html</id>
        <link href="https://thehackernews.com/2024/08/unpatched-avtech-ip-camera-flaw.html"/>
        <updated>2024-08-29T11:05:00.000Z</updated>
        <summary type="html"><![CDATA[A years-old high-severity flaw impacting AVTECH IP cameras has been weaponized by malicious actors as a zero-day to rope them into a botnet.
CVE-2024-7029 (CVSS score: 8.7), the vulnerability in question, is a "command injection vulnerability found in the brightness function of AVTECH closed-circuit television (CCTV) cameras that allows for remote code execution (RCE)," Akamai researchers Kyle]]></summary>
        <author>
            <name>info@thehackernews.com (The Hacker News)</name>
        </author>
    </entry>
</feed>